<programme channel="141429351" start="20210716053000 +0000" stop="20210716061500 +0000" catchup-id="979530234"><title>Murder, Mystery &amp; My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/43/20210709080027502wn4.jpg"></icon><desc>Criminal barristers Jeremy Dein and Sasha Wass look back at the case of John Dickman, who, after being convicted of murder in 1910, became the last man to be hanged at Newcastle Prison. On Friday 18 March 1910, 44-year-old John Nisbet boarded a 10:27am train from Newcastle Central Station. By the time the train reached the end of the line, he was dead. He had been shot five times; his bag, containing £370 in cash, had been stolen; and his body had been stuffed beneath the carriage seats.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716061500 +0000" stop="20210716070000 +0000" catchup-id="979530240"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/92/20210709080027502njp.jpg"></icon><desc>Anita Manning presents from Elsecar with experts Tim Weeks and Caroline Hawley. Both teams race around the antiques centre pursuing potential purchases for profit at auction, while Anita goes monkeying around with a Meissen collection.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716070000 +0000" stop="20210716080000 +0000" catchup-id="979530502"><title>The Great Northern Garden Build</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/95/20210709080027502ro8.jpg"></icon><desc>The RHS has been at the forefront of British gardening for more than 200 years. Best known for staging the world's most famous and prestigious flower show, Chelsea, it has four showcase gardens up and down the country.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716080000 +0000" stop="20210716090000 +0000" catchup-id="979530508"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/81/20210709080027502uwb.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716090000 +0000" stop="20210716120000 +0000" catchup-id="979530514"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/39/20210709080027502its.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716120000 +0000" stop="20210716123000 +0000" catchup-id="979530520"><title>Letterbox</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/65/202107090800275025qw.jpg"></icon><desc>Hosted by Mel Giedroyc, pairs of contestants go head-to-head to crack a series of passwords, in an attempt to take home £2,500 in cash.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716123000 +0000" stop="20210716131500 +0000" catchup-id="979530526"><title>Make Me a Dealer</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/76/20210709080027502i5j.jpg"></icon><desc>Pitching against each other are Steve Cuddy from Birmingham and Rusty Ashman from London.</desc><category>Doe-het-zelf, Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716131500 +0000" stop="20210716141500 +0000" catchup-id="979530532"><title>Rise of the Continents</title><date>2013</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/8/20210709080027502bu6.jpg"></icon><desc>Two hundred million years ago the continent we know as Eurasia didn't exist. Prof Iain Stewart shows that where the South of Eurasia is today there was once a ninety-million-square-kilometre Ocean known as the Tethys. It is the destruction of the Tethys Ocean that holds the key to Eurasia's formation. However, the formation of Eurasia is just the beginning of the story.</desc><category>Documentaire, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716141500 +0000" stop="20210716144500 +0000" catchup-id="979530538"><title>Great British Menu</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/36/2021070908002750398x.jpg"></icon><desc>Dessert is the last chance to secure a place in the regional final. Both Eddie Attwell and Tommy Heaney attempt technical desserts which feature white edible chocolate tennis balls, while Joery Castel cooks poffertjes, traditional Dutch pancakes.</desc><category>Culinair, Reality</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716144500 +0000" stop="20210716151500 +0000" catchup-id="979530544"><title>Great British Menu</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/71/20210709080027503q6o.jpg"></icon><desc>The two chefs who have made it through cook their four courses again. They are hoping to impress the formidable panel of judges, Oliver Peyton, Matthew Fort and Andi Oliver, who are joined by tennis's greatest entertainer, Mansour Bahrami.</desc><category>Culinair, Reality</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716151500 +0000" stop="20210716161500 +0000" catchup-id="979530550"><title>Gorilla Family and Me</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/97/20210709080027503xkq.jpg"></icon><desc>Gordon Buchanan returns to the Democratic Republic of Congo to discover the fate of his gorilla family. When he left, Chimanuka the silverback was being challenged by a rival. At stake were the lives of two of his children, Marhale the orphan and the baby Mwira. Having reconnected with his family, Gordon discovers they face a new threat - poachers in the forest.</desc><category>Documentaire, Dieren, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716161500 +0000" stop="20210716170000 +0000" catchup-id="979530556"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/62/202107090800275039al.jpg"></icon><desc>The team are at Dover Castle in Kent. Antique experts James Lewis and Catherine Southon search for items to take off to auction. James unearths a silver owl inkwell and Catherine discovers an alabaster bust. Paul Martin delves into the history of the English Channel.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716170000 +0000" stop="20210716173000 +0000" catchup-id="979530562"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/58/20210709080027503cfi.jpg"></icon><desc>Naga Munchetty, Jordan Stephens, Sally Lindsay and David O'Doherty take on a series of challenging quiz games selected by the host, teatime quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716173000 +0000" stop="20210716180000 +0000" catchup-id="979530568"><title>Animal Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/68/2021070908002750381g.jpg"></icon><desc>Kate Humble and Ben Fogle are back for another sun-drenched series following the lives of the exotic animals at Longleat Safari Park. Keepers Graeme and James travel to the other side of the world to help in the Australian bushfire rescue. Four of the park's koalas have come from the area of south Australia worst affected. The staff feel a deep sense of connection and are moved to help. They see first-hand the devastation caused by the bushfires and the seize the opportunity to make a real contribution to the rescue effort.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716180000 +0000" stop="20210716190000 +0000" catchup-id="979530574"><title>Monty Don's Japanese Gardens</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/96/20210709080027503s5k.jpg"></icon><desc>Monty Don returns to Japan during the fiery blaze of autumn. He visits the three great gardens of Japan to learn how they protect the garden from the coming winter and learns how the Japanese are weaving nature into their concrete urban jungle.</desc><category>Miniseries, Home &amp; Garden, Documentaire, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716190000 +0000" stop="20210716210000 +0000" catchup-id="979530580"><title>Golf: The Open Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/49/20210709080027503o02.jpg"></icon><desc>Eilidh Barbour brings you every twist and turn from the second round, with the Open being staged at Royal St George's on the Kent coastline for the first time in a decade. With the event cancelled last year because of the coronavirus pandemic, the defending champion from 2019 is Ireland's Shane Lowry. Back then, he shared the lead with American JB Holmes at the halfway point, while multiple Major winners Rory McIlroy, Tiger Woods and Phil Mickelson all missed the cut.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716210000 +0000" stop="20210716213000 +0000" catchup-id="979530586"><title>I'll Get This</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/97/2021070908002750310t.jpg"></icon><desc>Featuring Rylan Clark-Neal, Anton Du Beke, Carol Vorderman, Ed Gamble and Ellie Taylor.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716213000 +0000" stop="20210716220000 +0000" catchup-id="979530592"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210709/37/202107090800275031ck.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716220000 +0000" stop="20210716220500 +0000" catchup-id="980898672"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/29/202107100801051481vd.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716220500 +0000" stop="20210716230500 +0000" catchup-id="980898678"><title>Cricket: England v Pakistan T20 Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/10/20210710080105148fng.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of the first T20 international between England and Pakistan.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210716230500 +0000" stop="20210717005000 +0000" catchup-id="980898684"><title>Goldstone</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/86/20210710080105148itp.jpg"></icon><desc>Indigenous detective Jay Swan arrives in the town of Goldstone to search for a missing person, and his simple duty becomes complicated when he uncovers a web of crime and corruption.</desc><category>Film, Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717005000 +0000" stop="20210717012000 +0000" catchup-id="980899202"><title>Long Covid: Will I Ever Get Better? - Panorama</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/29/20210710080105148hks.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC correspondent Lucy Adams is one of more than a million people in the UK with long Covid. She has been suffering a range of symptoms for more than a year and wants to know why. Panorama follows her as she speaks to doctors with increasing caseloads, leading scientists carrying out research and other patients desperate to know when they will be well again. [SL]</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717012000 +0000" stop="20210717022000 +0000" catchup-id="984534806"><title>Dragons' Den</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/29/20210713080052464ji9.jpg"></icon><desc>Facing the Dragons: a digital entrepreneur with her online hypno-birthing platforms, two business partners from the north east with a unique recycled building system, a plant-based, biodegradable chewing gum start-up, and a dynamic pair of jewellers with their bespoke ring-making kits. When this last pair lose their grip on the numbers, their proposition appears to be more of a diamond in the rough than a glittering opportunity.</desc><category>Business &amp; Financial, Reality, Podiumkunsten</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717022000 +0000" stop="20210717053500 +0000" catchup-id="980899214"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/35/2021071008010514821v.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717053500 +0000" stop="20210717055000 +0000" catchup-id="980899220"><title>Wild &amp; Weird</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/37/202107100801051484uw.jpg"></icon><desc>Tim Warwood and Naomi Wilkinson introduce another collection of weird clips from the natural world, this time all the stories are themed around the strange places animals set up home. Among them, penguins nesting in a garden, pigs swimming in the sea and a fish that lives inside the bottom of another oceanic dweller, the sea cucumber.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717055000 +0000" stop="20210717062000 +0000" catchup-id="980899226"><title>The Dengineers</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/95/20210710080105148c8s.jpg"></icon><desc>11-year-old Tali started doing magic when she was three and has packs of cards in every room of the house to ensure a magic trick is never far away. She is frustrated that there have not been any great female magicians and wants to change that. She needs a magic den where she can practice her tricks in secret, without giving the game away!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717062000 +0000" stop="20210717065000 +0000" catchup-id="980899232"><title>Marrying Mum &amp; Dad</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/18/202107121800424298rm.jpg"></icon><desc>Two sisters plan to put a very 'on-trend' wedding for their mum and soon-to-be step-dad with a fashion themed big day. With the help of Instagram sensation, make-up expert and Zayn Malik's sister, Doniya Malik, the girls put on a fashion show like you've never seen before, complete with a real catwalk fashion show.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717065000 +0000" stop="20210717072000 +0000" catchup-id="980899238"><title>Blue Peter: Goodbye Lindsey!</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/32/20210712180042429d15.jpg"></icon><desc>It is Lindsey's last time on the show as a Blue Peter presenter! After eight incredible years, Richie, Mwaksy and Adam are seeing her off in style in the BP studio with a show packed full of surprises. Also, it is the final part of her epic drift car racing challenge.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717072000 +0000" stop="20210717073000 +0000" catchup-id="980899244"><title>What's Cooking Omari?</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/12/20210710080105149q4y.jpg"></icon><desc>Chef Omari is creating his family's favourite snack - choccy oat bars. His yummy snack, filled with oats, syrup and chocolate, is the perfect treat!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717073000 +0000" stop="20210717080000 +0000" catchup-id="980899250"><title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/82/20210710080105149zgs.jpg"></icon><desc>Steve's on a mission to find dinosaurs that have something a little special... fearsome killers, with incredible abilities! Get ready for a sensory sensation! His quest sees him race in the dark like a troodon and track prey from miles away taking tips from the daspletosaurus, and finally he gets his hands on a real-life caiman to show how their pressure pits are just like that of the spinosaurus. Strap yourself in for a sensory overload!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717080000 +0000" stop="20210717090000 +0000" catchup-id="980899256"><title>Orbit: Earth's Extraordinary Journey</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/16/20210710080105149d1j.jpg"></icon><desc>Right now you're hurtling around the sun at 64,000 miles an hour (100,000km an hour). In the next year you'll travel 584 million miles, to end up back where you started. Presenters Kate Humble and Dr Helen Czerski follow the Earth's voyage around the sun for one complete orbit, to witness the astonishing consequences this journey has for us all. In this first episode they travel from July to the December solstice, experiencing spectacular weather and the largest tides on Earth. To show how the Earth's orbit affects our lives, Helen jumps out of an aeroplane and Kate briefly becomes the fastest driver on Earth.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717090000 +0000" stop="20210717100000 +0000" catchup-id="980899262"><title>Mountain: Life at the Extreme</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/74/2021071008010514973m.jpg"></icon><desc>The highest mountain range on earth is home to extraordinary animals and remarkable ancient cultures. In the depths of winter, snow leopards creep into isolated mountain villages in search of food. In hidden valleys, bizarre-looking monkeys huddle for warmth in a frozen forest. Ancient Buddhist monasteries have age-old rituals creating beautiful works of art made from mountain sand, and athletes compete in the gruelling Everest marathon. Strange and exotic creatures live in the Himalaya - the chiru, with the warmest wool in the world, snakes bathing in hot springs and wild yaks competing in their annual rut.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717100000 +0000" stop="20210717110000 +0000" catchup-id="980899332"><title>Life in the Air</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/89/20210710080105149vf7.jpg"></icon><desc>With the help of some surprising creatures from around the world, this series sets out to discover how animals take to the air, defying the force all airborne animals must conquer, gravity. This episode looks at powered flight, revealing why peregrine falcons can top 200 miles an hour, how a hummingbird is a slave to its own rather manic lifestyle and that the albatross's secret to flying for free is its nose. Heavyweight beetles break the rules to find love, a devious sparrow-hawk uses agility to execute a lightning-fast raid on his prey and half a million mother bats dominate the sky above, and below, the ground with a dazzling display of aerial prowess.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717110000 +0000" stop="20210717120000 +0000" catchup-id="980899338"><title>Nadiya's Party Feasts</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/35/20210710080105149mf5.jpg"></icon><desc>Nadiya Hussain is throwing a celebration - and everyone is invited. With the party season fast approaching, Nadiya shares her favourite festive dishes that fill the table with vibrant colour, amazing aromas and fantastic flavours. She is making the perfect food to hand around and share, like melt-in-the-mouth halloumi chips, smoked mackerel pate choux and sticky lamb ribs. She is also preparing a hearty dive-in dish of beef chilli and jalapeno corn bread and some vibrant salads - brussels sprout slaw and pomegranate and parsley tabbouleh. And a party wouldn't be a party without some fantastic desserts, and Nadiya's chocolate eclair roll and passion fruit bundt will keep the guests coming back for more. Nadiya also meets people around the country who have their own special reasons to rustle up a celebration. She joins a group of school children in Staffordshire as they deliver a big thank you to 95-year-old volunteer Jack, lends a hand to Gilly, who is preparing one of her spectacular homemade trifles, and helps bake an extra special cake for the surprise birthday party of twin sisters Sonia and Sunita.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717120000 +0000" stop="20210717130000 +0000" catchup-id="980899344"><title>Nature's Miracle Orphans</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/28/20210710080105149gzy.jpg"></icon><desc>In Zimbabwe, Lucy Cooke meets Moyo, a baby elephant who has been living with carer Roxy since he was just a few days old. He was found close to starvation on the banks of a river. Roxy hopes to return Moyo to the wild, but only if he can overcome his fear of water. In Costa Rica, Patrick Aryee meets Robin, an orphaned anteater who must prove to surrogate mum Pedro that he can fend for himself before he can return to the rainforest.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717130000 +0000" stop="20210717144000 +0000" catchup-id="980899350"><title>The Wedding Planner</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/88/20210710080105149wj8.jpg"></icon><desc>Romantic comedy about a hard-working and ambitious wedding planner whose highly organised life changes when she quite literally falls for her top client's fiance. When she is saved from a potential accident by a handsome young doctor, the two share a romantic evening, but it turns out that he is engaged to one of her top clients. Will he choose the wedding planner over the tycoon?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717144000 +0000" stop="20210717154000 +0000" catchup-id="980899356"><title>Land of the Tiger: Our Wild Adventures</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/78/20210710080105149xpd.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC wildlife presenters look back at their adventures across India, Bhutan and Bangladesh. Liz Bonnin remembers a remarkable morning migration by thousands of cranes to the small village of Khichan in Rajasthan. Colin Stafford-Johnson recounts his time filming tigers in India and forming a special relationship with the boisterous cub Brokentail. Chris Packham looks back on a tiger-spotting trip to Bangladesh, which lead to 'one of the worst views of an animal he'd ever had, and yet somehow the best!' Liz shares a memorable encounter in the Western Ghats, where she visited the locals trying to preserve the rare lion-tailed macaque. Finally, Steve Backshall and Gordon Buchanan recall an expedition looking for tigers in the mountains of Bhutan. Although they saw a great many animals, including a red fox, a lammergeier, bears and even a snow leopard, there was no trace of a tiger population - until, after a gruelling trek, Gordon made a sudden and dramatic discovery.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717154000 +0000" stop="20210717163000 +0000" catchup-id="980899362"><title>Flog It!</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/80/20210710080105149g7b.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Martin and his team of experts invite members of the public to bring their antiques to be viewed and valued, with an option to sell at auction.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717163000 +0000" stop="20210717170000 +0000" catchup-id="980899368"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/46/20210710080105149e96.jpg"></icon><desc>Each week a group of four famous faces go toe to toe testing their general knowledge skills in a variety of entertaining trivia-based games. Every day this week the celebrity contestants - BBC Breakfast's Naga Munchetty, singer and actor Jordan Stephens, presenter and actor Sally Lindsay and comedian David O'Doherty - take on a series of challenging quiz games selected by the host, teatime quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quick-fire round at the end of each show as the scores are tallied across the week resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much coveted House of Games dartboard, or instead go for the must-have branded dressing gown? Fun, witty, and full of surprises, Richard's cross-examination of the celebs over the course of a week provides an entertaining watch for all the family as the level of competitiveness and camaraderie grows. And of course, this warm, feel-good quiz is perfect for playing along with at home.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717170000 +0000" stop="20210717173000 +0000" catchup-id="980899374"><title>Villages by the Sea - Robin Hood's Bay</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/52/20210712180042429kwk.jpg"></icon><desc>Archaeologist Ben Robinson reveals the story of smuggling intrigue and bravery on the Yorkshire coast.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717173000 +0000" stop="20210717190000 +0000" catchup-id="980899380"><title>Dad's Army</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/76/20210710080105149cbq.jpg"></icon><desc>Feature-length version of the classic sitcom about the Home Guard unit of a small seaside town. In 1940, with a German invasion threatened, the defence of Walmington-on-Sea is in the hands of local bank manager Captain Mainwaring and a motley collection of volunteers. After a series of blunders, the Home Guard finally get the glory they deserve.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717190000 +0000" stop="20210717210000 +0000" catchup-id="980899386"><title>Golf: The Open Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/59/20210710080105149fxo.jpg"></icon><desc>Eilidh Barbour presents extended highlights from the crucial third round, with the Open being staged at Royal St George's on the Kent coastline for the first time in a decade. This time ten years ago, the third round saw eventual winner Darren Clarke consolidate his lead at the top of the standings by shooting 69 to head into Sunday five under par. With the event cancelled last year because of the coronavirus pandemic, the defending champion from 2019 is Ireland's Shane Lowry.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717210000 +0000" stop="20210717222500 +0000" catchup-id="980899392"><title>Liam Gallagher: As It Was</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210710/10/202107100801051496sp.jpg"></icon><desc>The honest and emotional story of how one of the most electrifying rock 'n' roll frontmen went from the dizzying heights of his champagne supernova years in Oasis to a life of notoriety and bitter legal battles. Starting again alone, Liam risks everything to make the greatest rock 'n' roll comeback of all time. Directors Charlie Lightening and Gavin Fitzgerald invite us backstage for a no-holds-barred look at the life of one of the most talked-about and charismatic artists of his generation.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717222500 +0000" stop="20210717232500 +0000" catchup-id="982048910"><title>Britpop at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/87/202107121800424299fa.jpg"></icon><desc>A look back though the BBC archive to the era of `Cool Britannia', when Britpop ruled the airwaves, Camden was the centre of the universe and we were all proud to be British again. Featuring performances by Suede, Sleeper, Elastica, Blur and Oasis.</desc><category>Documentaire, Muziek, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210717232500 +0000" stop="20210718012500 +0000" catchup-id="982048916"><title>McFarland, USA</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/11/20210711080045151yz9.jpg"></icon><desc>Led by Jim White, a group of Latino students with an exceptional talent for long-distance running learn about discipline and a good work ethic as they face adversity together and bid to become cross country champions.</desc><category>Film, Docudrama, Biografie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718012500 +0000" stop="20210718052000 +0000" catchup-id="982048922"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/84/20210711080045152ntr.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718052000 +0000" stop="20210718060500 +0000" catchup-id="982048928"><title>A to Z of TV Gardening</title><date>2013</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/3/20210712180042429pdc.jpg"></icon><desc>Carol Kirkwood explores gardening subjects that all begin with the letter E.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718060500 +0000" stop="20210718063500 +0000" catchup-id="982048934"><title>Britain in Bloom</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/61/20210711080045152xky.jpg"></icon><desc>Chris Bavin travels to Birmingham to meet the business owners and residents of Soho Road, a busy route into the city, who are entering Bloom under the Business Improvement District category. Soho Road is a diverse area with anti-social issues, 600 businesses along the road are working with the council to improve trade and make the area safer and greener.</desc><category>Natuur, Home &amp; Garden, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718063500 +0000" stop="20210718070500 +0000" catchup-id="982048940"><title>Life in a Cottage Garden</title><date>2013</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/88/20210711080045152tb5.jpg"></icon><desc>It is spring and changes are afoot in the garden. Carol begins the season by clearing away the last of the winter debris. All pruning needs to be done before the end of March and she celebrates the new season by sowing her first seeds. An expert hedge pruner comes to cloud-prune Carol's box hedging but work is interrupted by a nesting hedge sparrow.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718070500 +0000" stop="20210718080000 +0000" catchup-id="982048946"><title>Countryfile</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/73/20210711080045152hwk.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Baker and Margherita Taylor are in Dorset, on the stunning Isle of Purbeck, looking at the importance of its diverse landscape and the changes the coastline has gone through over the centuries. Matt goes on safari to look at the wildlife that call this habitat home, and Margherita discovers what used to live along these shores millions of years ago. We catch up with Dwayne Fields and his gallant team of explorers on the second part of their Snowdonia adventure.</desc><category>Natuur en milieu, Landbouw, Dieren, Reizen, Outdoor, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718080000 +0000" stop="20210718083000 +0000" catchup-id="982048952"><title>Weatherman Walking: The Welsh Coast</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/88/20210711080045152qrn.jpg"></icon><desc>Derek gets wet - from rain, an overturned kayak in the sea… and a hot tub with a view! Walking the Pembrokeshire coast from Newport to Fishguard, the weatherman also learns how the last invasion of Britain was foiled by a feisty woman. Archaeologist Dr Erin Lloyd-Jones explores the link between Stonehenge and the Preseli mountains and party planner Onkar Singh Purewal visits a 'Hansel and Gretel' house, covered in shells.</desc><category>Outdoor, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718083000 +0000" stop="20210718090000 +0000" catchup-id="982048958"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/81/20210711080045152z3m.jpg"></icon><desc>The competition between Brian's heritage veg and Carole's contemporary veg heats up as Carole is happily harvesting, while Brian seems to have deliberately gone to seed. Meanwhile, Calum's shows off the progress of his giant onions, giant tomatoes, giant cabbages and ridiculously long runner beans at his allotment in Leven. And Dina Watt demonstrates the technique of growing vegetables from scraps and how to use the whole vegetable so that there is never any waste.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718090000 +0000" stop="20210718103000 +0000" catchup-id="982048964"><title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/95/20210711080045152y0r.jpg"></icon><desc>A look back at some of the best segments from `Saturday Kitchen'. The popular cookery show offers recipes and ideas for mouth-watering food, interviews with great chefs and celebrity guests.</desc><category>Culinair, Bloemlezing</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718103000 +0000" stop="20210718110000 +0000" catchup-id="982048970"><title>Classic Mary Berry</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/93/202107121800424297my.jpg"></icon><desc>Mary returns to school to celebrate her light, easy and delicious cooking. From a simple version of the classic kedgeree and some delightful breakfast drop scones, to a moreish chicken, avocado and bacon salad and deliciously easy beef burgers. Mary takes her inspiration from a visit to a groundbreaking primary school in south London which has built a secret garden where they teach their students how to grow vegetables and look after a brood of chickens.</desc><category>Culinair, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718110000 +0000" stop="20210718120000 +0000" catchup-id="982048976"><title>Million Pound Menu</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/49/20210711080045152w4l.jpg"></icon><desc>Fred Sirieix welcomes an all-British fine dining concept, Epoch, and a Scottish street-food trader, ShrimpWreck, selling tempura prawn buns to Manchester. Epoch is seeking £600,000 to open its first restaurant in central London. ShrimpWreck is after £100,000 to open in Scotland.</desc><category>Business &amp; Financial, Culinair, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718120000 +0000" stop="20210718125000 +0000" catchup-id="982048982"><title>Best Dishes Ever</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/82/202107110800451525ij.jpg"></icon><desc>A selection of classic recipes from some of the BBC's best-loved television chefs.</desc><category>Culinair, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718125000 +0000" stop="20210718151500 +0000" catchup-id="982048988"><title>West Side Story</title><date>1961</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/2/20210711080045152p60.jpg"></icon><desc>Against a backdrop of vicious gang warfare between the New Yorker Jets and the Puerto Rican Sharks, a romance develops across rival lines. 1960s update of `Romeo and Juliet', with amazing song and dance sequences.</desc><category>Film, Musical</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718151500 +0000" stop="20210718161500 +0000" catchup-id="982048994"><title>West Side Stories - The Making of a Classic</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/59/20210711080045152trs.jpg"></icon><desc>Bruno Tonioli and Suzy Klein go in search of the true stories behind the inception of the `West Side Story'. They hear first-hand from those involved in the show when it opened on Broadway in September 1957, including Sondheim himself.</desc><category>Documentaire, Musical</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718161500 +0000" stop="20210718170000 +0000" catchup-id="982049000"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/96/202107110800451523j6.jpg"></icon><desc>At the Culzean Castle in Ayrshire, experts Raj Bisram and Natasha Raskin Sharp are on hand to find a selection of objects to take to auction. Raj is drawn to a charming toy car from Germany, while Natasha finds a stunning art deco Carlton Ware vase. Paul Martin meets the team of stonemasons at Culzean, including the newest apprentices, to find out how they are preserving the design of the castle's original architect, Robert Adam.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718170000 +0000" stop="20210718173000 +0000" catchup-id="982049006"><title>The Yorkshire Dales</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/25/20210711080045152k2m.jpg"></icon><desc>Explorer Paul Rose heads for Swaledale, the wildest of the Yorkshire Dales, and joins the farmers who look after rare upland hay meadows. He also visits Muker Show and enters the cake-making contest using a pressure cooker he used on Mount Everest.</desc><category>Documentaire, Samenleving, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718173000 +0000" stop="20210718180000 +0000" catchup-id="982049012"><title>Grand Tours of Scotland's Lochs</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/36/20210711080045153ukr.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul visits Wester Ross and discovers the heritage of Little Loch Broom. He then travels to the off-grid community of Scoraig where he learns about violin making and wind power, before taking the plunge to explore the hidden depths of the Corrieshalloch Gorge.</desc><category>Reizen, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718180000 +0000" stop="20210718190000 +0000" catchup-id="982049018"><title>Tropic of Cancer</title><date>2010</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/95/20210712180042430ecm.jpg"></icon><desc>Simon Reeve travels from the beautiful Pacific coast of Mexico, where he visits the luxurious holiday resorts of Baja California, before crossing the country's rugged interior. The first stage of his journey ends in the Bahamas where he discovers the hidden menace on the beautiful coral reefs.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718190000 +0000" stop="20210718210000 +0000" catchup-id="982049024"><title>Final Round Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/7/20210712180042430r85.jpg"></icon><desc>Eilidh Barbour brings you every twist and turn from the fourth and final round, with the Open being staged at Royal St George's for the first time in a decade. The return to course on the Kent coastline will bring back happy memories for Darren Clarke. This time ten years ago, Clarke sealed an emotional first - and to date only - major championship at the age of 42 with a three-shot victory. Last year's event was cancelled due to the coronavirus pandemic, meaning the defending champion is Ireland's Shane Lowry following his triumph in 2019.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718210000 +0000" stop="20210718213000 +0000" catchup-id="982049030"><title>Pride Live at the Apollo</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/77/20210711080045153tg9.jpg"></icon><desc>Featuring great stand up taken from over 14 series of LGBT+ who have appeared on the Apollo stages, including sets from Tom Allen, Stephen K Amos, Jen Brister, Al Porter, Julian Clary, Suzi Ruffell and Gina Yashere.</desc><category>Standup komedie, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718213000 +0000" stop="20210718222000 +0000" catchup-id="982049036"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210711/91/20210711080045153jx4.jpg"></icon><desc>EZ's brazen plan faces some unexpected hurdles, Coco finds a surprising sanctuary, and Emily is urged into an outing.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718222000 +0000" stop="20210718231000 +0000" catchup-id="983241060"><title>Mayans MC</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/99/20210712080037518wjj.jpg"></icon><desc>EZ agonises over the smuggling failure, but older deeds overshadow his romance with Gaby and the rocky relationships of both Angel and Bishop.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210718231000 +0000" stop="20210719000500 +0000" catchup-id="983241066"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/96/202107121800424309ei.jpg"></icon><desc>Bishop hopes an old-school stunt can salvage the plan to break ranks with rival Mayans, even as other criminal players muscle in.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719000500 +0000" stop="20210719010500 +0000" catchup-id="983241072"><title>Gold Rush: Our Race to Olympic Glory</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/72/202107121800424308sw.jpg"></icon><desc>At the Atlanta Olympics in 1996, Britain finished at an all-time low of 36th in the medal table. After this disappointment, a renaissance began with the aim of rebuilding the nation's sporting prowess. Kickstarted by Conservative prime minister John Major, the project flushed Britain's sporting system with millions of pounds from the new National Lottery. Athletes would give up their day jobs and be paid to become full-time sportsmen and women.</desc><category>Sport, Documentaire, Miniseries</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719010500 +0000" stop="20210719014500 +0000" catchup-id="983241078"><title>Holby City</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/56/20210712080037519gjk.jpg"></icon><desc>Dom's mum Carole is admitted with a burnt arm, but might be hiding a more serious ailment. Kylie blurts out Ange's secret to Josh, and Max tries to rally the troops after the disastrous CQC findings. To add to her woes, Sahira's son turns up drunk, wounded and hiding a dark secret.</desc><category>Dramaseries, Medisch</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719014500 +0000" stop="20210719050000 +0000" catchup-id="983241084"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/61/20210712080037519vk8.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719050000 +0000" stop="20210719054500 +0000" catchup-id="983241090"><title>Murder, Mystery &amp; My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/57/20210712080037519rk8.jpg"></icon><desc>Leading barristers Jeremy Dein and Sasha Wass look back at their investigation into whether a young mother accused of poisoning her family in 1850 was hanged as a result of hearsay and gossip. In the mid-19th century, a poison panic gripped Victorian Britain when a slew of murders, many perpetrated by women, caused national hysteria. Their weapon of choice was an easily available powdered poison called arsenic.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719054500 +0000" stop="20210719063000 +0000" catchup-id="983241096"><title>Bargain Hunt: Animals Special</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/88/20210712180042430vvv.jpg"></icon><desc>Eric Knowles takes a look back at some of the most interesting animal-related items bought by the red and blue teams. It can be a jungle out there, so Eric offers advice on how to spot a bargain. He also heads to Peterborough to discover an extraordinary collection of horseshoes.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719063000 +0000" stop="20210719073000 +0000" catchup-id="983241102"><title>Eat Well for Less?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/42/20210712080037519u58.jpg"></icon><desc>Gregg and Chris head to Cardiff to meet Steph and Matt, parents to seven-year-old William and four-year-old Alex, with another baby on the way. Matt and Steph are stuck in a food rut due to William's serious food allergies. Following an anaphylactic reaction at the age of three, William cannot eat certain foods, including nuts, sesame seeds and flax seeds. As a result, the family are brand-loyal to particular products that they know William can safely eat.</desc><category>Culinair, Doe-het-zelf, Gezondheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719073000 +0000" stop="20210719080000 +0000" catchup-id="983241108"><title>The Week in Parliament</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/93/20210712080037519515.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC Parliament's programme looking back at the week in Westminster, presented by David Cornock.</desc><category>Politiek, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719080000 +0000" stop="20210719090000 +0000" catchup-id="983241114"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/63/202107120800375194bg.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719090000 +0000" stop="20210719111500 +0000" catchup-id="983241120"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/12/20210712080037519dc0.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719111500 +0000" stop="20210719120000 +0000" catchup-id="983241126"><title>Politics Live</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/92/202107120800375192h4.jpg"></icon><desc>Jo Coburn and panel discuss the big issues of the day.</desc><category>Politiek, Talkshow, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719120000 +0000" stop="20210719123000 +0000" catchup-id="983241132"><title>Letterbox</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/10/20210712080037519ctn.jpg"></icon><desc>Hosted by Mel Giedroyc, pairs of contestants go head-to-head to crack a series of passwords, in an attempt to take home £2,500 in cash.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719123000 +0000" stop="20210719133000 +0000" catchup-id="983241138"><title>Ice Station Antarctica</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/19/20210712180042430x08.jpg"></icon><desc>Antarctica is the last great wilderness. It's the coldest, windiest, driest and most isolated place on Earth. And every winter, for over three months of the year, the sun never rises. But it's also home to the British Antarctic Survey's Halley Research Station. A veteran of living and working at Halley in the early eighties, BBC weatherman Peter Gibbs makes an emotional return to the place he once called home. A place that, during his time, was key to the discovery of the ozone hole. The journey starts with an arduous 12-day, 3000-mile voyage onboard the RRS Ernest Shackleton. Once on the ice shelf, Peter is delighted to finally arrive at the futuristic research station and marvels at the cutting edge science being done at Halley today. From vital discoveries about how our lives are vulnerable to the sun's activities, to studying interplanetary travel and the threat of man-made climate change. But Peter's journey is also something of a rescue mission. The research station's home is a floating ice shelf that constantly moves and cracks, and the ice shelf has developed a chasm that could cast Halley adrift on a massive iceberg.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719133000 +0000" stop="20210719151500 +0000" catchup-id="983241144"><title>Scott of the Antarctic</title><date>1948</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/46/202107121800424309j6.jpg"></icon><desc>A faithful representation of the doomed Antarctic expedition of 1911-12 led by Captain Robert Falcon Scott. After much misfortune, the five-man team makes it to the South Pole through almost superhuman effort - only to find that the Norwegian flag is already flying. They then set out on the perilous return journey, but more disasters befall them.</desc><category>Film, Historisch drama</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719151500 +0000" stop="20210719161500 +0000" catchup-id="984534812"><title>Gorilla Family and Me</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/36/20210713080052464foy.jpg"></icon><desc>Gordon Buchanan returns to the Democratic Republic of Congo to discover the fate of his gorilla family. When he left, Chimanuka the silverback was being challenged by a rival. At stake were the lives of two of his children, Marhale the orphan and the baby Mwira. Having reconnected with his family, Gordon discovers they face a new threat - poachers in the forest. Can Gordon and the rangers help secure the future of our gorilla family?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719161500 +0000" stop="20210719170000 +0000" catchup-id="983241220"><title>Flog It!</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/23/20210712080037519ho4.jpg"></icon><desc>Today Flog It! comes from the Blickling estate in north Norfolk. Five antiques experts are on hand to find a selection of objects to take to auction. David Harper is excited by a Rolex oyster watch, and Paul Martin learns more about Lord Lothian, who inherited Blickling in 1930 and played a key role in getting America involved in the Second World War.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719170000 +0000" stop="20210719173000 +0000" catchup-id="983241226"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/38/20210712080037519hiv.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Ellie Taylor, actor and writer Steve Pemberton, presenter Fern Britton and comedian Josh Widdicombe test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719173000 +0000" stop="20210719180000 +0000" catchup-id="983241232"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/11/20210712080037519l2o.jpg"></icon><desc>The park's keepers have high hopes for their southern koala breeding programme as new boy Burke is showing signs of wanting to mate. Bellowing and spraying his scent everywhere is the rather unsubtle way he tries to attract the female koalas. Kate witnesses an Animal Park first as the secretive spotted hyenas are captured on camera. She takes part in a covert operation to outwit these wily creatures in order to have their enclosure managed.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719180000 +0000" stop="20210719190000 +0000" catchup-id="983241238"><title>Gold Town</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/5/20210712080037519ijt.jpg"></icon><desc>It's November 2019, and the delays in building the processing plant for the mine continue. Shifting 185,000 tons of mountain terrain to level the ground should have taken six weeks, but it has been three months, and they are nowhere near finished.</desc><category>Miniseries, Documentaire, Samenleving</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719190000 +0000" stop="20210719193000 +0000" catchup-id="983241244"><title>Only Connect</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/18/2021071208003751900s.jpg"></icon><desc>A team of gaming enthusiasts take on three animal lovers in this opening heat. They compete to complete this sequence: bow, pathy, tropy.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719193000 +0000" stop="20210719200000 +0000" catchup-id="983241250"><title>University Challenge</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/14/20210712080037519ll2.jpg"></icon><desc>In another first round match, students from University College London do battle with St Hilda's College, Oxford in a bid to reach the second round in the quiz for students. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719200000 +0000" stop="20210719213000 +0000" catchup-id="983241256"><title>Killing Escobar</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/8/20210712180042430ffx.jpg"></icon><desc>The incredible true story of Scottish mercenary Peter McAleese, who was hired to kill Colombian drug lord Pablo Escobar in 1989. With unprecedented access to Peter and other members of his team, this is the first full account of that fateful mission.</desc><category>Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719213000 +0000" stop="20210719221000 +0000" catchup-id="983241262"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210712/90/2021071208003751997b.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Mark Urban.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719221000 +0000" stop="20210719221500 +0000" catchup-id="984534818"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/72/20210713080052464k4e.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719221500 +0000" stop="20210719231500 +0000" catchup-id="984534824"><title>Reggie in China</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/73/20210713080052464rm1.jpg"></icon><desc>Reggie visits Shanghai, China's largest city, and Chengdu, capital of Sichuan province, to explore the fault line between modern day Chinese culture, and strict censorship rules imposed by the government that are subject to change at a moment's notice.</desc><category>Miniseries, Reizen, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210719231500 +0000" stop="20210720001500 +0000" catchup-id="984534830"><title>Countryfile</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/4/20210713080052464s09.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Baker and Margherita Taylor are in Dorset, on the stunning Isle of Purbeck, looking at the importance of its diverse landscape and the changes the coastline has gone through over the centuries. Matt goes on safari to look at the wildlife that call this habitat home, and Margherita discovers what used to live along these shores millions of years ago. We catch up with Dwayne Fields and his gallant team of explorers on the second part of their Snowdonia adventure.</desc><category>Natuur en milieu, Landbouw, Dieren, Reizen, Outdoor, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720001500 +0000" stop="20210720010000 +0000" catchup-id="984534836"><title>The Sheriffs Are Coming</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/74/20210713080052464ckm.jpg"></icon><desc>Sheriffs are tasked with removing squatters from a shop in north London. James and Mark are in Birmingham hoping to take away money owed by a kebab shop, and the sheriffs visit a garage that damaged the wheels of a customer's pride and joy.</desc><category>Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720010000 +0000" stop="20210720014500 +0000" catchup-id="984534842"><title>Frontline Fightback</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/32/20210713080052464ldv.jpg"></icon><desc>A 96-year-old D-Day veteran is brutally attacked on his doorstep. Incredibly, he survives, and police in Taunton, Somerset, quickly arrest his attacker after tracking his spending habits and lying in wait at a McDonalds restaurant. Online banking fraud is one of the UK's fastest growing crimes, but the latest voice recognition software is helping banks identify fraudsters and prevent them stealing our money.</desc><category>Miniseries, Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720014500 +0000" stop="20210720053000 +0000" catchup-id="984534848"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/31/20210713080052464yg1.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720053000 +0000" stop="20210720061500 +0000" catchup-id="984535430"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/71/20210713080052464gd6.jpg"></icon><desc>Leading criminal barristers Sasha Wass QC and Jeremy Dein QC revisit their investigation of an infamous Victorian poisoning case, where a wife was convicted of the murder of her husband. Liverpool, 1889. On 11 May, cotton broker James Maybrick passed away after a two-week battle with illness. A post-mortem revealed his body contained traces of the deadly poison arsenic. Suspicion soon fell on his wife, Florence Maybrick, after servants saw her handing some poisons.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720061500 +0000" stop="20210720070000 +0000" catchup-id="984535436"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/71/20210713080052464wqy.jpg"></icon><desc>Charlie Ross and experts Thomas Forrester and Stephanie Connell go antique-hunting in Brackley, Northamptonshire, before heading to Stratford-upon-Avon for today's auction. Charlie seeks illumination about the life of Victorian designer Charles Kempe, famous for his stained glass.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720070000 +0000" stop="20210720080000 +0000" catchup-id="984535442"><title>Gardeners' World</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/9/202107130800524648pq.jpg"></icon><desc>Monty catches up with all his summer jobs in the border and the vegetable garden. Carol gets inspiration for planting combinations at Cothay Manor and Gardens, and Arit learns about slugs and snails.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720080000 +0000" stop="20210720090000 +0000" catchup-id="984535448"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/77/202107130800524651sl.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720090000 +0000" stop="20210720111500 +0000" catchup-id="984535454"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/15/202107130800524652kw.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720111500 +0000" stop="20210720120000 +0000" catchup-id="984535460"><title>Politics Live</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/70/2021071308005246571e.jpg"></icon><desc>Jo Coburn is live in Westminster with Conservative MP Conor Burns, Labour MP Rosie Duffield, LBC presenter Iain Dale and Polly Mackenzie, Chief Executive of the cross party think tank Demos to discuss plans to make Covid vaccine passports mandatory at nightclubs, whether there should be a tax rise to fund social care and Laura Kuenssberg's interview with Dominic Cummings, former adviser to Boris Johnson.</desc><category>Politiek, Talkshow, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720120000 +0000" stop="20210720123000 +0000" catchup-id="984535466"><title>Letterbox</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/4/20210713080052465dtz.jpg"></icon><desc>Hosted by Mel Giedroyc, pairs of contestants go head-to-head to crack a series of passwords, in an attempt to take home £2,500 in cash.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720123000 +0000" stop="20210720131500 +0000" catchup-id="984535472"><title>Make Me a Dealer</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/96/20210713080052465x10.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul is in East Anglia with brothers Tony and John Wakefield competing against each other.</desc><category>Doe-het-zelf, Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720131500 +0000" stop="20210720135000 +0000" catchup-id="984535478"><title>Great British Comedies: Talking Pictures</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/30/20210713080052465f55.jpg"></icon><desc>Sylvia Syms looks back on the careers of some of the greatest British comedy stars. Featuring George Formby, the classic Ealing comedies, the Doctor series and the ground-breaking movies of Monty Python.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720135000 +0000" stop="20210720151500 +0000" catchup-id="984535484"><title>The Man in the White Suit</title><date>1951</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/73/20210713080052465k2q.jpg"></icon><desc>An eccentric research scientist working a menial job in a textile factory invents a fabric that never gets dirty and never wears out. When the tycoons of the clothes industry discover his secret, they ruthlessly set out to destroy the formula and the scientist is forced to go on the run, wearing a suit made from the miracle yarn, with just about everyone in pursuit.</desc><category>Film, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720151500 +0000" stop="20210720161500 +0000" catchup-id="993141999"><title>Gorilla Family and Me</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/52/20210720080040150knr.jpg"></icon><desc>Gordon Buchanan returns to the Democratic Republic of Congo to discover the fate of his gorilla family. When he left, Chimanuka the silverback was being challenged by a rival. At stake were the lives of two of his children, Marhale the orphan and the baby Mwira. Having reconnected with his family, Gordon discovers they face a new threat - poachers in the forest.</desc><category>Documentaire, Dieren, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720161500 +0000" stop="20210720170000 +0000" catchup-id="984535496"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/45/2021071308005246521f.jpg"></icon><desc>The show comes from Oxburgh Hall in Norfolk. David Harper is excited by a Polynesian war club, while Philip Serrell falls for a sewing machine. Paul Martin uncovers the history of the Bedingfeld family, who have called Oxburgh home for 500 years.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720170000 +0000" stop="20210720173000 +0000" catchup-id="984535502"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/35/2021071308005246598f.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Ellie Taylor, actor and writer Steve Pemberton, presenter Fern Britton and comedian Josh Widdicombe test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720173000 +0000" stop="20210720180000 +0000" catchup-id="984535508"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/56/20210713080052466qan.jpg"></icon><desc>Silverback Kesho is having his authority tested by a younger gorilla who seems to want to be leader of the pack. The bolshie behaviour is threatening the cohesion of the whole gorilla group, as Kate finds out. Ben meets one of the park's newest arrivals, an endangered pancake tortoise. With three other eggs in the incubator, the keepers are keeping their fingers crossed there will be more soon. Why would you hide a cod liver oil capsule inside a dead mouse?</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720180000 +0000" stop="20210720190000 +0000" catchup-id="993142005"><title>Dominic Cummings - The Interview</title><date></date><icon src=""></icon><desc>Laura Kuenssberg interviews Dominic Cummings about his role in government during the pandemic, his relationship with the Prime Minister, and his role in Brexit.</desc><category>Interview, Politiek</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720190000 +0000" stop="20210720200000 +0000" catchup-id="984535520"><title>Secrets of the Museum</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/47/20210713080052466nd5.jpg"></icon><desc>The museum conservators work to preserve and maintain four unique objects. Theatre and Performance keeper Geoff and conservator Jo work to repair an eye-popping red lurex suit that belongs to Jim Lea.</desc><category>Beeldende kunst, Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720200000 +0000" stop="20210720210000 +0000" catchup-id="984535526"><title>Forensics: The Real CSI</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/56/20210713080052466v00.jpg"></icon><desc>As the victim of a violent knife attack fights for his life in hospital, Crime Scene Coordinator Jo Ward is dispatched to his home in Birmingham to lead the forensic investigation into identifying his attacker. The victim is unable to tell police what happened because he has been put in a medically induced coma, and the investigation becomes more challenging when no witnesses are prepared to give a statement to the police.</desc><category>Misdaad, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720210000 +0000" stop="20210720213000 +0000" catchup-id="984535532"><title>Cunk on Britain</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/77/20210713080052466s4x.jpg"></icon><desc>Philomena is examining the Victorians and is joined by Chris Packham who tries to shed some light on Darwin's discoveries.</desc><category>Documentaire, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720213000 +0000" stop="20210720221000 +0000" catchup-id="984535538"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210713/48/20210713080052466fbg.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Emily Maitlis.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720221000 +0000" stop="20210720221500 +0000" catchup-id="985785137"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/90/20210714080037432417.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720221500 +0000" stop="20210720231500 +0000" catchup-id="985785143"><title>Cricket: England v Pakistan T20 Highlights</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/2/20210714080037432ztc.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of the third T20 international between England and Pakistan.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210720231500 +0000" stop="20210721001500 +0000" catchup-id="985785149"><title>RHS Hampton Court Palace Garden Festival</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/10/2021071408003743308a.jpg"></icon><desc>Coverage of the annual RHS Hampton Court flower show.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Event</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721001500 +0000" stop="20210721010000 +0000" catchup-id="985785475"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/85/202107140800374332u6.jpg"></icon><desc>Top criminal barristers Jeremy Dein QC and Sasha Wass QC reinvestigate a complex case from Victorian Britain that featured four prime suspects, two trials and ultimately just one man hanged for the murder of his neighbour. Norfolk, 1882. During the early hours of 19 November, in the narrow rows of Great Yarmouth, police on the beat noticed the door of one of the street's shops ajar. They searched the property and made a shocking discovery.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721010000 +0000" stop="20210721014500 +0000" catchup-id="985785481"><title>Frontline Fightback</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/56/202107140800374334nw.jpg"></icon><desc>An elderly woman has her handbag snatched on her way to bingo, but the robber doesn't get far. Police follow a digital trail of evidence and put him behind bars.</desc><category>Miniseries, Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721014500 +0000" stop="20210721053000 +0000" catchup-id="985785487"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/26/20210714080037433s7k.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721053000 +0000" stop="20210721061500 +0000" catchup-id="985785493"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/92/20210714080037433a6a.jpg"></icon><desc>Leading criminal barristers Sasha Wass and Jeremy Dein revisit the troubling case of a care home nurse convicted of poisoning a patient, a crime for which she would hang. Nottingham, 1935. Ada Baguley, a 55-year-old resident of a family-run nursing home, passed away. Initially Ada was thought to have died from natural causes, but a post-mortem revealed her body to contain lethal doses of morphine.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721061500 +0000" stop="20210721064500 +0000" catchup-id="985785499"><title>Great British Railway Journeys</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/51/20210714080037433kzl.jpg"></icon><desc>Starting in Hassocks, Michael makes his way to the beautiful Sussex village of Ditchling, where, between the wars, a Roman Catholic community of artists made their home. Michael finds out how they made their mark on the village, the capital and the nation's railways. In the seaside town of Bexhill-on-Sea, Michael hears of the work of the wartime air raid precautions wardens, immortalised in the BBC series `Dad's Army'.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721064500 +0000" stop="20210721071500 +0000" catchup-id="985785505"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/82/20210714080037433mcw.jpg"></icon><desc>Carole and Mairi take a look at the progress of the beds of wildflower seeds and turf that they sowed and laid eight weeks ago. Kirsty is also at Beechgrove, where she, Carole and Mairi enjoy a masterclass on the Japanese art of Kokedama.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721071500 +0000" stop="20210721094500 +0000" catchup-id="985785511"><title>Olympics 2020 Women's Football: Team GB v Chile</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/92/20210714080037433gge.jpg"></icon><desc>Alex Scott presents live coverage as we get our first sight of Team GB's athletes at the Tokyo Olympics, with the women's footballers taking centre stage. The women's football tournament gets going ahead of the opening ceremony of the 32nd summer Olympic Games, which takes place on Friday in Japan's capital. The Chile clash is the first of three for Team GB's women, who also face hosts Japan on 24 July before taking on Canada three days later. Team GB reached the quarter-finals in their only other Games experience at London 2012 - can they hit the ground running in Sapporo?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721094500 +0000" stop="20210721101500 +0000" catchup-id="985785517"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/54/20210714080037433lys.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721101500 +0000" stop="20210721120000 +0000" catchup-id="989457046"><title>Politics Live (Later)</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/77/20210717080030150utl.jpg"></icon><desc>Jo Coburn and panel discuss the big issues of the day.</desc><category>Politiek, Talkshow, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721120000 +0000" stop="20210721123000 +0000" catchup-id="985785529"><title>Letterbox</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/61/20210714080037433clk.jpg"></icon><desc>Hosted by Mel Giedroyc, pairs of contestants go head-to-head to crack a series of passwords, in an attempt to take home £2,500 in cash.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721123000 +0000" stop="20210721131500 +0000" catchup-id="985785535"><title>Make Me a Dealer</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/28/20210714080037433k04.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Martin presents with Alex White from Essex up against Kati Walsh from London.</desc><category>Doe-het-zelf, Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721131500 +0000" stop="20210721134500 +0000" catchup-id="985785541"><title>Reel History of Britain</title><date>2011</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/37/20210714080037433z53.jpg"></icon><desc>Melvyn Bragg is at the Francis Combe Academy in Watford to look back to the 1960s and a time when passing or failing an exam, the eleven-plus, could map out a child's future. Former Francis Combe pupil Bernie Batchelor will come face-to-face with his mischievous 12-year-old former self and former TV presenter, Marylyn Mason tells us how her failure of the eleven-plus drove her to work harder in later life.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721134500 +0000" stop="20210721151500 +0000" catchup-id="985785547"><title>School for Scoundrels</title><date>1960</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/97/20210714080037433q6r.jpg"></icon><desc>Kind-hearted but weak-willed Henry Palfrey is cheated and abused by car salesmen, a head waiter, an upper-class cad and his employees. When charming April Smith is stolen away from him, Henry takes drastic action and enrols in the College of Lifemanship, run by Mr Potter, where he can learn to beat others in life.</desc><category>Film, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721151500 +0000" stop="20210721161500 +0000" catchup-id="993142011"><title>Nature's Wildest Weapons: Horns, Tusks and Antlers</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/61/20210720080040150b9d.jpg"></icon><desc>The animal kingdom possesses a fearsome arsenal - a variety of extreme weapons used in epic battles to gore, stab, crush and batter. But are they more than just instruments of deadly force? For Professor Doug Emlen, it has been his lifetime's ambition to discover the secrets of nature's arms races, what triggers them and what they can teach us about the most formidable weapons on earth - our own.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721161500 +0000" stop="20210721170000 +0000" catchup-id="985785559"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/15/20210714080037433j12.jpg"></icon><desc>The show comes from the Blickling Estate in north Norfolk. David Harper is excited by an early device for watching films, whilst David Fletcher and James Lewis reminisce about Rupert the Bear books and Dinky toys.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721170000 +0000" stop="20210721203000 +0000" catchup-id="985785565"><title>The Hundred: Oval Invincibles v Manchester Originals</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/96/20210714080037433x20.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage as the much-anticipated women's Hundred competition kicks off with the first of a fascinating double-header over two nights at the Kia Oval. The inaugural season of the new 100-ball month-long competition was delayed from the summer of 2020 by the coronavirus pandemic. The action begins with a women's clash between the Invincibles and the Originals, before the corresponding men's sides face off on Thursday evening. The finals will take place at Lord's on Saturday, 21 August - can these sides hit the ground running in south London tonight?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721203000 +0000" stop="20210721213000 +0000" catchup-id="985785571"><title>Inside the Factory</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/13/20210714080037433209.jpg"></icon><desc>Gregg Wallace is in Essex at an enormous cereal bar factory, which produces 400,000 fruit- and nut-packed treats a day. Gregg follows production from the arrival of two tonnes of macadamia nuts all the way through to dispatch.</desc><category>Documentaire, Consumentenprogramma's</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721213000 +0000" stop="20210721221000 +0000" catchup-id="985785577"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210714/70/20210714080037434ywe.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Emily Maitlis.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721221000 +0000" stop="20210721221500 +0000" catchup-id="987002114"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/80/20210715080032460bu7.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210721221500 +0000" stop="20210722000500 +0000" catchup-id="987002120"><title>Memento</title><date>2000</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/39/20210715080032460xtd.jpg"></icon><desc>A man struggles to piece his life back together after the brutal murder of his wife, but hindered by his loss of short-term memory, the result of the beating he received at the hands of his wife's killer.</desc><category>Film, Thriller, Mysterie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722000500 +0000" stop="20210722010500 +0000" catchup-id="987002126"><title>RHS Hampton Court Palace Garden Festival</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/21/20210715080032460f21.jpg"></icon><desc>Coverage of the annual RHS Hampton Court flower show.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Event</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722010500 +0000" stop="20210722020500 +0000" catchup-id="987002132"><title>Forensics: The Real CSI</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/41/20210715080032460i3z.jpg"></icon><desc>Police respond to a call from a residential area of Dudley, where a woman reports that a house is being smashed up and a group are beating someone up outside it. When the forensic team from West Midlands Police arrive shortly afterwards, the attackers have fled. They find the body of a young man and a complex crime scene with evidence that a series of violent incidents have taken place over several hundred yards.</desc><category>Misdaad, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722020500 +0000" stop="20210722030500 +0000" catchup-id="987002138"><title>Africa: our Wild Adventures</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/20/20210715080032460k1u.jpg"></icon><desc>Presenters share memories of their wild adventures across Africa. Gordon Buchanan reminisces about his career beginnings in Africa, when he was only seventeen. Camerawoman Sue Gibson remembers the time she spent filming a baby elephant called Safina.</desc><category>Natuur, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722030500 +0000" stop="20210722035000 +0000" catchup-id="987002144"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/59/2021071508003246074b.jpg"></icon><desc>Sasha Wass QC and Jeremy Dein QC investigate a murder case from rural Lincolnshire in which a wife was accused of murdering her husband with arsenic. Wrangle, Lincolnshire, 1884. On a winter's afternoon, cottager William Lefley arrived at his local doctor's surgery in agonising pain. He had just eaten a rice pudding prepared by his wife Mary, and made the dramatic accusation that she had poisoned him.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722035000 +0000" stop="20210722053000 +0000" catchup-id="987002150"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/65/202107150800324605mq.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722053000 +0000" stop="20210722061500 +0000" catchup-id="987002156"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/62/202107150800324614nj.jpg"></icon><desc>Top criminal barristers Sasha Wass QC and Jeremy Dein QC revisit their investigation into an infamous case of a housewife accused of murdering her young husband. She became the last woman to be publicly hanged in Dorset, and her story inspired a classic novel. Dorset, 1856. In the early hours of 6 July, Martha Brown, a resident of Birdsmoorgate in rural Dorset, called on her neighbour begging for help.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722061500 +0000" stop="20210722070000 +0000" catchup-id="987002162"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/80/20210715080032461t4v.jpg"></icon><desc>Eric Knowles presents from an antiques centre in Cheshire, with some changes to the rules: with the help of Ben Cooper and Richard Madley, one of the items bought by each team must cost at least £75 and they must also buy an item of Eric's choosing.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722070000 +0000" stop="20210722080000 +0000" catchup-id="987002168"><title>The Frozen North: Our Wild Adventures</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/60/20210715080032461ktk.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC Wildlife presenters look back on their adventures in the frozen regions of the Arctic. With brutal weather and often treacherous landscapes, survival here is a tough ask. Liz Bonnin recalls a memorable adventure in in Ussuriysk.</desc><category>Natuur, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722080000 +0000" stop="20210722090000 +0000" catchup-id="987002174"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/51/202107150800324612ob.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722090000 +0000" stop="20210722111500 +0000" catchup-id="987002436"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/96/20210715080032461c0i.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722111500 +0000" stop="20210722120000 +0000" catchup-id="987002442"><title>Politics Live</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/39/20210715080032461jxp.jpg"></icon><desc>Jo Coburn and panel discuss the big issues of the day.</desc><category>Politiek, Talkshow, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722120000 +0000" stop="20210722123000 +0000" catchup-id="987002448"><title>Letterbox</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/95/20210715080032461ur7.jpg"></icon><desc>Hosted by Mel Giedroyc, pairs of contestants go head-to-head to crack a series of passwords, in an attempt to take home £2,500 in cash.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722123000 +0000" stop="20210722130000 +0000" catchup-id="987002454"><title>Sir Chris Hoy's Secret World of Japanese Bicycle Racing</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/4/20210715080032461jim.jpg"></icon><desc>Olympic icon Sir Chris Hoy heads to Japan, host of the 2021 Tokyo Games, to explore the phenomenon of the keirin, the most extreme and exciting event in track cycling. A test of controlled pacing then a tactical fight to the line, keirin is a sport in its own right in its country of origin and is steeped in the history and rituals that make Japanese culture so unique.</desc><category>Sport, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722130000 +0000" stop="20210722161500 +0000" catchup-id="987002460"><title>Britain's Greatest Olympic Moments</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/90/20210715080032461osd.jpg"></icon><desc>Clare Balding and Gabby Logan take a deep dive into the BBC Sport archive, looking back at some of the most memorable moments from Britain's most-loved sports stars. Spanning many decades, this bumper show counts down the top 25 moments from Britain's Summer Olympics history and in doing so reminds us of the many glorious gold medals Britain has won over the years. The show is full of inspiration and emotion, with highlights including legendary moments from London 2012, Tokyo 1964, Los Angeles 1984, Barcelona 1992, Sydney 2000 and Rio 2016. Please tell us what your greatest British Olympic moment is by using #bbcolympics.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722161500 +0000" stop="20210722170000 +0000" catchup-id="987002466"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/36/20210715080032461mge.jpg"></icon><desc>The show comes from Oxburgh Hall in Norfolk. Six antiques experts are on hand to find a selection of objects to take to auction. Anita Manning discovers a Victorian dynamometer used for measuring the pressure of steam.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722170000 +0000" stop="20210722203000 +0000" catchup-id="987002472"><title>The Hundred: Oval Invincibles v Manchester Originals</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/79/20210715080032461fdq.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage as the much-anticipated men's Hundred competition kicks off with the second of a fascinating double-header over two nights at the Kia Oval. The inaugural season of the new 100-ball month-long competition was delayed from the summer of 2020 by the coronavirus pandemic. Wednesday saw the corresponding sides meet as the women's tournament got started in south London. Can the likes of star man Jos Buttler help the Originals to see off the Invincibles as they bid to end the campaign in the Lord's-hosted final on Saturday 21 August?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722203000 +0000" stop="20210722213000 +0000" catchup-id="987002478"><title>Heist: The Northern Bank Robbery</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/28/20210715080032461f9f.jpg"></icon><desc>Two of Northern Ireland's leading journalists, Darragh MacIntyre and Sam McBride, shed new light on one of the most notorious crimes in UK-Irish history - the Northern Bank robbery.</desc><category>Misdaad, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722213000 +0000" stop="20210722221000 +0000" catchup-id="987002484"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210715/23/20210715080032461lvp.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Katie Razzall.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722221000 +0000" stop="20210722221500 +0000" catchup-id="988315043"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/61/20210716080057435vb4.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722221500 +0000" stop="20210722231500 +0000" catchup-id="988315049"><title>Forensics: The Real CSI</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/9/202107160800574352kj.jpg"></icon><desc>As the victim of a violent knife attack fights for his life in hospital, Crime Scene Coordinator Jo Ward is dispatched to his home in Birmingham to lead the forensic investigation into identifying his attacker. The victim is unable to tell police what happened because he has been put in a medically induced coma, and the investigation becomes more challenging when no witnesses are prepared to give a statement to the police.</desc><category>Misdaad, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210722231500 +0000" stop="20210723001500 +0000" catchup-id="988315055"><title>RHS Hampton Court Palace Garden Festival</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/63/20210716080057435klo.jpg"></icon><desc>Coverage of the annual RHS Hampton Court flower show.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Event</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723001500 +0000" stop="20210723010000 +0000" catchup-id="988315061"><title>The Sheriffs Are Coming</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/24/202107160800574357tb.jpg"></icon><desc>Luke and Carl visit a north London bar in search of money owed to a company who repaired their equipment but didn't get paid for the work. At a car lot, James and Mark meet a tricky debtor who makes extraordinary demands, and Ben and Myles go in search of money owed by a cleaning company to a former employee.</desc><category>Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723010000 +0000" stop="20210723014500 +0000" catchup-id="988315067"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/10/20210716080057435y3v.jpg"></icon><desc>Leading criminal barristers Jeremy Dein QC and Sasha Wass QC reinvestigate a case of matricide dating from the 1920s, in which a renowned fraudster went to the gallows accused of murdering his mother. Kent, 1929. On the evening of 23 October, in the coastal town of Margate, a distraught guest of the Hotel Metropole stormed downstairs into the lobby. That guest was Sydney Fox. He screamed that his mother's room was on fire, and begged for help.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723014500 +0000" stop="20210723054500 +0000" catchup-id="988315073"><title>This is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/71/20210716080057435rdt.jpg"></icon><desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc><category>Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723054500 +0000" stop="20210723063000 +0000" catchup-id="988315079"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/24/20210716080057435imf.jpg"></icon><desc>Top criminal barristers Jeremy Dein QC and Sasha Wass QC revisit the complex case against a Victorian auctioneer accused alongside his brother and two others of murdering his wife. Penge, 1877. On 12 April a desperately frail woman was taken on an arduous journey from rural Kent to Penge on the outskirts of south east London. That woman was 36-year-old wealthy heiress Harriett Staunton. Moaning and barely conscious, she had to be carried the final stretch to her lodging house.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723063000 +0000" stop="20210723070000 +0000" catchup-id="988315085"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/49/20210716080057435rko.jpg"></icon><desc>The competition between Brian's heritage veg and Carole's contemporary veg heats up as Carole is happily harvesting, while Brian seems to have deliberately gone to seed. Meanwhile, Calum's shows off the progress of his giant onions, giant tomatoes, giant cabbages and ridiculously long runner beans at his allotment in Leven. And Dina Watt demonstrates the technique of growing vegetables from scraps and how to use the whole vegetable so that there is never any waste.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723070000 +0000" stop="20210723080000 +0000" catchup-id="988315091"><title>The Great Northern Garden Build</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/54/20210716080057435h2w.jpg"></icon><desc>The team at RHS Bridgewater are responsible for creating one of the most ambitious and challenging garden projects the UK has ever seen. With unique access, go behind the scenes and meet the top team of designers, engineers and gardeners all tasked with taking on this colossal project on the site of a former grand Victorian estate in Greater Manchester.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723080000 +0000" stop="20210723090000 +0000" catchup-id="988315097"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/46/20210716080057435xxx.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723090000 +0000" stop="20210723100000 +0000" catchup-id="988315103"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/36/20210716080057435sx9.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723100000 +0000" stop="20210723104500 +0000" catchup-id="989457052"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/60/20210717080030150abk.jpg"></icon><desc>Butterknowle, County Durham, 1884. On a dark and rainy Saturday night, following a pigeon-shooting competition, Police Sergeant William Smith was out on his rounds at pub closing time. Suddenly, a group of three men emerged from the darkness and brutally attacked him.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723104500 +0000" stop="20210723111500 +0000" catchup-id="988315109"><title>Island Medics</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/27/20210716080057435mc8.jpg"></icon><desc>A 95 year old navy veteran is winched from the deck of a cruise ship, having lain undiscovered in his cabin for 11 hours. He's diabetic, dehydrated and has suspected acute pancreatitis.</desc><category>Documentaire, Gezondheid, Medisch</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723111500 +0000" stop="20210723115500 +0000" catchup-id="988315115"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/29/20210716080057435abf.jpg"></icon><desc>Natasha Raskin Sharp oversees the hunt for bargains in Peterborough. A team of brothers-in-law take on a team of friends and compete to buy three items that will make the most profit at auction.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723115500 +0000" stop="20210723122500 +0000" catchup-id="989457058"><title>Garden Rescue: Top of the Plots</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/31/20210717080030150j70.jpg"></icon><desc>Charlie Dimmock and the Rich brothers, David and Harry, fondly look back at some of their favourite water gardens, the ones transformed with centrepiece water features. There's a stunning Japanese inspired pond with a teahouse, a contemporary stepping stone water feature ready for a wedding reception, and the ultimate wildlife pond, complete with a lush meadow garden. Charlie and the boys have also got plenty of new top tips, including the best exotic plants for your pond.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Bouwen en verbouwen, Reality</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723122500 +0000" stop="20210723132500 +0000" catchup-id="988315133"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/90/202107160800574353gr.jpg"></icon><desc>Interior designer Sarah Moore meets people up and down the UK who are throwing out what they consider to be worthless goods. She takes three of these worn-out items and transforms them beyond recognition, which in turn gives them a higher value.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723132500 +0000" stop="20210723141000 +0000" catchup-id="989457064"><title>My Unique B&amp;B</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/63/20210717080030150ows.jpg"></icon><desc>In the Cotswolds, unique spaces expert Simon Parfett and his team meet Tammy and Colin. Wanting to spend more time together as a family and create extra income, they decided to buy a horsebox which they could rent out to festival-goers.</desc><category>Bouwen en verbouwen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723141000 +0000" stop="20210723145000 +0000" catchup-id="988315139"><title>Alec Guinness: Talking Pictures</title><date>2013</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/93/2021071608005743699h.jpg"></icon><desc>A retrospective look at television appearances made over the years by Alec Guinness, capturing the milestones and highlights of his life and career.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723145000 +0000" stop="20210723161500 +0000" catchup-id="988315145"><title>Whisky Galore!</title><date>1949</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/34/2021071608005743651m.jpg"></icon><desc>Classic Ealing comedy about a scotch-laden ship that runs aground off the coast of the Outer Hebrides during the Second World War. The local islanders have depleted their supply of the amber nectar and are overjoyed at the thought of stocking up again. However, it is Sunday, and the teetotallers object to making free with the unexpected cargo.</desc><category>Film, Komedie, Oorlog</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723161500 +0000" stop="20210723170000 +0000" catchup-id="988315151"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/4/20210716080057436lhj.jpg"></icon><desc>The team are at Penrhyn Castle in North Wales. Antiques expert Claire Rawle uncovers a pristine vintage Barbie doll, and Adam Partridge finds a 300-year-old map of the area. Paul Martin finds an ice axe that may have been used to scale Mount Everest.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723170000 +0000" stop="20210723173000 +0000" catchup-id="988315157"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/60/2021071608005743661t.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Ellie Taylor, actor and writer Steve Pemberton, presenter Fern Britton and comedian Josh Widdicombe test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723173000 +0000" stop="20210723180000 +0000" catchup-id="988315163"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/11/20210716080057436kqz.jpg"></icon><desc>There is high drama as Yana the tiger cracks a canine. It must be removed, but it's not a simple procedure and the anaesthetic doesn't go to plan. With the help of a bucket of water and a tiny camera, Kate sets out to answer a burning question.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723180000 +0000" stop="20210723190000 +0000" catchup-id="988315169"><title>RHS Flower Show Tatton Park</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/8/20210716080057436qe9.jpg"></icon><desc>Arit Anderson and Adam Frost introduce this 2021's RHS Flower Show Tatton Park. With help from the team of garden experts, they present the blooming best of the show, all under the theme of `flower power'. Rachel De Thame sees how the spectacular contemporary floral displays of Fleur de Villes are created. Frances Tophill harnesses the power of trees for our health and well-being. Mark Lane joins the nursery team who have created a completely white garden display.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723190000 +0000" stop="20210723200000 +0000" catchup-id="988315175"><title>Gardeners' World</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/27/20210716080057436oj0.jpg"></icon><desc>At Longmeadow, Monty gives a masterclass on the summer pruning of fruit, has advice on maintaining ponds, and plants up a pot to give colour and interest to last into the autumn months. Adam Frost travels to Brodsworth Hall in South Yorkshire to meet a head gardener who has been set the challenge of restoring the gardens to their 19th-century glory.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723200000 +0000" stop="20210723210000 +0000" catchup-id="988315181"><title>Reclaiming Amy</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/67/20210716080057436szv.jpg"></icon><desc>To mark the ten year anniversary of the death of Amy Winehouse, her closest family and friends, who were with her throughout her life, reveal the truth about the music icon and the impact that her loss has had on them. Amy's mother Janis, who has never spoken in depth before, wants to reclaim the legacy of her daughter, celebrating Amy as the complex, strong and incredible woman she was and giving a different version of events from the story of the singer so often told.</desc><category>Muziek, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723210000 +0000" stop="20210723213000 +0000" catchup-id="988315187"><title>BBC Sessions: Amy Winehouse</title><date>2007</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/80/20210716080057436zws.jpg"></icon><desc>Hot from her triumph at the 2007 Brits where she won Best British Female in a tough field, Britain's best-selling albums artist of 2007, Amy Winehouse sashays into Bayswater's illustrious Porchester Hall for a one-off concert featuring songs from her current hit album, `Back to Black', including singles `Rehab' and `You Know I'm No Good', and 2003's Mercury Music Prize-nominated album, `Frank'.</desc><category>Muziek</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723213000 +0000" stop="20210723220000 +0000" catchup-id="988315193"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210716/61/20210716080057436fb7.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723220000 +0000" stop="20210723220500 +0000" catchup-id="989457070"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/19/202107170800301504fh.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723220500 +0000" stop="20210723233500 +0000" catchup-id="989457076"><title>Killing Escobar</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/21/20210717080030150xf5.jpg"></icon><desc>The incredible true story of Scottish mercenary Peter McAleese, who was hired to kill Colombian drug lord Pablo Escobar in 1989. With unprecedented access to Peter and other members of his team, this is the first full account of that fateful mission.</desc><category>Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210723233500 +0000" stop="20210724003000 +0000" catchup-id="989457082"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/51/20210717080030150xou.jpg"></icon><desc>EZ's brazen plan faces some unexpected hurdles, Coco finds a surprising sanctuary, and Emily is urged into an outing.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724003000 +0000" stop="20210724012000 +0000" catchup-id="989457088"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/76/20210717080030150w34.jpg"></icon><desc>EZ agonises over the smuggling failure, but older deeds overshadow his romance with Gaby and the rocky relationships of both Angel and Bishop.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724012000 +0000" stop="20210724021000 +0000" catchup-id="989457158"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/85/20210717080030150bsa.jpg"></icon><desc>Bishop hopes an old-school stunt can salvage the plan to break ranks with rival Mayans, even as other criminal players muscle in.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724021000 +0000" stop="20210724024500 +0000" catchup-id="989457164"><title>The Dark Side of Horse Racing - Panorama</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/84/20210717080030150r0r.jpg"></icon><desc>Horse racing is one of the most popular and profitable sports, a £5 billion industry in the UK and Ireland followed by millions. Panorama reporter Darragh MacIntyre investigates what can happen to racehorses when their careers end. The industry says that racing is now safer than ever, that the number of deaths on the track is falling and that the animals are looked after in retirement. Panorama discovers that off the track, many horses suffer career-ending injuries, and rather than being rehabilitated or retrained for life outside the sport, race horses that have been owned and trained by some of the biggest names in the industry have been put down, some meeting grisly deaths. [SL]</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724024500 +0000" stop="20210724031500 +0000" catchup-id="989457170"><title>Great British Railway Journeys</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/51/20210717080030150tds.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael Portillo follows his 1930s Bradshaw's guide to the unspoilt East Sussex Cinque Port of Rye. On the windswept harbour beach, he hears how, in 1928, a generation of lifeboatmen lost their lives in a tragic rescue attempt at sea. Michael visits the town's modern day lifeboat station to see how the RNLI's brave crews train today.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724031500 +0000" stop="20210724032000 +0000" catchup-id="989457176"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/91/20210717080030150gti.jpg"></icon><desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724032000 +0000" stop="20210724053500 +0000" catchup-id="989457182"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/51/20210717080030150v2z.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724053500 +0000" stop="20210724055000 +0000" catchup-id="989457188"><title>Wild &amp; Weird</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/70/20210717080030150nd8.jpg"></icon><desc>A look at marriage-themed stories, including how a porcupine found true love in a zoo, why a sewer may be a good place to prospect for gold, and a wedding in Arizona hit by a gigantic dust storm.</desc><category>Kinderen, Dieren, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724055000 +0000" stop="20210724062000 +0000" catchup-id="989457194"><title>The Dengineers</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/54/202107170800301519ae.jpg"></icon><desc>Campbell loves cycling and uses rollers to train at home, but there isn't much room and he has to move the sofa to put the rollers down. His mum and dad are getting fed up of the oil he gets everywhere. Campbell needs a cycling den where he can cycle all over the world without getting oil on his parents' sofa!</desc><category>Kinderen, Bouwen en verbouwen, Reality</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724062000 +0000" stop="20210724065000 +0000" catchup-id="989457200"><title>Marrying Mum &amp; Dad</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/31/20210717080030151adq.jpg"></icon><desc>Skull-obsessed Lilia is transporting her mum and future step-dad to Mexico as she attempts to recreate Mexico's biggest festival, Day of the Dead with ghoulishly good results. But will the wedding be `dead' good or deathly once our corpse bride and groom are revealed?</desc><category>Kinderen, Reality, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724065000 +0000" stop="20210724072000 +0000" catchup-id="989457206"><title>Blue Peter: KSI Earns His BP Badge!</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/26/20210719180047429q4m.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the first of our summer specials from the BP Garden. Richie, Mwaksy and Adam pick a Summer Squad of BP fans using their ideas, stories and brilliant post to inspire everyone to earn their BP badges. Richie meets internet superstar KSI, who performs his new single Holiday and picks his favourite raps from viewer send-ins!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724072000 +0000" stop="20210724073000 +0000" catchup-id="989457212"><title>What's Cooking Omari?</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/90/20210717080030151ckh.jpg"></icon><desc>Chef Omari is creating a delicious dinner for when dad gets home from work, cosy macaroni. This bowl of smooth, melty gorgeousness has a spicy pumpkin twist.</desc><category>Kinderen, Culinair, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724073000 +0000" stop="20210724080000 +0000" catchup-id="989457218"><title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/7/20210717080030151544.jpg"></icon><desc>Steve goes on an undercover mission to unearth the sneakiest dinosaurs that were far deadlier than they first appeared.</desc><category>Kinderen, Dieren, Geschiedenis, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724080000 +0000" stop="20210724090000 +0000" catchup-id="989457224"><title>Orbit: Earth's Extraordinary Journey</title><date>2012</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/8/202107170800301512sv.jpg"></icon><desc>Kate Humble and Dr Helen Czerski cover the January to March equinox. Kate gets closer to the Sun than she has ever been before, while Helen visits a place that gets some of the biggest and fastest snowstorms on Earth.</desc><category>Documentaire, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724090000 +0000" stop="20210724103000 +0000" catchup-id="989457230"><title>Saturday Kitchen Live</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/78/20210717080030151w17.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt and chefs David Carter and Shauna Froydenlund are joined by special guest Tom Allen. There are great moments from the BBC food archive, including clips from Rick Stein, Keith Floyd, Nigella Lawson and Mary Berry.</desc><category>Culinair, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724103000 +0000" stop="20210724113000 +0000" catchup-id="989457236"><title>A Cook Abroad: Tony Singh's India</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/83/20210717080030151pso.jpg"></icon><desc>Scottish chef Tony Singh travels to India, the country of his ancestors, to trace his family roots and discover whether his mum's Punjabi cooking is the real deal. He begins his journey in Amritsar before braving the Grand Trunk Road to Delhi.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen, Culinair</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724113000 +0000" stop="20210724123000 +0000" catchup-id="989457242"><title>Life in the Air</title><date>2014</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/28/20210717080030151cdj.jpg"></icon><desc>In the busy skies above our planet we'll meet a creature that creates sound out of thin air with the world's fastest courtship display and arguably the worlds most aggressive bird, harnessing cold aggression to protect its patch of sky. In a South American jungle we'll unravel the secrets of night time `hunt and evasion' flying, as bats and moths fight for the upper hand in one of the worlds oldest arms races.</desc><category>Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724123000 +0000" stop="20210724124000 +0000" catchup-id="989457248"><title>Best Dishes Ever</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/6/20210717080030151cru.jpg"></icon><desc>Our line-up of top chefs are looking at classic winter warmers that work equally well in spring, autumn and summer too. The menu includes Keith Floyd's beautiful beef provencale, a chicken dumpling soup from Rachel Khoo, the Hairy Bikers' perfect apple pie and James Martin working wonders with the humble jacket potato.</desc><category>Culinair, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724124000 +0000" stop="20210724125500 +0000" catchup-id="989457254"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/26/20210719180047429ube.jpg"></icon><desc>Hazel Irvine and Gabby Logan introduce the latest action from the opening day of the Olympics, with medals decided in fencing, judo and taekwondo. Britain's Ashley McKenzie is looking for a medal in the men's -60kg judo, while the men's gymnastics qualifying continues, with Max Whitlock and his GB team-mates looking to book places in the team final and in the individual apparatus finals.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724125500 +0000" stop="20210724163000 +0000" catchup-id="989457260"><title>The Hundred: Trent Rockets v Southern Brave</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/10/20210719180047429zh0.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage of the exciting new Hundred competition as Trent Rockets and Southern Brave play in their very first match. There are eight teams from seven cities competing this summer, and the fast-paced game sees 100 balls per innings - whoever scores the most runs wins. Featuring some of the world's best cricketers, the Trent Rockets boast the likes of England batsmen Joe Root and Dawid Malan, while the Southern Brave can call on England star Chris Jordan and New Zealand's batting sensation Devon Conway. Isa Guha presents the action and will be joined on commentary duties by Michael Vaughan, Phil Tufnell and special guests.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724163000 +0000" stop="20210724170000 +0000" catchup-id="989457266"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/92/202107170800301511uk.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Ellie Taylor, actor and writer Steve Pemberton, presenter Fern Britton and comedian Josh Widdicombe test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724170000 +0000" stop="20210724180000 +0000" catchup-id="989457272"><title>Japan with Sue Perkins</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/9/20210717080030151izj.jpg"></icon><desc>Sue Perkins starts her journey in Tokyo, Japan's glittering capital city and home to 36 million people. She trains with a female sumo wrestling team, meets a family who live with robots and attends a solo-wedding.</desc><category>Reizen, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724180000 +0000" stop="20210724190000 +0000" catchup-id="989457278"><title>RHS Flower Show Tatton Park</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/72/20210717080030151yr0.jpg"></icon><desc>Rachel de Thame and Joe Swift lead the team of garden experts as 2021's RHS Flower Show Tatton Park comes to a close. Love will be in the air as Carol Klein discovers the `plants with passion' on display in the floral marquee.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Natuur</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724190000 +0000" stop="20210724193000 +0000" catchup-id="989457284"><title>Dad's Army</title><date>1969</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/40/20210717080030151lp5.jpg"></icon><desc>An enemy aircraft crash-lands in the local reservoir, testing Captain Mainwaring's communication system.</desc><category>Sitcoms, Oorlog</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724193000 +0000" stop="20210724203000 +0000" catchup-id="989457290"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/95/20210719180047429is1.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeanette Kwakye introduces coverage of the men's road race and looks back at what happened in the women's football.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724203000 +0000" stop="20210724220500 +0000" catchup-id="989457296"><title>Pavarotti in Hyde Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210717/98/20210717080030151wz8.jpg"></icon><desc>In celebration of his 30-year career, the late Pavarotti is accompanied by the Philharmonia as he performs 20 arias as well as `O Sole Mio' and `Nessun Dorma' in a concert in Hyde Park.</desc><category>Muziek</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724220500 +0000" stop="20210724235500 +0000" catchup-id="990729008"><title>Stronger</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/99/202107180800424339ag.jpg"></icon><desc>Jeff Bauman loses both of his legs when two bombs explode during the Boston Marathon on April 15, 2013. With unwavering support from his family and girlfriend, Bauman embarks on a long and heroic journey to physical and emotional rehabilitation.</desc><category>Drama, Film, Biografie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210724235500 +0000" stop="20210725020000 +0000" catchup-id="990729014"><title>Marguerite</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/56/20210718080042433ako.jpg"></icon><desc>Paris in the 1920s. Wealthy Marguerite Dumont is an enthusiastic lover of opera. She often holds private concerts at home during which she sings for friends and acquaintances, but seems completely oblivious to the fact that she has been gifted with an astonishing lack of singing talent. Her fanciful delusions are aided by her entire social circle, in thrall to her money, as well as her servants and her husband - none of whom has ever uttered a single word of criticism.</desc><category>Film, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725020000 +0000" stop="20210725020500 +0000" catchup-id="990729020"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/17/20210718080042433ni2.jpg"></icon><desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725020500 +0000" stop="20210725053500 +0000" catchup-id="990729218"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/72/20210718080042433g5r.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725053500 +0000" stop="20210725060500 +0000" catchup-id="990729224"><title>Britain in Bloom</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/58/20210718080042433l85.jpg"></icon><desc>Chris Bavin heads to the seaside town of Southport in Merseyside where the Bloom team has been taking part in the annual floral competition for more than 20 years. After budget cuts in 2008, the council could no longer afford to look after all the town's green spaces.</desc><category>Natuur, Home &amp; Garden, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725060500 +0000" stop="20210725070500 +0000" catchup-id="990729230"><title>Gardeners' World</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/66/202107180800424330wc.jpg"></icon><desc>At Longmeadow, Monty gives a masterclass on the summer pruning of fruit, has advice on maintaining ponds, and plants up a pot to give colour and interest to last into the autumn months. Adam Frost travels to Brodsworth Hall in South Yorkshire to meet a head gardener who has been set the challenge of restoring the gardens to their 19th-century glory.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725070500 +0000" stop="20210725080000 +0000" catchup-id="990729236"><title>Countryfile</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/98/20210718080042433t43.jpg"></icon><desc>Anita Rani and Tom Heap head to Yorkshire's Flamborough Head. Anita visits England's largest onshore seabird colony at Bempton Cliffs, helping track breeding numbers and witnessing a very special arrival as a rare Albatross pays a visit. Below the cliffs, Tom explores some of the coast's chalk caves, discovering the rare life they support, and Tom and Anita are joined by local youngsters as they go on a rockpool safari to take stock of the marine life washed up at low tide.</desc><category>Natuur en milieu, Landbouw, Dieren, Reizen, Outdoor, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725080000 +0000" stop="20210725083000 +0000" catchup-id="990729242"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/46/202107180800424347l3.jpg"></icon><desc>It's cherry harvest and cherry-tasting time in both Beechgrove and in sunny Joppa. Kirsty creates a green talking point for any stylish home by taking a recycled picture frame and creating an easy-to-copy piece of living wall art with succulents.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725083000 +0000" stop="20210725093000 +0000" catchup-id="990729248"><title>Sunday Morning Live</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/75/20210718080042434f54.jpg"></icon><desc>A thought-provoking debate and instant audience reaction on the big ethical talking points of the week, together with roving reports from around the UK.</desc><category>Debat, Talkshow, Actualiteit</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725093000 +0000" stop="20210725110000 +0000" catchup-id="990729254"><title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/91/20210718080042434jvt.jpg"></icon><desc>A look back at some of the best segments from `Saturday Kitchen'. The popular cookery show offers recipes and ideas for mouth-watering food, interviews with great chefs and celebrity guests.</desc><category>Culinair, Bloemlezing</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725110000 +0000" stop="20210725111500 +0000" catchup-id="990729260"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/77/202107191800474296wx.jpg"></icon><desc>Hazel Irvine and Gabby Logan present further coverage from day two of the 2020 Olympics in Tokyo, which includes taekwondo and swimming.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725111500 +0000" stop="20210725121500 +0000" catchup-id="990729266"><title>A Cook Abroad: Rachel Khoo's Malaysia</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/76/20210718080042434j6b.jpg"></icon><desc>Cook and food writer Rachel Khoo heads to Malaysia, home of her extended family, to explore one of the most exciting cuisines on the planet. From the tropical shores of a remote fishing village, to a foraged feast deep in the jungle, Rachel travels across this multi-cultural country to find out whether good food can unite a nation.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen, Culinair</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725121500 +0000" stop="20210725125000 +0000" catchup-id="990729272"><title>Songs of Praise: Generations of Faith</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/92/20210719180047429o2z.jpg"></icon><desc>The Rev Kate Bottley is on the border of Staffordshire and Shropshire to join three generations of the Robinson family, discovering the Catholic history of Boscobel House, where after being defeated in the English Civil War, King Charles II went into hiding in a priest hole.</desc><category>Muziek, Religie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725125000 +0000" stop="20210725130000 +0000" catchup-id="990729278"><title>Lifeline</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/76/20210718080042434nml.jpg"></icon><desc>Claudia Winkleman presents an appeal on behalf of Target Ovarian Cancer, a charity funding scientific research into new treatments and providing support for all those affected by the disease.</desc><category>Goede doelen, Actualiteit</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725130000 +0000" stop="20210725163000 +0000" catchup-id="990729348"><title>The Hundred: London Spirit v Oval Invincibles</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/58/20210719180047429nxd.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725163000 +0000" stop="20210725170000 +0000" catchup-id="990729354"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/65/202107180800424346ip.jpg"></icon><desc>Coming from Grittleton House in Wiltshire, where antique experts Mark Stacey and Michael Baggott find objects to take off to auction. Mark hopes to get a good return on a couple of boomerangs and Michael admires a silver Chinese tea strainer with a jade handle. Paul Martin visits Fairfield House on the outskirts of Bath where in the 1930s the Ethiopian Emperor Haile Selassie lived after he was forced into exile when Mussolini invaded his home country.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725170000 +0000" stop="20210725173000 +0000" catchup-id="990729360"><title>The Yorkshire Dales</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/71/202107180800424341op.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul meets the butchers in Ilkley whose Yorkshire produce is being sold all over the country, heads for Bolton Abbey and spends time with the Duke of Devonshire, and takes time out with the Calendar Girls who shot to fame two decades ago.</desc><category>Documentaire, Samenleving, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725173000 +0000" stop="20210725180000 +0000" catchup-id="990729366"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/0/20210718080042434vgg.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Ellie Taylor, actor and writer Steve Pemberton, presenter Fern Britton and comedian Josh Widdicombe test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725180000 +0000" stop="20210725190000 +0000" catchup-id="990729372"><title>Tropic of Cancer</title><date>2010</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/75/20210718080042434q2r.jpg"></icon><desc>The second leg of the journey sees Simon dodge the Moroccan secret police in Western Sahara, travel on one of the world's longest trains in Mauritania, visit a forgotten refugee camp in the Algerian desert where more than 100,000 people live, and take a swim in a Libyan oasis with a government minder who bears an uncanny resemblance to Colonel Gadaffi.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725190000 +0000" stop="20210725200000 +0000" catchup-id="990729378"><title>Inside Monaco: Playground of the Rich</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210718/29/20210718080042434z1s.jpg"></icon><desc>Director Michael Waldman explores how this extraordinary country operates. He meets everyone from Prince Albert and his staff in the palace to wealthy widow Monika Bacardi, who takes him on a tour in her chauffeur-driven classic Rolls Royce.</desc><category>Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725200000 +0000" stop="20210725210000 +0000" catchup-id="990729384"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/14/20210719180047429yt7.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725210000 +0000" stop="20210725213000 +0000" catchup-id="995681188"><title>The Big Asian Stand Up</title><date></date><icon src=""></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725213000 +0000" stop="20210725222500 +0000" catchup-id="990729390"><title>Mayans MC</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/38/20210719180047430ntt.jpg"></icon><desc>EZ has a difficult time finding his footing in the club's hierarchy, and Angel loses himself to sex, booze, and violence.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725222500 +0000" stop="20210725231000 +0000" catchup-id="991904648"><title>Mayans MC</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/13/202107191800474302th.jpg"></icon><desc>Brutality is required as Bishop's Mayans seek to confront Ramos, and Adelita revisits her depleted outlaw clan.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210725231000 +0000" stop="20210726000500 +0000" catchup-id="991904654"><title>Mayans M.C.</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/28/20210719180047430lst.jpg"></icon><desc>Home truths prove distressing as Angel disrupts a family `brunch'. Miguel learns more of his mother's death, and Letica fears Coco is beyond saving.</desc><category>Misdaaddrama, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726000500 +0000" stop="20210726012500 +0000" catchup-id="991904660"><title>Norfolk</title><date>2015</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/42/202107191800474304na.jpg"></icon><desc>A teenage boy and his battle-weary father live a simple life in Norfolk. Days are spent hunting, fishing and daydreaming. Then out of nowhere, the father, a mercenary, is given a final deadly mission, one that threatens to destroy not just the target, but the love between a father and his son.</desc><category>Drama, Film, Thriller</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726012500 +0000" stop="20210726022500 +0000" catchup-id="991904666"><title>Gold Rush: Our Race to Olympic Glory</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/57/202107191800474308t8.jpg"></icon><desc>After the Sydney Olympics in 2000, Britain failed to move up from tenth position in the medal table at the Athens games in 2004. Increasingly reliant on a generation of ageing champions, it was time for our younger hopes to step up and deliver. And to ensure that funding delivered results, UK Sport introduced a no compromise approach, meaning that all funded athletes needed to start winning medals. The pressure was on for youngster Tom Daley to step up to the big time.</desc><category>Sport, Documentaire, Miniseries</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726022500 +0000" stop="20210726030500 +0000" catchup-id="991904672"><title>Holby City</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/32/202107190800474332yx.jpg"></icon><desc>Dom is shocked when he discovers Carole's secret, Hanssen is torn as to how to handle Abs's secret, and Josh tries to prove to Ange that he's up to the role of being a father.</desc><category>Dramaseries, Medisch</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726030500 +0000" stop="20210726031000 +0000" catchup-id="991904678"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/42/20210719080047433q59.jpg"></icon><desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726031000 +0000" stop="20210726054500 +0000" catchup-id="991904684"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/19/20210719080047433y6m.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726054500 +0000" stop="20210726063000 +0000" catchup-id="991904690"><title>Pointless</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/24/20210719080047433jbq.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726063000 +0000" stop="20210726073000 +0000" catchup-id="991904696"><title>The Repair Shop</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/51/20210719080047433nah.jpg"></icon><desc>First to arrive is Tom Wenham, with a pair of running shoes used by his grandma when she represented Great Britain at the Berlin Olympics in 1936. The bespoke shoes enabled Audrey and her relay teammates to race their way to a silver medal in front of Hitler. Repairing the running shoes is a huge responsibility for the barn's newest recruit, cobbler Dean Westmoreland.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726073000 +0000" stop="20210726080000 +0000" catchup-id="991904702"><title>The Week in Parliament</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/24/20210719080047433dek.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of the week's proceedings in Parliament, presented by David Cornock.</desc><category>Politiek, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726080000 +0000" stop="20210726090000 +0000" catchup-id="991904772"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/84/20210719080047433pvx.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726090000 +0000" stop="20210726110000 +0000" catchup-id="991904778"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/40/20210719080047433b3m.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726110000 +0000" stop="20210726114500 +0000" catchup-id="991904784"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/86/20210719180047430rnh.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726114500 +0000" stop="20210726123000 +0000" catchup-id="991904790"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/32/202107190800474347x4.jpg"></icon><desc>The reds and blues are bargain hunting at Gloucester antiques centre with the help of experts Raj Bisram and Stephanie Connell. As usual they have one hour to spend £300 on 3 items to take to auction. Presenter, Eric Knowles travels to Stroud to learn about an unknown inventor who changed landscape of the world.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726123000 +0000" stop="20210726131500 +0000" catchup-id="991904796"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/56/20210719080047434jki.jpg"></icon><desc>Sarah is at Altrincham Recycling Centre, Greater Manchester, where she is on the look out for three dump diamonds that she can transform into fabulous furnishings. Sarah finds a granite worktop that she thinks has designer Daniel Heath written all over it.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726131500 +0000" stop="20210726134500 +0000" catchup-id="991904802"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/6/20210719080047434o28.jpg"></icon><desc>Two farming families are both hoping that their much-loved pygmy goats will bring them acclaim at this years Mid Devon Agricultural show. The competition is tough and there's record numbers of goats in the ring.</desc><category>Documentaire, Landbouw</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726134500 +0000" stop="20210726143000 +0000" catchup-id="991904808"><title>Escape to the Country</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/46/2021071908004743459l.jpg"></icon><desc>Sonali Shah is property hunting in the Derbyshire countryside with a couple who have a £450,000 budget and hopes that this move will transport them to a village with community spirit and a complete change of scenery. Away from the search, Sonali visits the factory of Royal Crown Derby and discovers how the porcelain industry here is a real hallmark of Britain's ceramic making heritage.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Bouwen en verbouwen, Business &amp; Financial</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726143000 +0000" stop="20210726153000 +0000" catchup-id="991904814"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/96/20210719080047434xs6.jpg"></icon><desc>Ruth Madoc and Su Pollard, best known for their appearances in sitcom `Hi-De-Hi', are antique hunting with Phil Serrell and Raj Bisram. Setting off from the Welsh border town of Monmouth, they head for auction in Congleton, Cheshire.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726153000 +0000" stop="20210726161500 +0000" catchup-id="991904820"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/9/20210719080047434gy8.jpg"></icon><desc>The show comes from Culzean Castle on the west coast of Scotland. Experts Natasha Raskin Sharp and Raj Bisram are on hand to find a selection of objects to take to auction. Natasha values a collection of Victorian Spiritualist photographs, while a Hornby toy train set grabs Raj's attention.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726161500 +0000" stop="20210726170000 +0000" catchup-id="991904826"><title>Pointless</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/85/202107190800474348j3.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726170000 +0000" stop="20210726173000 +0000" catchup-id="991904832"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/28/20210719080047434rcd.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Shappi Khorsandi, journalist and newsreader Michael Buerk, actress Amanda Abbington and comedian Elis James test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726173000 +0000" stop="20210726180000 +0000" catchup-id="991904838"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/76/202107190800474342b0.jpg"></icon><desc>Kate meets Blue, an ostrich with an identity problem. He seems to think he's a zebra, and while he's hanging out with his stripy friends, he's neglecting his parental duties. Giant otters Inny and Gordit are a handful, and cleaning their mucky enclosure is a major logistical challenge.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726180000 +0000" stop="20210726190000 +0000" catchup-id="991904844"><title>Gold Town</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/34/20210719080047434ioo.jpg"></icon><desc>It's February 2020, and the mine is six months behind schedule, with no sign of the processing plant. Despite their efforts, winter conditions mean they haven't been able to finish creating a flat platform on the hillside for building to start.</desc><category>Miniseries, Documentaire, Samenleving</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726190000 +0000" stop="20210726193000 +0000" catchup-id="991904850"><title>Only Connect</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/18/20210719080047434rzl.jpg"></icon><desc>Three space enthusiasts take on a team of music lovers in this opening heat to find the connection between Sole support, Sequence outcome, Serve jam and Stable police officer.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726193000 +0000" stop="20210726200500 +0000" catchup-id="991904856"><title>University Challenge</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/37/20210719080047434t6w.jpg"></icon><desc>In another first round match, the students representing London Business School battle it out with Hertford College, Oxford for a place in the second round. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726200500 +0000" stop="20210726211500 +0000" catchup-id="991904862"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/42/2021071918004743003a.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726211500 +0000" stop="20210726213500 +0000" catchup-id="995681194"><title>Olympics 2020 Live</title><date></date><icon src=""></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726213500 +0000" stop="20210726221500 +0000" catchup-id="991904874"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210719/56/20210719080047434xdw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726221500 +0000" stop="20210726222000 +0000" catchup-id="993145409"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/98/20210720080040150ke3.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726222000 +0000" stop="20210726232000 +0000" catchup-id="993145415"><title>Secrets of the Museum</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/60/20210720080040150ayr.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210726232000 +0000" stop="20210727002000 +0000" catchup-id="993145421"><title>Countryfile</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/52/20210720080040150tw2.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727002000 +0000" stop="20210727010500 +0000" catchup-id="993145427"><title>Frontline Fightback</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/72/20210720080040150gkr.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727010500 +0000" stop="20210727011000 +0000" catchup-id="995681200"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/51/20210722080047439v8e.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727011000 +0000" stop="20210727054500 +0000" catchup-id="993145439"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/6/202107200800401511c7.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727054500 +0000" stop="20210727061500 +0000" catchup-id="993145445"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/63/20210720080040151qkr.jpg"></icon><desc>It's cherry harvest and cherry-tasting time in both Beechgrove and in sunny Joppa. Kirsty creates a green talking point for any stylish home by taking a recycled picture frame and creating an easy-to-copy piece of living wall art with succulents.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727061500 +0000" stop="20210727070000 +0000" catchup-id="993145451"><title>Pointless</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/10/202107200800401516i1.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727070000 +0000" stop="20210727073000 +0000" catchup-id="993145457"><title>Great British Railway Journeys</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/33/20210720080040151r2s.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael heads to the splendid Walmer Castle, home during the 1920s to Lord Beauchamp. Michael's guide, the founder of the LGBTQ working group for English Heritage, tells Michael of the lavish homosexual parties Lord Beauchamp held at the castle.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727073000 +0000" stop="20210727080000 +0000" catchup-id="993145463"><title>The Yorkshire Dales</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/87/202107200800401516rj.jpg"></icon><desc>Adventurer and explorer Paul Rose starts his journey in the town of Hawes where locals now run many of their own services, including the buses. Paul checks out why cycling is so popular in the Dales and tries to get to the top of the Buttertubs Pass.</desc><category>Documentaire, Samenleving, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727080000 +0000" stop="20210727090000 +0000" catchup-id="993145469"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/70/20210720080040151s3j.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727090000 +0000" stop="20210727110000 +0000" catchup-id="993145539"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/48/20210720080040151u82.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727110000 +0000" stop="20210727114500 +0000" catchup-id="993145545"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/95/20210720080040151kgu.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727114500 +0000" stop="20210727123000 +0000" catchup-id="993145551"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/13/202107200800401511ny.jpg"></icon><desc>Anita Manning presents from Harrogate with experts Kate Bliss and Mark Stacey. There's a tense atmosphere at Thomas Watsons auctioneers, and Anita catches up with Charles Hanson and a very special musical collection.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727123000 +0000" stop="20210727131500 +0000" catchup-id="993145557"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/88/2021072008004015125c.jpg"></icon><desc>An old card table gets a new deal when Sarah decides to take it to furniture designer Norman Wilkinson. Together they decide this little winner could do with a sparkling new top. Sarah's second item is a lightweight wardrobe with ample space to be completely transformed.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727131500 +0000" stop="20210727134500 +0000" catchup-id="993145563"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/5/20210720080040151366.jpg"></icon><desc>Veteran farming family The Dunn's and retired businessman Stephen are all heading to Ryedale to show off their finest sheep. For Stephen this is a chance to carry on his wife's legacy and for both families it's the opportunity to build on their reputations.</desc><category>Documentaire, Landbouw</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727134500 +0000" stop="20210727143000 +0000" catchup-id="993145569"><title>Escape to the Country</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/40/20210720080040151blm.jpg"></icon><desc>Margherita Taylor is on a house hunting mission in the Dorset countryside, helping a couple with £500,000 find a character property with space for entertaining and a baby grand piano, as well as an outdoor setting to keep a keen gardener busy. Along the way, Margherita heads out to the oyster beds of Poole harbour to discover more about how they are farmed and harvested sustainably to meet popular demand.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Bouwen en verbouwen, Business &amp; Financial</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727143000 +0000" stop="20210727153000 +0000" catchup-id="993145575"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/63/202107200800401512s7.jpg"></icon><desc>Top Italian cooks Antonio Carluccio and Gennaro Contraldo are on a road trip around East Anglia. Restaurateurs, writers and old friends, the greedy Italians forage for antiques in the company of experts David Harper and James Braxton.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727153000 +0000" stop="20210727161500 +0000" catchup-id="993145581"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/23/202107200800401518ty.jpg"></icon><desc>Members of the public try to make money out of their antiques by taking a risk at auction.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727161500 +0000" stop="20210727170000 +0000" catchup-id="993145587"><title>Pointless</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/53/202107200800401517ed.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727170000 +0000" stop="20210727173000 +0000" catchup-id="993145593"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/47/20210720080040151k4b.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Shappi Khorsandi, journalist and newsreader Michael Buerk, actress Amanda Abbington and comedian Elis James test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727173000 +0000" stop="20210727180000 +0000" catchup-id="993145599"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/21/20210720080040152bel.jpg"></icon><desc>Wolves Max and Mel are repeatedly being attacked by the pack's alpha male, and their injuries are becoming more serious. So the keepers embark on an ambitious project to create a completely new pack with a difference. Ben gets a peek at some incredible footage of male koala Burke as the park's new breeding programme takes a huge step forward.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727180000 +0000" stop="20210727190000 +0000" catchup-id="993145669"><title>Great Australian Railway Journeys</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/58/202107200800401524y2.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael Portillo ventures down under to experience one of the world's greatest rail journeys aboard the legendary Ghan Railway. His 1913 Bradshaw's Guide tells him `a transcontinental railway is being constructed' and he traces its route from the southern harbour of Port Augusta to the port of Darwin on the north coast.</desc><category>Reizen, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727190000 +0000" stop="20210727200000 +0000" catchup-id="993145675"><title>Secrets of the Museum</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/85/20210720080040152nfu.jpg"></icon><desc>Some of the largest paintings ever seen at the V&amp;A are unveiled, Manuel's costume from Fawlty Towers goes on show, and the museum's oldest teddy bear has a special visitor.</desc><category>Beeldende kunst, Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727200000 +0000" stop="20210727210000 +0000" catchup-id="993145681"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/9/202107200800401522fr.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727210000 +0000" stop="20210727213000 +0000" catchup-id="993145687"><title>Cunk on Britain</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/64/20210720080040152eh6.jpg"></icon><desc>Philomena examines the first half of the 20th century: with two world wars, but no World Cup.</desc><category>Documentaire, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727213000 +0000" stop="20210727221000 +0000" catchup-id="993145693"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210720/47/20210720080040152nht.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Emily Maitlis.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727221000 +0000" stop="20210727221500 +0000" catchup-id="994398530"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/73/20210721080042432w8p.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727221500 +0000" stop="20210727231500 +0000" catchup-id="994398544"><title>My Congo</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/24/20210721080042432zmz.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210727231500 +0000" stop="20210728001500 +0000" catchup-id="994398557"><title>Our NHS: A Hidden History</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/56/20210721080042432i1v.jpg"></icon><desc>As we emerge from a global pandemic that has turned our world upside down, David Olusoga explores the hidden history of the nurses, doctors and health workers who, for more than 70 years, have been coming to Britain from overseas to serve in the NHS. Without them the NHS would have been in danger of collapse, not least during the current COVID crisis.</desc><category>Documentaire, Gezondheid, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728001500 +0000" stop="20210728010000 +0000" catchup-id="994398569"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/85/202107210800424324xs.jpg"></icon><desc>Prominent criminal barristers Sasha Wass QC and Jeremy Dein QC investigate an infamous Scottish murder case from 1862. A former domestic servant was sentenced to death for killing one of her friends, despite there being a compelling alternative suspect. Glasgow, 1862. On a summer's afternoon, members of the affluent Fleming family returned home from holiday to discover that their housemaid Jess McPherson was missing. They eventually unlocked her bedroom door to find her dead body.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728010000 +0000" stop="20210728014500 +0000" catchup-id="994398585"><title>Frontline Fightback</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/81/2021072108004243288n.jpg"></icon><desc>A Premier League footballer's house is targeted twice by burglars of high-value properties - but they are quickly caught thanks to a helicopter fitted with heat-seeking cameras.</desc><category>Miniseries, Documentaire, Misdaad</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728014500 +0000" stop="20210728015000 +0000" catchup-id="994398597"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/76/20210721080042432ooh.jpg"></icon><desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728015000 +0000" stop="20210728054500 +0000" catchup-id="994398606"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/17/20210721080042432i6d.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728054500 +0000" stop="20210728063000 +0000" catchup-id="994398618"><title>Pointless</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/65/20210721080042432nsn.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728063000 +0000" stop="20210728070000 +0000" catchup-id="994398630"><title>Great British Railway Journeys</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/47/20210721080042432ii4.jpg"></icon><desc>Armed with his interwar copy of Bradshaw's Guide to the Railways, Michael reaches the Kent seaside resort of Herne Bay, where he learns about a pioneering aviatrix who began her working life as a typist in Hull but whose epic achievements made her an international celebrity. Michael takes the train five miles west along the coast before heading offshore into the entrance to the Thames Estuary.</desc><category>Documentaire, Reizen</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728070000 +0000" stop="20210728073000 +0000" catchup-id="994398642"><title>Beechgrove</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/20/20210721080042432jhu.jpg"></icon><desc>Carole and Mairi are at Beechgrove taking a look at the now-blooming wildflower bank that Chris cleared, weeded and sowed in 2019. Meanwhile, Kirsty is in her pretty and productive allotment, repurposing an old wine box to make into a trendy planter for some of her purple produce. Elsewhere, George is at home in sunny Joppa taking a look at his no-mow meadow and the yellow rattle that he sowed last year, and Chris is at home high up in the Cotswolds, where he shows us a potting shed.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728073000 +0000" stop="20210728080000 +0000" catchup-id="994398653"><title>Super League Show</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/97/2021072108004243202j.jpg"></icon><desc>Tanya Arnold presents highlights and analysis from the latest round of matches in Super League. Catalans Dragons are looking to maintain their impressive start to the season. The Dragons are top of the table and this week take on Castleford. Champions St Helens are in second place, they have a home game against Hull Kingston Rovers whilst Wigan take on Wakefield. Leeds play Salford, Huddersfield are at home to Hull FC and Leigh go in search of their first win of the season.</desc><category>Sport, Rugby League</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728080000 +0000" stop="20210728090000 +0000" catchup-id="994398665"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/55/20210721080042433z8p.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728090000 +0000" stop="20210728110000 +0000" catchup-id="994398677"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/21/20210721080042433f7h.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728110000 +0000" stop="20210728114500 +0000" catchup-id="994398689"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/71/20210721080042433yna.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728114500 +0000" stop="20210728123000 +0000" catchup-id="994398698"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/86/20210721080042433fgt.jpg"></icon><desc>Natasha Raskin Sharp finds out more about the history of local landscape with artist David Walker Barker. She is also joined by experts Tim Weeks and Colin Young, and both teams are determined to buy three items that will make a profit at auction.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728123000 +0000" stop="20210728131500 +0000" catchup-id="994398708"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/5/202107210800424330jg.jpg"></icon><desc>Sarah Moore enlists the help of upholsterer Anthony Devine to turn a set of stools into something stylish. Plus, wood working duo Josh and Oli put their creative skills to the test by attempting to turn an oak table into sleek skateboards.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728131500 +0000" stop="20210728134500 +0000" catchup-id="994398720"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/35/20210721080042433fbb.jpg"></icon><desc>Bath and its beautiful architecture is the backdrop for one of the oldest farmers markets in Britain where Hugh will be trying to sell his families award winning cheese and the Kimber family will be selling their meat and dairy products straight off the farm.</desc><category>Documentaire, Landbouw</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728134500 +0000" stop="20210728143000 +0000" catchup-id="994398795"><title>Escape to the Country</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/86/202107210800424339v6.jpg"></icon><desc>Sonali Shah is house hunting with a couple who have a budget of £650,000 and want to quit the city to find a house with great entertaining potential in the Cheshire countryside. Sonali also delves into the region's manufacturing heritage at one of the country's best preserved textile mills from the Industrial Revolution.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Bouwen en verbouwen, Business &amp; Financial</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728143000 +0000" stop="20210728153000 +0000" catchup-id="994398805"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/52/20210721080042433twz.jpg"></icon><desc>Aldo Zilli and Ching He-Huang do battle on this road trip around south eastern England, aided by experts Natasha Raskin and Paul Laidlaw. Aldo plumps for a gold ring despite expert advice while Ching hopes antiques with an eastern origin will far well at auction in north London.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728153000 +0000" stop="20210728161500 +0000" catchup-id="994398816"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/3/20210721080042433yxz.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Martin finds out all about the fascinating people of Sledmere house through the ages.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728161500 +0000" stop="20210728170000 +0000" catchup-id="994398828"><title>Pointless</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/9/20210721080042433pij.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728170000 +0000" stop="20210728173000 +0000" catchup-id="994398837"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/1/20210721080042434qw1.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Shappi Khorsandi, journalist and newsreader Michael Buerk, actress Amanda Abbington and comedian Elis James test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728173000 +0000" stop="20210728180000 +0000" catchup-id="994398843"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/13/20210721080042434up0.jpg"></icon><desc>A romantic liaison is planned between two crafty kinkajous. But these animals have sharp teeth and claws, so the keepers must keep a close eye on this first date. If all goes well, the park could have its first ever kinkajou. Kate administers a calming treat to Razina the rhino, who has been undergoing fertility treatment in an effort to help rescue the northern white rhino species.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728180000 +0000" stop="20210728190000 +0000" catchup-id="994398913"><title>Great Australian Railway Journeys</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/26/20210721080042434d6i.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael Portillo explores New South Wales, steered by his 1913 Bradshaw's Guide. He strikes west into the Blue Mountains and travels 570 miles into the interior of the vast Australian continent to reach the mining city of Broken Hill. In the waterside metropolis of Sydney, the NSW capital, Michael investigates the origins of the city as a penal colony, visiting the Hyde Park Barracks, where many of the first convicts were housed.</desc><category>Reizen, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728190000 +0000" stop="20210728200000 +0000" catchup-id="994398919"><title>Chris Packham: The Walk That Made Me</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/55/20210721080042434hl4.jpg"></icon><desc>Wandering along the River Itchen and Itchen Navigation, Chris explains the importance of natural surroundings when it comes to our well-being. His journey stirs up powerful and difficult memories from his own struggles with mental health issues. Walking with a hand-held camera, Chris heads north, starting a few miles outside Southampton and ending up at Winchester Cathedral. Following the path of one the oldest waterways in the country, he meets those who live, work and play in the area.</desc><category>Documentaire, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728200000 +0000" stop="20210728210000 +0000" catchup-id="994398925"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/58/20210721080042434pir.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728210000 +0000" stop="20210728213000 +0000" catchup-id="994398931"><title>Mortimer &amp; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/49/20210721080042434mdd.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul takes Bob on a trip down memory lane and back to the River Lea in Hertfordshire, where Paul used to come as a teenager with his mates. They would catch the train from north London to fish this network of rivers and canals that flow from Hertfordshire into the Thames, and just like when Paul was young, Paul and Bob fish for perch.</desc><category>Vissen, Outdoor</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728213000 +0000" stop="20210728221000 +0000" catchup-id="994398937"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210721/78/20210721080042434gj1.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Emily Maitlis.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728221000 +0000" stop="20210728221500 +0000" catchup-id="995681206"><title>Weather</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/37/20210722080047440gfq.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer, Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728221500 +0000" stop="20210728235500 +0000" catchup-id="995681212"><title>Chappaquiddick</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/52/202107220800474403yc.jpg"></icon><desc>On July 18, 1969, Senator Ted Kennedy drives his car off of a bridge on Massachusetts' Chappaquiddick Island. The accident results in the death of passenger Mary Jo Kopechne, a 28-year-old campaign strategist who worked for Kennedy. The ongoing investigation into the mysterious and scandalous events forever alters his political legacy and ultimately changes the course of presidential history.</desc><category>Film, Thriller, Historisch drama</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210728235500 +0000" stop="20210729005500 +0000" catchup-id="995682050"><title>Forensics: The Real CSI</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/30/202107220800474402ho.jpg"></icon><desc>Forensic scene investigator Drew Birtles is deployed to lead the search for evidence after a woman in her 50s phones 999 to allege that an engineer who visited her home by appointment to fit a smart meter has indecently exposed himself. Facing a case that is difficult to prove, Drew sets to work using forensic light sources and DNA evidence to build a picture of what went on in the woman's house.</desc><category>Misdaad, Wetenschap</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729005500 +0000" stop="20210729015500 +0000" catchup-id="995682056"><title>Asia: Our Wild Adventures</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/56/20210722080047440j0i.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC presenters look back on their adventures throughout Indonesia and Mongolia, situated in earth's largest continent: Asia. Steve Backshall looks back on one particularly unnerving adventure in Indonesia, a place very close to his heart.</desc><category>Natuur, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729015500 +0000" stop="20210729024000 +0000" catchup-id="995682062"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/58/202107220800474407l8.jpg"></icon><desc>Leading criminal barristers Jeremy Dein QC and Sasha Wass QC investigate a complex case from Victorian Manchester. Following the shooting of a policeman during an attempt to rescue prominent political prisoners, five men stood trial and three were hanged, including 19-year-old William Philip Allen. Manchester, 1867. A police van transporting two notorious political prisoners was travelling through the city.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729024000 +0000" stop="20210729024500 +0000" catchup-id="995682068"><title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/38/2021072208004744001h.jpg"></icon><desc>Detailed weather forecast.</desc><category>Weer</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729024500 +0000" stop="20210729053000 +0000" catchup-id="995682074"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/50/20210722080047440w08.jpg"></icon><desc>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729053000 +0000" stop="20210729061500 +0000" catchup-id="995682080"><title>Pointless</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/9/20210722080047441022.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729061500 +0000" stop="20210729070000 +0000" catchup-id="995682086"><title>Murder, Mystery and My Family: Case Closed?</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/92/2021072208004744121w.jpg"></icon><desc>Butterknowle, County Durham, 1884. On a dark and rainy Saturday night, following a pigeon-shooting competition, Police Sergeant William Smith was out on his rounds at pub closing time. Suddenly, a group of three men emerged from the darkness and brutally attacked him.</desc><category>Documentaire, Geschiedenis</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729070000 +0000" stop="20210729080000 +0000" catchup-id="995682092"><title>Gardeners' World</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/58/20210722080047441hh6.jpg"></icon><desc>At Longmeadow, Monty gives a masterclass on the summer pruning of fruit, gives advice on maintaining ponds and plants up a pot to give colour and interest to last into the autumn months. Adam Frost travels to Brodsworth Hall in South Yorkshire to meet a head gardener who has been set the challenge of restoring the gardens to their 19th century glory.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729080000 +0000" stop="20210729090000 +0000" catchup-id="995682098"><title>BBC News at 9</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/57/202107220800474416xb.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729090000 +0000" stop="20210729110000 +0000" catchup-id="995682104"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/14/20210722080047441121.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729110000 +0000" stop="20210729114500 +0000" catchup-id="995682110"><title>Olympics 2020</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/60/20210722080047441d9g.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729114500 +0000" stop="20210729123000 +0000" catchup-id="995682116"><title>Bargain Hunt</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/56/20210722080047441egq.jpg"></icon><desc>Eric Knowles presents from Lincoln with experts Gary Pe and Jonathan Pratt. The reds and blues race around the Lincolnshire Antiques and Home show, while Eric uncovers the intriguing story behind a collection of postcards from the WWI era.</desc><category>Spelshow, Verzamelen, Kunstnijverheid, Veiling</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729123000 +0000" stop="20210729131500 +0000" catchup-id="995682122"><title>Money for Nothing</title><date>2017</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/23/202107220800474416pt.jpg"></icon><desc>Sarah saves three incredible items from certain doom, including a green enamel light shade for blacksmith Bex Simon to work on. Plus, a battered old brown 1970s sideboard for screen printing sensation Daniel Heath to revamp.</desc><category>Reality, Doe-het-zelf</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729131500 +0000" stop="20210729134500 +0000" catchup-id="995682128"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/88/2021072208004744138r.jpg"></icon><desc>British White Cattle farmers Vivien, a retired GP and David and Angela are hoping to help keep their rare breeds alive by competing at the 104th Tendring Show in Essex. It's their local show and means a lot to them and the future of their beloved herds.</desc><category>Documentaire, Landbouw</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729134500 +0000" stop="20210729143000 +0000" catchup-id="995682134"><title>Escape to the Country</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/15/20210722080047441gq7.jpg"></icon><desc>Alistair Appleton is on a property-searching mission in the Devon countryside, helping a mother-and-daughter duo with £750,000 find a home for three generations of their family and an eco-camping business. He also visits Chagford Community Farm.</desc><category>Home &amp; Garden, Bouwen en verbouwen, Business &amp; Financial</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729143000 +0000" stop="20210729153000 +0000" catchup-id="995682140"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/56/20210722080047441zs8.jpg"></icon><desc>Two legends of British comedy, Ronni Ancona and Jan Ravens are joined on this road trip by antiquers Phil Serrell and James Braxton. Starting in the north Yorkshire town of Redcar they'll head for auction in Stockport in Cheshire.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Beeldende kunst</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729153000 +0000" stop="20210729161500 +0000" catchup-id="995682146"><title>Flog It!</title><date>2016</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/73/202107220800474423si.jpg"></icon><desc>The team are at Wolverhampton Art Gallery. Experts Caroline Hawley and David Harper are on hand to value items and take them off to auction. Turning up out of the hundreds of bags and boxes is a jumble sale find that proves to be a valuable piece of jewellery.</desc><category>Verzamelen, Veiling, Kunstnijverheid</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729161500 +0000" stop="20210729170000 +0000" catchup-id="995682152"><title>Pointless</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/66/202107220800474425gu.jpg"></icon><desc>A twist on the classic quiz show formula, contestants search through the depths of their knowledge in an attempt to score as few points as possible.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729170000 +0000" stop="20210729173000 +0000" catchup-id="995682158"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title><date>2018</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/91/20210722080047442rce.jpg"></icon><desc>Richard Osman hosts as comedian Shappi Khorsandi, journalist and newsreader Michael Buerk, actress Amanda Abbington and comedian Elis James test their general knowledge skills.</desc><category>Spelshow, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729173000 +0000" stop="20210729180000 +0000" catchup-id="995682164"><title>Animal Park</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/95/202107220800474428dv.jpg"></icon><desc>The keepers at the park face a challenge from some territorial lions who are attacking their vehicles whenever they go off-road. However, one of the lions, Sweetpea, may have an underlying medical condition that is causing her to be aggressive. Ben helps set up an experiment to find out if the Cuban crocodiles, Fang and Kayo, can perform the famous death roll.</desc><category>Reality, Natuur, Dieren, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729180000 +0000" stop="20210729190000 +0000" catchup-id="995682170"><title>Great Australian Railway Journeys</title><date>2019</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/71/20210722080047442jr8.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael Portillo embarks on a rail adventure aboard the transcontinental Indian Pacific Railway, from the southern port city of Adelaide, South Australia, 1,700 miles deep into the desert, to the gold rush town of Kalgoorlie, and finishes in Perth, Western Australia. First, Michael explores McLaren Vale, where an enterprising early 19th century Briton with a murky past began to grow vines.</desc><category>Reizen, Documentaire</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729190000 +0000" stop="20210729200000 +0000" catchup-id="995682176"><title>Yorkshire Firefighters</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/69/20210722080047442g75.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the run up to Bonfire Night, and the crews across some of West Yorkshire's 40 stations are wondering how lockdown and the banning of organised bonfires will affect their normally busy workload around November 5th. They soon find out as they are called out to a post box fire and reports of a firework being pushed through the letterbox of a house in Leeds, where a terrified mother and young daughter are inside.</desc><category>Documentaire, Samenleving</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729200000 +0000" stop="20210729201000 +0000" catchup-id="995682182"><title>QI XS</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/13/20210722080047442drd.jpg"></icon><desc>In this selection of highlights, Sandi takes on the world's loneliest frog, an exploding horse, and a dog called Ronnie Barker, accompanied by Alan Davies and their guests.</desc><category>Spelshow, Komedie</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729201000 +0000" stop="20210729210000 +0000" catchup-id="995682188"><title>Olympics 2020 Extra</title><date></date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/0/20210722080047442n5e.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729210000 +0000" stop="20210729213000 +0000" catchup-id="995682194"><title>Live at the Apollo: The One About Transport</title><date>2020</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/73/20210722080047442dp9.jpg"></icon><desc>Classic routines about transport from Michael McIntyre, Gina Yashere, Lenny Henry, Rachel Parris, Chris McCausland, Jason Manford and more.</desc><category>Standup komedie, Entertainment</category></programme><programme channel="141429351" start="20210729213000 +0000" stop="20210729221000 +0000" catchup-id="995682200"><title>Newsnight</title><date>2021</date><icon src="https://t-mobiletv.nl:443/CPS/images/universal/film/program/202107/20210722/8/20210722080047442ycn.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Kirsty Wark.</desc><category>Nieuws</category></programme>