<programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229011500 +0000" stop="20221229021500 +0000" catchup-id="G-rBw4u80Ns32zF0wwA7O2qp3eC2dLBGldxm4Flc"><title>Signed: Trailblazers: A Rocky Mountain Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The trio are inspired to step out of their own comfort zone as they prepare to emulate Isabella’s most impressive feat - summitting a 14,000ft mountain. They also meet the African-American sisters blazing a trail through the male-dominated world of rodeo, howl with wolves at a wildlife sanctuary, and visit the spiritual and religious centres clustered around the Sangre de Cristo Mountains.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229021500 +0000" stop="20221229024500 +0000" catchup-id="ooXInznA8mgxwTDqZDNYgpsQ05XV4MeI_3o6l4Aj"><title>See Hear</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/ueAmDj_irz8MdgbkftyL0Q.jpg"></icon><desc>A special episode that looks back at 2022 and its highs and lows, including the passing of the BSL Act, the invasion of Ukraine, the explosion of deaf representation on the silver screen and the passing of the Queen. Yvonne and Julian are at Avon Valley Adventure and Wildlife Park to see the Christmas lights, and later on, they interview actress Amy Murray, who appears in in Netflix’s The Witcher: Blood Origin as Fenrik. Meanwhile, Damaris Cooke reports on how the England deaf futsal women’s team has made history by becoming European champions in October and meets captain Emma Brown and manager Marios Costi, as well as some of the players, to find out more about their journey to gold.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229024500 +0000" stop="20221229031500 +0000" catchup-id="E-IujqHMHtBAPfsJrt3wnGr89m03f-kNmabGYjWl"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Shirley Ballas</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>World-renowned dancer and head judge of Strictly Come Dancing, Shirley Ballas, checks into the B&amp;B by the sea. Nestled on the wild coast of Northern Ireland, this 19th-century Victorian villa is a very special place, looked after by host Sharon and her team. They ensure that all guests come away from the B&amp;B with new skills and a fresh perspective. Sharon is joined by Michelin-starred chef Alex Greene, who runs the kitchen and makes sure every meal is a truly memorable experience. Driver Rory ensures that all guests get to and from the B&amp;B without a hitch whilst providing extensive knowledge of the local area. Nicknamed the Queen of Latin, Shirley takes a break from her hectic schedule to offer her time to the B&amp;B, but Sharon and her team keep Shirley on her toes with this Northern Irish adventure. Unfortunately, there isn't any time to relax, as Shirley is put straight to work with the team. From pig farming to pottery making, Shirley takes every challenge in her stride.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229031500 +0000" stop="20221229034500 +0000" catchup-id="emrUuinnPBCVIYk5OXZlky57Oz6l8cYqCX-CZ4z1"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Deborah Meaden</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Deborah Meaden has taken time out of her busy schedule to lend a hand to the B&amp;B team. She has a unique connection to the sea, making this visit even more personal for the TV star. This stay is also an experience of firsts for Deborah, who has never been to Northern Ireland before, never ridden a horse in the sea before and - wait for this - never cooked a meal before. Sharon and the team hope to see if this 'dragon' can take the heat in the kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229034500 +0000" stop="20221229041500 +0000" catchup-id="C_gZMCGUcZepOo4FOKyrg8a0T3xvLbX-EaiDgu2F"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Fred Sirieix</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Television presenter and renowned maitre d' Fred Sirieix checks into the B&amp;B by the sea. Fred may have made his mark working in some of the world's best hotels and restaurants, but after recently discovering his Irish ancestry, he's lending his hospitality skills to the B&amp;B team. The team set Fred an important challenge to find the best local tipple to compliment a special custard. They visit the oldest licensed whisky distillery in the world before mucking in at the local butchers to test Fred's sausage-making skills. Fred originally trained as a pastry chef, so he adds a certain je ne sais quoi to the B&amp;B kitchen, where he takes on a seafood feast, a twist on the classic crumble and black and white pudding sausages. But Fred knows that no trip to the seaside is complete without a wee dip.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229041500 +0000" stop="20221229044500 +0000" catchup-id="69AyECSsEvOMBC3HAogB5UQQojHFmjyGLGsfUj6J"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Ellie Simmonds</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s the turn of Paralympian swimmer Ellie Simmonds to check in to the B&amp;B. Ellie won our hearts competing for Team GB during four Paralympic games and although she might have recently retired from swimming, this athlete still has a special connection to the water. The B&amp;B by the sea is the perfect place for Ellie to reconnect with the water in a different way. Sharon and the team take Ellie on a whistle stop tour of Northern Ireland’s beautiful Causeway coast. During her stay she sets sail on the Atlantic ocean, discovering all the magnificent coastline has to offer, including the site of former Kinbane Castle. She visits a potato farm with a spectacular view and gets down and dirty digging for some spuds. No time at the B&amp;B is complete without a visit to the B&amp;B kitchen, where chef Alex sets Ellie to work preparing a veggie bao bun feast and for brunch they tackle potato bread – a breakfast staple in these parts.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229044500 +0000" stop="20221229051500 +0000" catchup-id="ljIIRmnmOvdPVUol28dnuWEZQ85Zw7JgKhgkZUEI"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Ugo Monye</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the turn of rugby star and presenter Ugo Monye to check into the B&amp;B by the sea. Nestled on the wild coast of Northern Ireland, this 19th century Victorian villa is a very special place. Ugo played for both the England and Harlequins teams, but now he has retired from rugby, that hasn't stopped his adventurous spirit. He comes to the B&amp;B eager to get stuck into all the challenges the team throws at him. His first stop is seeing if he can bring in the catch of the day. The cold northern Atlantic waters are to thank for providing Northern Ireland with spectacular seafood, and on this trip they're fishing for scallops. With the fresh catch, chef Alex is hoping to put Ugo to work in the kitchen preparing braised fennel, nduja and scallop stew, and for dessert, a chocolate brownie with a creamy Guinness ice cream.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229051500 +0000" stop="20221229062000 +0000" catchup-id="KTaXeDFGDT0f1SlAVCuUxJcDD4F6dULcI_CfLel8"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229062000 +0000" stop="20221229072000 +0000" catchup-id="DFkhxCzY2iyohoKwZXlA5y3dNxvO8tAPkY9-j_XZ"><title>Signed: Celebrity MasterChef : Christmas Cook Off</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/irQ7v7kv6eBCn6V_5FOXzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Happy Mondays' Bez, athlete Iwan Thomas, pop star Josh Cuthbert and opera superstar Lesley Garrett compete for the Celebrity MasterChef Golden Whisk trophy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229072000 +0000" stop="20221229082000 +0000" catchup-id="pOxgfAbIHXj0qeGNdlvXuQMj9CcLAjXnK2-B4XX2"><title>The Polar Bear Family and Me : Summer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/FG1WRun9VpzBJWNlay8_ZA.jpg"></icon><desc>Gordon Buchanan and the team return to Svalbard in mid-June on the trail of Lyra and her cubs Miki and Luca. Gordon works with scientists to try to understand how his polar bear family are surviving the unusual arctic weather. He finds Lyra and renews his bond with her, but discovers that cub Luca is missing. Lyra is devoted to her remaining cub Miki, but his future is also uncertain. Gordon documents the intimate details of polar bear family life as he sees Lyra and Miki in their epic struggle to survive as this mother bear tries to keep her cub safe.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229082000 +0000" stop="20221229092000 +0000" catchup-id="PQLZeCGSM-IZoiS_8TTc_UjwPeEIwD9sWMnyaPnZ"><title>Jay's Yorkshire Workshop</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Jay Blades' workshop makes furniture for local heroes in Yorkshire, who this week are two sisters who help the homeless and a farmer who helped a friend in his hour of need.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229092000 +0000" stop="20221229111000 +0000" catchup-id="zOoeo8d7nb5bBfrAq88D4maEO84wGY10BkW_cWT1"><title>The Private Affairs of Bel Ami</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/RbL9GF7huoFx4kgv3xWGDA.jpg"></icon><desc>Drama set in 19th-century Paris. Adapted from the novel by Guy de Maupassant, the film tells the story of Georges Duroy, a womanising rogue whose ambitions to gain wealth and social status leave a string of broken hearts in his wake.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229111000 +0000" stop="20221229121000 +0000" catchup-id="gYpJkJ3lOKLqcghqnyxcxSCVcguGaiOMRwyavyfP"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/1Z9nbrr8IrBWkzAAQUML9w.jpg"></icon><desc>Three different projects, with three different renovation issues are tackled in Gillingham in Kent, Chaddesden in Derby and Burslem in Stoke-on-Trent. All three properties were sold at auction, and the new owners hope to make money on their investments. But for one young couple their auction buy is destined to be their first home together.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229121000 +0000" stop="20221229125500 +0000" catchup-id="uqdN0i7nBfIhWbe8oMZ12p3hy6kjjTqjhRktlbEB"><title>Bargain Hunt : Rock/Pop Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>In this jam-packed show, Bargain Hunt goes on tour around the country, looking back at some of the most memorable rock and pop buys. Natasha Raskin Sharp pays a visit to the iconic BBC Maida Vale music studios and gets the lowdown on an incredible collection of music memorabilia. She also drops in on some of our favourite experts and auctioneers to hear their hints and tips about buying or selling music-related items. And legendary rock band Happy Mondays go head to head with Pulp in the ultimate battle of the bands!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229125500 +0000" stop="20221229132500 +0000" catchup-id="xZpoknfgPPcj0r5DvJRfRPq6a7tm41JixY_isCJy"><title>Great British Railway Journeys : Deal to Margate</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/192c50Pz3pfXih58HtFmcw.jpg"></icon><desc>Michael heads to the splendid Walmer Castle, home during the 1920s to a Lord Warden of the Cinque Ports, Lord Beauchamp, whose openly homosexual lifestyle led to his exile from the country.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229132500 +0000" stop="20221229142500 +0000" catchup-id="cI3M951cGoclPMw314tGcwdGyft7XuK9r86d0NB-"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Cat Among the Pigeons</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Lucy Worsley explores Agatha Christie’s haunted, unconventional early life to discover the origins of her talent for murder – and uncovers some carefully concealed secrets.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229142500 +0000" stop="20221229161500 +0000" catchup-id="Lbl5lSfs3EGuuF939BgtZ2XUa9o-5ghrVBObrET7"><title>Evil Under the Sun</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/CFyP-IZAJR1tVDlt9_P9ag.jpg"></icon><desc>Agatha Christie's murder mystery. Detective Hercule Poirot sets out to discover the truth behind the death of a stage star at a resort hotel on an Adriatic island.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229161500 +0000" stop="20221229183000 +0000" catchup-id="SWNeGFR4ZqYDTxmzSXa_cFPU_Rim7ihL3MU54e7p"><title>Death on the Nile</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/cl-JYrAgyL242_SBx83SoA.jpg"></icon><desc>Classic whodunnit. While on a Nile steamer, detective Hercule Poirot investigates the death of a honeymooning heiress who had stolen her best friend's fiance and crossed most of the other passengers at some time in the past - giving them all a motive for murder.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229183000 +0000" stop="20221229193000 +0000" catchup-id="a6Sg-j1GUGS9qxSeAH1q1TQANExSMi7KMnYfBsNc"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s pop star versus soap star as former Pussycat Doll Kimberly Wyatt takes on Coronation Street’s Ryan Thomas in a battle of buying and selling. These two best friends bomb around the B-roads in a muscle car from Kim’s American childhood while hitting the shops around Ryan’s old stomping ground, Manchester. There are also a couple of starstruck experts, Natasha Raskin-Sharp and Serhat Ahmet, to help them find the good stuff within a £400 budget. With an antique collecting heritage in the blood of both celebrities, the pressure is on to bring home that auction winning item. Kim and Serhat pin their hopes on a strange looking sculptural item with a hidden history, while Ryan and Natasha are on a mission to find an iconic piece of Corrie memorabilia.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229193000 +0000" stop="20221229200000 +0000" catchup-id="PPJfnN8-ufc4ZkH_LpOOwqUloGCuYtS84cyy_ESN"><title>Richard Osman's Festive House of Games : Week 2: Thursday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>In this special festive edition, celebrity contestants Brian Conley, Scarlett Moffatt, Anneka Rice and Phil Wang take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being awarded the House of Games Festive Trophy on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229200000 +0000" stop="20221229203000 +0000" catchup-id="dvb0bDed5MZ5Go51BGCkDHRGp76FRNQtxSvg9Jdf"><title>Only Connect Special : Happy Hour: Alesmen v Cosmopolitans</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Victoria Coren Mitchell is back in the host's chair for a one-off special of Only Connect, the series where knowledge will only take you so far. Patience and lateral thinking are also vital. Two favourite teams from previous series return for a very special and chilly episode of Only Connect. The Nordiphiles and Apres Skiers compete to draw the connections between things which, at first glance, seem utterly random. So join Victoria if you want to know what connects Just-Williams, Tracy-T, Vanilla Van Winkle and O'Shea Cube.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229203000 +0000" stop="20221229210000 +0000" catchup-id="TdrB7BdIvwKP5v6ArPgAuHB0lQ5ANWe6PyjyUIG_"><title>Christmas University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>Two of the four highest-scoring winning teams from the heats return to play the second of this year’s semi-finals. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229210000 +0000" stop="20221229215500 +0000" catchup-id="auOup68ubZkvKq43oAqic88p1O6sTR9vScvpEG7T"><title>Marie Antoinette : The Slap</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/H2gpW2YCIsmq4QcGWPe6dw.jpg"></icon><desc>Marie Antoinette is just a teenager when she’s forced to leave Vienna to marry the Dauphin, the heir to the French throne. She must produce a Bourbon heir to secure the alliance between France and Austria, but she is as unprepared for her job as her awkward teenage husband. How will this free spirit react to Versailles, with its complex rules of etiquette?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229215500 +0000" stop="20221229225500 +0000" catchup-id="vxQioujrXPWzT7BSgsVOoV1yRc-jKyG6B5kzVnoO"><title>Madonna at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>A look back at a selection of magical Madonna moments on various BBC shows, from her first Top of the Pops appearance with Holiday in 1984 right up to the present day. This collection covers Madonna's journey from Material Girl to Queen of Pop and captures how over the years her ability to combine charisma, controversy and classic pop tunes has made her the female icon of her times and a true global superstar.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221229225500 +0000" stop="20221230003500 +0000" catchup-id="1Eg-bStlA-EuvIvnrsPWIhX4VpEY3bJft_f572EG"><title>Desperately Seeking Susan</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/lsIL9yfkE86cMYFLyJMIKg.jpg"></icon><desc>Offbeat romantic comedy. A bored suburban housewife becomes obsessed with a rebellious freewheeler whom she stumbles across in a series of ads in the personal columns from someone who is 'desperately seeking Susan'. But Susan is in big trouble, and matters are further complicated when the housewife is mistaken for her and drawn into a bizarre world</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230003500 +0000" stop="20221230023000 +0000" catchup-id="FnuAC-UNzsnew8iiA4k-QWq084DfdExAr_MVeTXF"><title>Madonna: Truth or Dare</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/vel9DnlOVgKucWXroEyAZw.jpg"></icon><desc>A candid, behind-the-scenes portrait of the superstar on the 1990 Blonde Ambition tour. Madonna has spent her career cleverly manipulating the meanings of public and private, and this purportedly warts-and-all film takes this even further. Includes concert performances of hits including Express Yourself, Holiday, Vogue and Like a Virgin - the latter nearly getting the singer arrested for obscene behaviour</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230023000 +0000" stop="20221230030000 +0000" catchup-id="_-iNq_mUc-5gwRbjee1wYI-pASoEyTPlPmkrk__L"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Gloria Hunniford</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Gloria Hunniford left Northern Ireland to pursue her career, but this stay is an opportunity for her to reconnect with her roots and reminisce.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230030000 +0000" stop="20221230033000 +0000" catchup-id="tv4FKVCb2RvoOGHF1qmR8shBMfb6riWVE7bTfk8X"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Larry Lamb</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Coming to stay at the B&amp;B is prolific actor and Gavin and Stacey star Larry Lamb. Larry is no stranger to Northern Ireland, but the B&amp;B team make sure to take Larry on a whistlestop adventure, all in the name of a day’s work at the B&amp;B. During Larry’s stay he meets a special Japanese herd who help provide the star ingredient for the evening meal: a twist on the classic beef wellington with a Northern Irish wagyu steak, served with smoked mash and red cabbage. And while most guests start their morning at the B&amp;B with a challenge, Sharon and driver Rory bring Larry to a local spot he’s never visited before - the picturesque seaside town of Ballycastle, which has a special place in driver Rory’s heart. Before checking out, chef Alex takes Larry under his wing, baking a unique take on a Northern Irish soda bread with bacon and eggs. It's the perfect end to Larry’s stay.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230033000 +0000" stop="20221230040000 +0000" catchup-id="x9ftFnL9Nd_dtJemTSBS8N2xvrY1ut8bLqFvOVWV"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Cerys Matthews</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Checking in to the B&amp;B is Welsh musician, author and radio host Cerys Matthews. Cerys may have travelled the world with her music, but this is her first visit to Northern Ireland’s Causeway Coast, as well as a special B&amp;B by the sea. Cerys and chef Alex visit a local farm with a passion for turning rapeseed flowers into delicious flavoured oils. They meet Richard, a sixth generation farmer, and his wife Leona to learn more about their home-grown rapeseed oil. Cerys and Alex can’t help but take some of the flavoured oils back to the B&amp;B to match with the evening meal. Knowing Cerys’ love of cooking and Japanese flavours, chef Alex asks her to assist in preparing the B&amp;B dinner. They make a dish of miso baked aubergines with a mixed bean salad, as well as a light and airy souffle cheesecake, the perfect end to the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230040000 +0000" stop="20221230043000 +0000" catchup-id="IGXnG0IciT50J4SMHkWmfS9Pu6Jwz6G66clalbQ5"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Linford Christie</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Britain’s fastest ever sprinter, Linford Christie, checks in the B&amp;B hoping to make quick work of the daily tasks. He’s taking a break from his coaching to reflect on his career, as well as embracing the itinerary the B&amp;B team have set for the sporting legend. Whilst at the B&amp;B, Linford discovers a true taste of Northern Ireland’s coast – a local honey flavoured with the wildflowers that decorate this spectacular coastline. With the help of the resident chef Alex, they create an epic feast of spiced spatchcocked chicken and strawberry trifle, all sweetened up with this local delicacy. Linford has only recently learned to swim, and the B&amp;B team know there’s no fresher dip that jumping into waters off Northern Ireland’s coast. Sharon takes Linford open-water swimming, a truly memorable experience for any newbie swimmer. And before Linford checks out, he takes another crack in the kitchen, whipping up some fluffy pancakes for the B&amp;B brunch.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230043000 +0000" stop="20221230050000 +0000" catchup-id="S0b550hE1Q87CwCjpHs9zYPiMOept2RdMrlUbWdo"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Debbie McGee</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Television, stage and radio star Debbie McGee checks in to the B&amp;B hoping to bring some magic to her stay. During Debbie’s fifty plus years in showbiz, she’s achieved a myriad of things, not least becoming the first female member of the magic circle in the 90s. But during Debbie’s stay at the B&amp;B, she experiences a number of firsts, including smoking fish and glass blowing with an unusual ingredient. Her first stop on her Northern Irish adventure is the local smokehouse whose owner Ruairidh Morrison has mastered the art of hot and cold smoking local salmon to perfection. Ruairidh has also experimented with smoked black pepper which adds a kick to the B&amp;B dessert. Debbie found a love of the kitchen cooking for her late husband Paul Daniels, so fits right at home with chef Alex in the B&amp;B kitchen. Here they whip up a seafood feast and a sweet treat incorporating the locally smoked black pepper.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230050000 +0000" stop="20221230063000 +0000" catchup-id="iOPA7RNHFiIahng3neboU8cz6ZwPzQ_IwGyi8DTF"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230063000 +0000" stop="20221230073000 +0000" catchup-id="wXHNvOU5Fy7MrZZu-PjIMHOz6obwRgLu_BdUwlhA"><title>Signed: My Life at Christmas with Sally Phillips : Shirley Ballas</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Sally Phillips visits the home of Strictly Come Dancing head judge Shirley Ballas to hear how Christmas has marked her journey from her childhood in the Wirral to huge acclaim across the world as a professional dance champion. Shirley shares her story of hard work, passion and loss - with one particularly tragic Christmas at its heart.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230073000 +0000" stop="20221230083000 +0000" catchup-id="4Fotk6sT7ZnIm-3OArb1WNXurtTt-5jhkmDaEfNr"><title>The Polar Bear Family and Me : Autumn</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Xb_ZO2xPv65u-e3W_GW03w.jpg"></icon><desc>Gordon Buchanan and the team return to Svalbard in September on the trail of Lyra and her cub Miki. They have been away for six weeks and don't know if either bear is still alive. Lyra's collar hasn't sent a signal for a month - finding her this time will be a huge challenge. But Gordon does find her, and Miki is also alive. Times are tough, though. Lyra is very thin and has been reduced to eating moss and seaweed.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230083000 +0000" stop="20221230093000 +0000" catchup-id="0Y920vB5eNZ0ZGtgxBgn5JrDzSiQiKIO9ujyJy3c"><title>Jay's Yorkshire Workshop</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Jay Blades' workshop makes furniture for local heroes in Yorkshire. This week, a man who set up a men's mental health charity and a youth worker who turns people's lives around.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230093000 +0000" stop="20221230111500 +0000" catchup-id="AYAaOcBkah73Pjt1Zm-9Fxhn_43bPkZaNsRqoaFK"><title>D-Day the Sixth of June</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-5tFg444LPJXDHnVlTJIFw.jpg"></icon><desc>Panoramic account of the Normandy invasion during World War II, focusing on a love triangle that develops in the days leading up to the assault. An American officer, assigned to London and desperate for combat honours, meets a woman whose fiance is fighting in Africa. The two fall deeply in love, but the fiance's return to England forces them to set aside their romance</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230111500 +0000" stop="20221230121500 +0000" catchup-id="vzJrQ9F9ziki0f75vXEOQMCspEkqbHgd8-TFyrln"><title>Homes Under the Hammer</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/sYFxGdR8cnf1iLwe_UEYsA.jpg"></icon><desc>A first-time property investor takes on a garden-level flat in London's Crystal Palace, Dion meets a lorry driver who is renovating a mid-terrace house in Stoke-on-Trent, and in Strood in Kent, a navy reservist transforms a three-storey townhouse into a stylish holiday let. All three properties were sold at auction, and all threw up a few trials and tribulations for their new owners.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230121500 +0000" stop="20221230130000 +0000" catchup-id="SgCXCqfHYjpC0OuXQpLZBSf4DPf_iRJyr3qJitHX"><title>Bargain Hunt : Glass Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>This special episode shines a light on all things glass! Eric Knowles takes a tour across the UK looking at some of the most memorable glass items bought by our reds and blues, and he shares his tips when it comes to buying and selling glass. Eric also tries his hand at glass cutting, Natasha Raskin Sharp blows some glass, and Roo Irvine discusses her passion for glass with Charlie Ross.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230130000 +0000" stop="20221230133000 +0000" catchup-id="sMW8TqLCqOolCq-iohppvlCYo-8rUO_Efcy8GHk0"><title>Great British Railway Journeys : Herne Bay to Leeds Castle, Kent</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/192c50Pz3pfXih58HtFmcw.jpg"></icon><desc>Armed with his interwar copy of Bradshaw’s Guide to the Railways, Michael reaches the Kent seaside resort of Herne Bay, where he learns about a pioneering aviatrix who began her working life as a typist in Hull but whose epic achievements made her an international celebrity. Michael takes the train five miles west along the coast before heading offshore into the entrance to the Thames Estuary. He is amazed by seven enormous steel sea forts, which loom out of the water 90 feet above the seabed. The engineering involved in constructing these impressive structures is awe-inspiring, as is their role in protecting the nation from enemy bombing during the Second World War. In the seaside town of Whitstable, Michael tucks into its famous staple, oysters. He then crosses the North Downs to Lenham, from which he visits Leeds Castle, the 'loveliest castle in the world' and home between the wars to the visionary Lady Olive Bailey.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230133000 +0000" stop="20221230143000 +0000" catchup-id="zJF5xuwNilSroHyEvb9CiUpa53XHwCjxqeksrHc-"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Destination Unknown</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>On the evening of 3 December 1926, Agatha Christie left her home in Sunningdale, Berkshire, in her Morris Cowley. The next morning, the car was found abandoned, balanced precariously on the edge of a quarry. Ten days later, Agatha was discovered in a hotel in Harrogate, claiming to have lost her memory. Lucy Worsley delves into this traumatic watershed moment in Agatha's life. She visits the key locations, from the chalk pit where Agatha crashed her car to Abney Hall, the grand house where she took refuge (and which would inspire several of her books). Lucy reveals connections between Agatha's real-life experiences and her novels, and uncovers new evidence about Agatha's mental health and the cutting-edge psychiatric treatment she went on to receive.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230143000 +0000" stop="20221230162500 +0000" catchup-id="BQI-FtlFIVCJaZcoNf4KGPx6q0NXsLIaGFZOd5Be"><title>Witness for the Prosecution</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/3eJyc4z8rihxvnSQjHLVrQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Classic courtroom drama about a the trial of a married man accused of murdering a rich widow, a case that proves to be full of unexpected twists and turns. His defence is conducted by a veteran barrister, tempted out of retirement by the intriguing case. Based on the Agatha Christie book</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230162500 +0000" stop="20221230183000 +0000" catchup-id="yPL04VAWawuMtT1uEvFb3Pkxxu4ImzX7Y3SMUi-k"><title>Murder on the Orient Express</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/0c9fnk1drIYAO08-XVFigw.jpg"></icon><desc>All-star adaptation of Agatha Christie's novel set on the Orient Express. A financier travelling from Istanbul to Paris is found dead, stabbed a dozen times, and it is up to celebrated Belgian detective Hercule Poirot to solve the crime. He painstakingly interviews those in the same railway car and through an elaborate re-creation aims to discover just who carried out the deed.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230183000 +0000" stop="20221230193000 +0000" catchup-id="jINbzT4Z7DzV_6g-9mOmEAYqzVKm0jaGhdIIg4Fi"><title>The Year in Music at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>A chance to look back at an amazing 12 months of live music at the BBC. Lauren Laverne leads us through a year of unforgettable performances – from the 6 Music Festival to Glastonbury, Radio 1’s Big Weekend to Later... and featuring some of the world’s biggest artists as well as some exciting new talent.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230193000 +0000" stop="20221230200000 +0000" catchup-id="kFKFK770d4qfmxTYjXPizsumBv3-N0-Zem1T26ov"><title>Richard Osman's Festive House of Games : Week 2: Friday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>In this special festive edition, celebrity contestants Brian Conley, Scarlett Moffatt, Anneka Rice and Phil Wang take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being awarded the House of Games Festive Trophy on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games fondue set?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230200000 +0000" stop="20221230203000 +0000" catchup-id="OiWYfx7o1ARdTpkiTjenByNGOgm19-mn47K3_w0_"><title>Only Connect : North and South: Scunthorpe Scholars v Oxonians</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Victoria Coren Mitchell is back in the host's chair for a one-off special of Only Connect: the series where knowledge will only take you so far. Patience and lateral thinking are also vital. Two favourite teams from previous series - one from the north and one from the south - return for a very special episode with a geographical flavour. They compete to draw together the connections between things which, at first glance, seem utterly random. So join Victoria Coren Mitchell if you want to know what connects Hong Kong and La Quiaca, Rock of Gibraltar and Mangawha, Jakarta and Bogota [almost] and North Pole and South Pole.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230203000 +0000" stop="20221230210000 +0000" catchup-id="p0YD-nTOLyBbmYBNqr_K5p3iJdd5xQ2ND0WfU5oK"><title>Christmas University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s the grand final of the Christmas competition, in which teams of notable former students compete on behalf of their alma maters. Only two alumni teams remain: who will take the series title? Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230210000 +0000" stop="20221230224500 +0000" catchup-id="lCyg1Mba2pyoutpDSbhBoU1M2OGKxVu-BcWMHnSj"><title>My Old School</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/mBY0v_5n-ecNk-S_o-dnzg.jpg"></icon><desc>The story of Scotland's most notorious impostor. A 16-year-old boy is the new kid at school and becomes a model pupil - until he is unmasked.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230224500 +0000" stop="20221230234500 +0000" catchup-id="cPxTdMsQfRSUhIFdcW8CN_wcg4TU6viBum6c-B-q"><title>Miriam Margolyes: Australia Unmasked</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>On the first leg of her adventure, Miriam Margolyes is confronted with the complexities of Tasmania’s rich history. She meets those still fighting for a 'fair go'.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221230234500 +0000" stop="20221231003000 +0000" catchup-id="mhHrkVKdNlMEa24jm3mTSGMX2T79QXTIvM5yI2S0"><title>Frankie Boyle's 2022 New World Order : 2022</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Yt8fAoVbMGXYLN5kURdE1w.jpg"></icon><desc>Frankie Boyle returns with an end of year special where, with the help guests Sophie Duker, Miles Jupp, Jamali Maddix and Kiri Pritchard-McLean, he dissects the unsettling year that was 2022. The show features Frankie at his satirical best with stand-up, review and discussion – all in an attempt to make sense of the last 12 months.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231003000 +0000" stop="20221231022000 +0000" catchup-id="kNxWeNcZiLMI8wpJ6d1z-ptWkycVOV-o6BHvL9iH"><title>Signed: Film: 1917</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/VVnh2gNCzMIdXtOcD7lImA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231022000 +0000" stop="20221231032000 +0000" catchup-id="OcHW97bQUh1kQHy3xAYvoby8W6n1PBKfb0I_wVUe"><title>Signed: Simon Schama's History of Now : The Price of Plenty</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>After the Second World War, there were deep divisions in America about how to move forward. Should it be a social democracy, in which a benevolent state would look after its most vulnerable citizens? Or should it put its faith in individual enterprise and the free market to provide plenty for all? Simon Schama examines how the filmmaker Charlie Chaplin and author Ayn Rand created radically different visions of how this new postwar world should work, and how writers such as Rachel Carson drew attention to the damage being inflicted on the natural world. He talks to author Margaret Atwood about how Carson inspired her own work and to photographer Edward Burtynsky about his photographic projects to document haunting images of the pursuit of consumerism.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231032000 +0000" stop="20221231035000 +0000" catchup-id="EdLbC3yUsrEAdT8kxaB6YpmQR0KR6GRYA08jES9l"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Si King</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Proud Geordie biker Si King is taking a break from his travels around the world to check into the B&amp;B by the sea. Si is well known for his part in TV cooking duo The Hairy Bikers, but this time he's riding solo, mucking in at the B&amp;B. Whilst Si is keen to help in the kitchen, first he is sent on a mission to find the perfect pairing beer for the B&amp;B dinner. Hoping to support the local community in everything they do, Sharon organises for Si to visit the Lacada Brewery - a community-led project that has mastered the art of the perfect brew. With the local flavourful tipple, Si assists chef Alex in the kitchen creating a seafood feast to celebrate the bountiful catch from Northern Ireland's coast. Before Si checks out, the team take him to meet a group of local anglers hoping to bring in the catch of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231035000 +0000" stop="20221231042000 +0000" catchup-id="4C-pQmYLlxjUkDSvIykWtgBmc8RH7DprLi_Udyke"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Neil Ruddock</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the turn of football legend Neil 'Razor' Ruddock to check into the B&amp;B. Razor retired from the beautiful game 20 years ago, but he hasn't succumbed to the quiet life just yet. Razor's been keeping himself busy regularly hosting talks and appearing on our TV screens, and he brings that attitude with him to the B&amp;B. Sharon and Alex want to give Razor the opportunity to learn more about the local produce, so Alex takes him to Glenarm Castle's estate to meet their herd of Shorthorn cattle. Then, they use Shorthorn ribs to create a delicious dinner for the whole B&amp;B team. Knowing Razor might need to brush up on his Northern Irish history, Sharon brings him to Londonderry for a little lesson.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231042000 +0000" stop="20221231045000 +0000" catchup-id="D3pqQGsTpGmtj-QVRS5xHz_1vYB68xdwERXnkjMy"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Nina Wadia</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Actress and comedian Nina Wadia checks into the B&amp;B. Nina was brought up near the coast in Hong Kong and has fond recollections of her time by the water, so her stay at the B&amp;B is a chance to reminisce on her favourite memories of the seaside. Luckily, the B&amp;B team believe there's no better way to get to know the local area than setting sail to witness the beautiful coastline. But Nina doesn't get to relax, she's put to work bringing in the catch of the day - lobster. And all that hard graft can't go to waste, because she's taught by chef Alex how to cook a decadent lobster linguine with wild garlic to celebrate the fresh catch. Day two brings more new experiences for Nina - a turn making chocolate truffles with the local chocolatier. If she can resist eating them, they'll be the perfect treat to end her stay at the B&amp;B.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231045000 +0000" stop="20221231052000 +0000" catchup-id="5lL5VE6nRK5thRUzmV-XlSqFcYhvMqgvjwqsvEgZ"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Adam Woodyatt</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It's the turn of actor Adam Woodyatt to check into the B&amp;B. Adam has recently taken a break from his famous role as Ian Beale in long-running soap EastEnders, so for this trip, he is swapping London's East End for Northern Ireland's spectacular Causeway Coast. For dinner, Alex needs Adam's help to prepare an Indian-inspired feast, but they're still missing a few key ingredients. Luckily Sharon knows a local farm that might be able to help. Chef Alex makes use of Adam's newfound passion for cooking, preparing an Indian spiced goat curry with yogurt flat breads, followed by a rhubarb fool with a chai tea-infused custard: a perfect way to toast Adam's first day exploring the Causeway Coast. After a good night's sleep, Sharon decides the best wake up call for Adam is a workout on the beach. Accompanied by some local fitness enthusiasts, he's put through his paces with a special fitness session, trying to keep up with the rest of the B&amp;B team.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231052000 +0000" stop="20221231055000 +0000" catchup-id="j1re7ERpZpZWKJBbbKU0G418tJ3WQ_oaUxLglXkO"><title>B&amp;B By the Sea : Richard Blackwood</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hollyoaks star and comedian Richard Blackwood is checking into the B&amp;B. Richard decided at a young age that he was destined for a life in the spotlight, but during his stay, is taking a break from stardom to muck in with the B&amp;B team. The team task Richard with looking after the star ingredient for the B&amp;B shopping list - making some chorizo for a French-inspired supper. The B&amp;B's resident chef Alex takes him to meet a local pig farmer to help Richard in his mission. Whilst staying at the B&amp;B, all guests test their cooking skills in the kitchen, helping to prepare the evening meal. Chef Alex takes Richard under his wing to prepare a cassoulet celebrating the locally made chorizo and a sea buckthorn tart inspired by Northern Ireland's coastline. Day two, and Sharon has a special task in mind for Richard. He might be known for his sharp wit, but Sharon wants him to sharpen his skills working with a local artisan producer.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231055000 +0000" stop="20221231062000 +0000" catchup-id="WjVOdp4ivzmMztRkRjLEQxdGybW-XMi83WoZh2N_"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231062000 +0000" stop="20221231071500 +0000" catchup-id="4OlZNgAAZNeSZx9YEb4dqR09svG7HMhTxS4WAX71"><title>Heaven Made</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The Benedictine nuns of Kylemore Abbey on the west coast of Ireland embark on a new business venture, embracing the ancient craft of beekeeping to produce honey with a special flavour unique to the abbey. For centuries, the traditional clothing worn by monks has been a black habit. At Quarr Abbey on the Isle of Wight, Brother Matthew, a monk in training, receives his very first habit, created by seamstress Julia, a lay person at the abbey. At St Augustine’s Abbey in Chilworth, Surrey, Father John is preparing to leave the sanctuary of the abbey to source ingredients for his latest beauty product, a scented lip balm.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231071500 +0000" stop="20221231081500 +0000" catchup-id="RhhPNVuyp7NpKM0X-upUh5GSItgp_zfHFZHR-QCF"><title>A Wild Year : The Pembrokeshire Coast</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/tX7hd_yQ5UTqabeJ_ngZnw.jpg"></icon><desc>In the far south west corner of Wales lies Pembrokeshire's wild and rugged coast. Twisting and turning along the edge of the Atlantic, life on this ancient coastline is defined by the rhythm of the seasons and the power of the sea. Fishing these fertile waters has long been a tradition here. Every day, local fisherman Jono Voyce heads out from Solva harbour into St Brides Bay to fish for the lobster and crab he supplies to these coastal communities. With the arrival of spring, he will soon be busier than ever, providing for thousands of visitors who flock to this coast every summer for a taste of the sea. By July, beaches are the playground for countless visitors. But their activity depends on the tides. Tides give a predictable rhythm to life on the coast. In Pembrokeshire, where the water level rises as much as 30 feet a day, they are some of the highest in the world.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231081500 +0000" stop="20221231091500 +0000" catchup-id="ToV3OyYCZM5tW7UAF--EXrnk07D2TH3bKLhGbVGO"><title>Jay's Yorkshire Workshop</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>This week, Jay and his workshop make furniture for a veteran who set up a charity to help other ex-forces members and a couple who have fostered 130 children.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231091500 +0000" stop="20221231101500 +0000" catchup-id="bcZHMwMLgqfAYe8VLNcPBflaP7hQvgk7aSXQLz4O"><title>Agatha Christie: Lucy Worsley on the Mystery Queen : Unfinished Portrait</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Lucy Worsley examines Agatha Christie’s later life and discovers how, amid the turbulent social and political change of the 1930s and 40s, newfound personal happiness ushered in a golden age for her writing. In 1930, recovering from a personal crisis, Agatha Christie fell in love with and married Max Mallowan. This relationship, and the security it brought, saw Agatha enter the most prolific and successful chapter of her career. This would be the period in which she penned some of her most famous and enduring bestsellers, including Murder on the Orient Express. Lucy follows in Agatha’s footsteps to discover the roots of these works and explores how, in later life, Agatha achieved global celebrity but remained very much the anonymous observer, hiding in plain sight.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231101500 +0000" stop="20221231122000 +0000" catchup-id="OYAmo0Fb4eMR37Tci-qGMnI0GeIS7hSv_NJN8QB-"><title>Shadowlands</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/yoX3AN32INsBxouDWcXsMw.jpg"></icon><desc>Romantic drama. CS Lewis, Oxford don and well-known children's author, appears to be content with his quiet academic life. Then he agrees to meet American poet Joy Gresham, whose forthright personality seems to be at odds with Lewis's unadventurous routine. But over the course of a Christmas spent together, his feelings begin to change.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231122000 +0000" stop="20221231130500 +0000" catchup-id="_kn2ARDqPUhHtGiwPZAIeX25yGCi5eDagY0WeUAG"><title>Talking Pictures : Anthony Hopkins</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231130500 +0000" stop="20221231151000 +0000" catchup-id="bElMxIeqBCeCUYMXwHXm6OA_0yo11VB23F2SgjxQ"><title>The Remains of the Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/ZPbD34ByXu3dPQmjLONV-A.jpg"></icon><desc>Mr Stevens is butler to Lord Darlington, who in the years leading up to the Second World War had great sympathy with Germany and hoped to retain the peace between Britain and the Nazis. Overseeing the running of the great house, Stevens is joined by housekeeper Miss Kenton. In postwar Britain, Stevens gets a letter from Miss Kenton and decides to seek her out. From the Booker Prize-winning novel by Kazuo Ishiguro.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231151000 +0000" stop="20221231173500 +0000" catchup-id="oJ3mMEWiH_ojpVPdmzgK1IbvMASB-iB2Qtl-zxAH"><title>West Side Story</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/hcR3CU8fstYjSAOGkZb7XQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Multi-Oscar-winning screen version of Leonard Bernstein's vibrant Broadway musical about the love between a boy and girl from rival New York gangs. Romeo and Juliet is transposed to the Hell's Kitchen area of New York City during the 1950s. Bernstein's music, Stephen Sondheim's lyrics and Jerome Robbins's choreography combine to make this a classic Hollywood musical. Songs include Tonight, Somewhere and Maria</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231173500 +0000" stop="20221231194500 +0000" catchup-id="LQv1oClTrHyy5fgR_5tJL4NeLNtnPKbLakqlB-Um"><title>Stephen Sondheim's Old Friends</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>On 3 May 2022, Cameron Mackintosh invited many of Stephen Sondheim's old friends to join him in London's West End for a thrilling, joyously staged production. He had specially devised it to celebrate Stephen's extraordinary talents as a composer and lyricist. Featuring an all-star cast including Michael Ball, Helena Bonham Carter, Rob Brydon, Petula Clark, Anna-Jane Casey, Rosalie Craig, Janie Dee, Judi Dench, Daniel Evans, Maria Friedman, Haydn Gwynne, Bonnie Langford, Damian Lewis and Julia McKenzie.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231194500 +0000" stop="20221231201500 +0000" catchup-id="L2jLQhcEIJM-oCSOhH6J_Fixu3Asu3AUnPjB_Ppp"><title>Only Connect : Education: Clareites v Beaks</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Victoria Coren Mitchell hosts the series where knowledge will only take you so far. Patience and lateral thinking are also vital. In this episode, two former teams with a connection to education return for a special. They compete to draw together the connections between things which at first glance, seem utterly random. So join Victoria Coren Mitchell if you want to know what connects Called strikeout, Ya, There exists and Pilcrow.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231201500 +0000" stop="20221231211500 +0000" catchup-id="3ioY3ta8gXyifNR5cEQSlP-33Zt0r3BNJ7f950Ai"><title>Mortimer &amp; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing : Christmas 2022</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/86JsBRvh5ni1jRhhVkpuYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Whitehouse takes Bob Mortimer on the ultimate fishing adventure to the magical country of Norway, where the locals say that cod is God and fishing takes precedence over almost everything else. This is Paul's type of Christmas break, and it will be the first time they have fished together beyond the UK and Ireland. They travel to Vesteralen and the Lofoten Islands in the Arctic Circle, a chain of islands made up of majestic snow-topped mountains, deep fjords, long, surf-swept beaches and small, historic fishing villages. They must face a legendary tidal whirlpool, the maelstrom, in their attempt to catch the 'cheetahs of the water', coalfish.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231211500 +0000" stop="20221231220000 +0000" catchup-id="O_0_NWCA0iRnvpdlmHmXIsbiPLNAdxbmcBkB5mOn"><title>The Morecambe &amp; Wise Show : 1970: The Lost Tape</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>As a Christmas treat for comedy fans, this is a complete episode of The Morecambe and Wise Show that had been considered lost for over 50 years. Eric's son Gary Morecambe discovered the programme in an unmarked film can in 2020, and now it has been lovely restored and can be enjoyed in full for the first time since being broadcast on 8 October 1970. The show, written by the legendary Eddie Braben, was episode 1 of Eric and Ernie's first series to appear on BBC1, and was originally watched by over 14 million viewers. As well as some classic sketches from Eric and Ernie, the show also features songs and music from Paul Anka, Patricia Lambert, Kenny Ball and his Jazzmen, and the boys themselves rounding things off with a burst of Bring Me Sunshine.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231220000 +0000" stop="20221231233000 +0000" catchup-id="Ip1TlM9hChWr_s6vpuzmfH5AKowCs3FhnlPNk_xc"><title>Match of the Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Rh4xXqm21taLSf7Ct76QlA.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of Saturday’s Premier League fixtures, which include leaders Arsenal visiting Brighton as they bid to enter 2023 still on top of the table. Reigning champions Manchester City host Everton, while a resurgent Newcastle United meet Leeds in what promises to be an entertaining clash at St James’ Park. Other games include Manchester United’s trip to Molineux to face Wolves, Bournemouth welcoming Crystal Palace and Southampton travelling to the capital to play Fulham.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20221231233000 +0000" stop="20230101013500 +0000" catchup-id="tIcxMcITeL6PxecOR6vpYJQWOOsz3GrPRUOkrlMd"><title>Jools' Annual Hootenanny</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Jools Holland hosts his annual hootenanny, which sees him and his Rhythm and Blues Orchestra bring in 2023 with a host of musical guests with songs from this year and across the decades for the ultimate New Year’s Eve party.   Following two years of a more intimate version of the show, this year the Hootenanny returns to a full cast of guests and an invited audience for the 30th year of the show. Feautring George Ezra, Self Esteem, Cat Burns, Andy Fairweather Low, Roland Gift, Gabrielle, The Real Thing, and Rachael and Vilray, as well as the return of Ruby Turner and the Pipes and Drums of the 1st Battalion Scots Guards.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101013500 +0000" stop="20230101030000 +0000" catchup-id="KkdyJ8JEcKmquUTfEPCJrKP6ePntsxg6LXHU4AWO"><title>Alan Partridge: Alpha Papa</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/K2oF-IK_WKUnX3-YyPtNWA.jpg"></icon><desc>To save his own job, Alan gets radio colleague Pat laid off, but when the man returns to the relaunched station with a shotgun and a siege ensues, Alan is given the high-profile role of go-between, trying to appease both the hostage taker and armed police. So lots of people have Alan in their sights. Hit big screen spin-off for the self-obsessed former TV 'personality', from BBC Films.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101030000 +0000" stop="20230101040000 +0000" catchup-id="ohxMD9vP6vLSy-p0p8xR2hmXh_ByLmTZdOx_LInY"><title>Britpop at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In the mid-90s, Britpop stamped its presence onto the British music scene and made boys wearing eyeliner cool again. What better reason to raid the BBC archives for a rich treasure trove of the joy and the time that was Britpop? Featuring the girls (Elastica, Sleeper) and the boys (Suede, Menswear) and many of the other bright young things that contributed to five years of Cool Britannia, Blur v Oasis and Camden being the centre of the universe. Britpop at the BBC reminds us all why we were all so proud to be British again in the 1990s.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101040000 +0000" stop="20230101061500 +0000" catchup-id="JxA90PFq6U0zVnyvWI-NXIMnqnC6VKFjfjHXzNzP"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101061500 +0000" stop="20230101071000 +0000" catchup-id="0idPhomVZnygRSp3snez9XaNAs8b1TpMTndUFa-o"><title>Countryfile : Hogmanay and New Year Traditions</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101071000 +0000" stop="20230101081000 +0000" catchup-id="nnDUVyK0y5MJRBJmbSTkyMcP3HNTY1d4GqNHB9JS"><title>A Wild Year : The Fens</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/uil3r2tmKaakLLx7pz4Afw.jpg"></icon><desc>Hidden away in the most easterly part of the British Isles are the Fens of East Anglia, a landscape of big skies and distant horizons, wild wetlands and fertile farmland. Water has always been the driving force here - its ebb and flow has shaped the fens for thousands of years. The ancient wetlands covered hundreds of square miles and overflowed with wildlife. Today, well over 90% has gone, drained over the centuries and converted into farmland. Yet despite these changes, it is still possible to glimpse the richness of those wetlands. Every winter, thousands of migrating whooper swans return to the flooded pastures of the Ouse washes from their Arctic breeding grounds. Here, they join thousands of other waterfowl in one of Britain's greatest wildlife gatherings. On the Welney Wetlands, spring sees 'mad' march hares boxing over mates. It was once thought these bouts were male hares boxing for dominance, but it is often the females throwing the punches to fend off the attentions</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101081000 +0000" stop="20230101084000 +0000" catchup-id="EnMnjfp5ZmM9NtWFHDAJWlAJceQ2K68kVCeG2r32"><title>Weatherman Walking : Dinefwr Park &amp; Sully</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Derek Brockway is on ranger duties at a country estate in Carmarthenshire, exploring Dinefwr Park's 800 acres of magical medieval landscape and getting up close and personal with a very rare cattle breed. In the Vale of Glamorgan, Derek is joined by one of the nation's favourite Olympians, Colin Jackson. Together, they explore a five-mile coastal route that has it all: dinosaur footprints, WW2 gun battery remains, the site of a major communication breakthrough and an iconic Victorian pier.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101084000 +0000" stop="20230101101500 +0000" catchup-id="Vu3eIf-fiwqZ-g3lGPHRNyxzu9aI9pZA2badqMLz"><title>Saturday Kitchen New Year Best Bites</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/RP_5PKqX4rIMk-YZUlBkXg.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt takes a look back at some of his favourite recipes and best moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101101500 +0000" stop="20230101124500 +0000" catchup-id="4bTLm74mXxIxEureQwGvv_oG-s2koYTV5EfNLi9N"><title>New Year's Day Concert Live from Vienna</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra perform the 2023 New Year's Day concert from the Golden Hall of the Musikverein in Vienna. Franz Welser-Möst conducts the orchestra in the traditional feast of waltzes and polkas composed by the Strauss family and their contemporaries, culminating in the timeless By the Beautiful Blue Danube and Radetzky March.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101124500 +0000" stop="20230101164000 +0000" catchup-id="PF_pZyKQ32YAFSlkRwGL5-u301NZAw0eefNXeStI"><title>Cleopatra</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/55LI0mhIgwtDe7DHuKWcyA.jpg"></icon><desc>Oscar-winning epic of the legendary Queen of the Nile and her two great loves, Julius Caesar and Mark Antony. Caesar arrives in Egypt in 48 BC to settle the dispute between Ptolemy and his sister, Cleopatra, who is denied her rightful power. Caesar reinstates Cleopatra as sole ruler and returns with her in triumph to Rome. But her passionate affair with Mark Antony leads to scandal, deadly political plots and tragedy.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101164000 +0000" stop="20230101164500 +0000" catchup-id="Lf_K30dQgRhJ_MBPz4NWubOmCWIFIZG7uq9CBCLp"><title>Signed: The Archbishop of Canterbury's New Year Message</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The archbishop of Canterbury, the Most Rev Justin Welby, reflects on the challenges facing the care system and offers a hopeful vision of society for the new year.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101164500 +0000" stop="20230101183000 +0000" catchup-id="iKJGY4C2DHaddNt02Eh3y7SndWpGVKbcZ-absMXf"><title>Planet of the Apes</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Mgeca7IWXnkGDxA4ecNsZg.jpg"></icon><desc>Classic sci-fi story about an exploratory mission which goes drastically wrong, sending a group of astronauts 2,000 years into the future. When they crash-land, they find themselves on a planet where humans live like Neanderthals, controlled and conditioned by a super-intelligent race of apes. The film awed cinema audiences upon its release and won an Oscar for John Chambers's stunning make-up effects</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101183000 +0000" stop="20230101190000 +0000" catchup-id="pSgn5M7AB-4wtqC6KCPn5SXrmiBFQxylsJiYClyO"><title>Only Connect : The Birds and the Bees: Birdwatchers v Beekeepers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Victoria Coren Mitchell is back in the host's chair for a one-off special of Only Connect, the series where knowledge will only take you so far. Patience and lateral thinking are also vital. Two favourite teams from previous series - the Birdwatchers and the Beekeepers - return for a very special episode. They compete to draw together the connections between things which, at first glance, seem utterly random. So join Victoria if you want to know what connects Aia, anks, arthez and uffon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101190000 +0000" stop="20230101200000 +0000" catchup-id="pnavFnbLbBCz4tt98FOscdq5bTgnjPfi0M1_l17Z"><title>Antiques Roadshow : 100 Years of the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/3bzLUHsDZ7qzi7YPXgOBzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Antiques Roadshow is at Alexandra Palace in north London to celebrate 100 years of BBC Television, where items include a collection of Doctor Who autographs and the Mastermind chair.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101200000 +0000" stop="20230101210000 +0000" catchup-id="Lka4i7vWpIb4kKL0eHt4B7nfLsEZcGqNfqA8LFxU"><title>Digging for Britain : Roman Towns and Tudor Shipwrecks</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/LJ8awR8hj0JbnL4YR0XcGw.jpg"></icon><desc>Digs in southern England reveal a previously unknown Roman town, a Tudor ship buried beneath a quarry and evidence of Henry VIII’s financialforgery under the Tower of London.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101210000 +0000" stop="20230101220000 +0000" catchup-id="z7-9moOC-HW_COcvvmb_FaLDdy4eYVktFd_PwLnG"><title>Motown Master: Lamont Dozier at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>A celebration of the work of songwriter Lamont Dozier, who passed away in 2022, featuring a rich selection from the BBC’s archive of performances of his work from over the decades. As one of the legendary Holland-Dozier-Holland trio, Lamont helped create the Motown sound that spread right across the globe in the 1960s, setting a new standard in popular songwriting and winning over fans like Bob Dylan and the Beatles with songs like You Keep Me Hanging On, Baby Love, This Old Heart of Mine and Reach Out I’ll Be There. This collection features Dozier’s best loved and most recognisable hits, performed by the artists like Diana Ross and the Supremes, The Four Tops, and Martha and the Vandellas, who he helped turn into international stars, as well as those who have kept his work alive and relevant to this day including Phil Collins, Kylie Minogue, Rod Stewart and Rag'n'Bone Man.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101220000 +0000" stop="20230101230000 +0000" catchup-id="X5NkTSqMXtFU1kSdPclLrySK18QG41KkjWI6MXd2"><title>When Motown Came to Britain</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In 1965, some of Motown's brightest new stars, including The Supremes, Stevie Wonder, Martha and the Vandellas, and Smokey Robinson and the Miracles, arrived in London for a tour that would change the face of British music history. At that time, pop music fans in the UK were unlikely to hear black music on mainstream radio, and names like Stevie Wonder and Smokey Robinson still meant nothing to most British people. But thousands of miles away from where these exciting new sounds were being recorded in Detroit, a small group of dedicated British music fans had stumbled across the songs and began championing its artists. This is the story of how, by doing so, they paved the way for the first Motown tour of Britain, changing the country's popular culture forever and helping propel the Motown artists to international stardom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230101230000 +0000" stop="20230102004000 +0000" catchup-id="1jFUsmMaSOYT70JvkDnxrk1HSc5oAIw4OlnB7ebN"><title>Marvin Gaye: Live at Montreux</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Captured during his live appearance at the Montreux Jazz Festival in July 1980, this highly energetic concert reinforces Marvin Gaye as the undisputed prince of Motown. He performs many of his timeless classics, including Let’s Get It On, Ain’t No Mountain High Enough, What’s Going On and I Heard It Through the Grapevine, resulting in thundering appreciation and applause from his audience. One of the most gifted talents to come up through the ranks of the Motown label, Marvin Gaye has paved the way for the unrelenting progression of popular black tracks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102004000 +0000" stop="20230102014000 +0000" catchup-id="nCbb6TWSkArO-PHPyF7k3RdiUaAo6vksT6xZJrrp"><title>Smokey Robinson at the Electric Proms</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The last night of the Electric Proms stars American soul legend Smokey Robinson in a very special celebration of 50 years of Motown. Presented from London's Roundhouse by Trevor Nelson and Edith Bowman, Smokey and his band are joined on stage by the BBC Concert Orchestra for a unique performance of arrangements specially commissioned by the BBC. The set includes classic soul and Motown songs from Smokey's career like Tears of a Clown, Tracks of My Tears and My Girl, alongside new material from his forthcoming album Time Flies When You're Having Fun.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102014000 +0000" stop="20230102024000 +0000" catchup-id="W_OCMrmNHFvs0Tl5jah_8H6z92vtCzD6bTVMbUrD"><title>Signed: Celebrity MasterChef : Festive Extravaganza</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/irQ7v7kv6eBCn6V_5FOXzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Dancer AJ Pritchard, actor Chizzy Akudolu, drag performer Kitty Scott-Claus and reality star and The X Factor: Celebrity winner Megan McKenna face two tough culinary challenges in this year's second festive special. Their first task is all about what to do with Christmas leftovers. Each celebrity has been given their own seasonal leftover from which to create a dish, and to help John and Gregg taste and judge is a very special guest judge, former Celebrity MasterChef champion Lisa Faulkner. Then it’s party time as the four celebrities are challenged to cook a dinner that they would serve at a New Year’s celebration. Expect plenty of laughs, some great Christmas banter and some surprisingly good food as the celebrities all do their best to be crowned the Celebrity MasterChef festive champion 2022.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102024000 +0000" stop="20230102034000 +0000" catchup-id="f1laL3x-FtHKtEF7EYmspOgDOxT6JsLkTfSTHuxW"><title>Mary Berry's Ultimate Christmas</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Mary Berry shares her ultimate Christmas feast, including all the trimmings, with friends Angela Hartnett, Monica Galetti and Rylan Clark.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102034000 +0000" stop="20230102063500 +0000" catchup-id="ZwVMDKwvfhAWtzOFa1OWK_OalZK00O5jBsUAE6Ra"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102063500 +0000" stop="20230102072000 +0000" catchup-id="K5gcHgG1GuXHMG_VnwDTXlF6bOECtS-Kk4BrQtX-"><title>Signed: Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. Roo Irvine, Melissa Downhill and Kevin Paxton are in Dunfermline.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102072000 +0000" stop="20230102082000 +0000" catchup-id="mcFDAo5wFZCkBQhYsiYJr0JHNEzJ0MJcrz00DTCd"><title>Dynasties : Macaque: Monkeys in the Mountains - A Dynasties Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/_q0hn4HFVrECdTkTsuVVsA.jpg"></icon><desc>High in the Atlas Mountains of Morocco lives a group of Barbary macaque monkeys. The alpha male, known as Mac, has just battled to win the leadership of the troop. He must now lead and protect them while fending off rivals who still want his crown.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102082000 +0000" stop="20230102092000 +0000" catchup-id="WBY4lGoq6botB0QRY58Thu5njgaWdhm9Tfjhi-0A"><title>Jay's Yorkshire Workshop</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Jay Blades' workshop makes furniture for local heroes in Yorkshire. This week, a 12-year-old who saved his dad's life and a woman who gets furniture to those in need.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102092000 +0000" stop="20230102111000 +0000" catchup-id="cKb-TAo0cbD-RIdzaGF_TEYIAa5wl7ePR3LugZUb"><title>In Which We Serve</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/xzmrpB6uMZGPBOO-SO7oUA.jpg"></icon><desc>This is the story of a ship - the HMS Torrin - from its construction to its participation at Dunkirk and its final sinking in the Battle of Crete. As the ship goes down, the crew remember their homes and loved ones. Based on true events as recounted to Noel Coward by Lord Mountbatten.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102111000 +0000" stop="20230102121000 +0000" catchup-id="b2LHVRriGiZXUtraVblgAqGFYsWBoVx9S3QN0ENE"><title>Dogs in the Wild: Meet the Family : Secrets of Success</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>One family, 37 faces: from the Arctic wolf to the talkative dhole, the tiny fennec fox to the long-legged maned wolf, this is the definitive celebration of dogs in the wild.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102121000 +0000" stop="20230102124000 +0000" catchup-id="zWQWrO0z_QLp8CtkpHfqXVa6Fu8gpUL4lOS-f_Am"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Comfort Food</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge helps local dieters lose weight for good. As a self-confessed former comfort eater, Tom knows only too well the temptations which lay ahead for the group.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102124000 +0000" stop="20230102142000 +0000" catchup-id="oqnsp-BheGX68-34AYj82QQ_SvxXfqw2GgBakvEE"><title>The Man Who Never Was</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/eGH_HS2aTxepNSXvlOBidQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Espionage thriller in which a British intelligence officer plans an elaborate hoax in the spring of 1943 to fool the Germans into thinking the Allies are about to invade Greece, not Sicily. The plan calls for the navy to float a dead body carrying false identification and information so that the Germans will pick it up. The first part of the mission succeeds, but will the Nazis take the bait?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102142000 +0000" stop="20230102161500 +0000" catchup-id="KkSCmUJHJUu__8OOtVuYJAFPrFd7TGJsI8JzlIKd"><title>The Battle of the River Plate</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/P0XGK9kwKzWUdKrQg_jI4A.jpg"></icon><desc>Second World War naval adventure based on the true story of the pursuit of the seemingly unstoppable German battleship Graf Spee. Allied forces chase the vessel all the way to South America, but, after several failed attempts to sink the enemy ship, the Allies find themselves hatching a desperate and audacious plan.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102161500 +0000" stop="20230102171500 +0000" catchup-id="C9gY1m1DoIth83Seg0mxvR7rMj6k11j-kv9yP2Ao"><title>The Real Marigold Hotel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Lq6Kza8WP3_iKQVZrV8GDg.jpg"></icon><desc>Britt Ekland, Duncan Bannatyne, Dame Zandra Rhodes, Paul Chuckle, Henry Blofeld, John Altman, Susie Blake and Barbara Dickson arrive in Puducherry and settle into their new home.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102171500 +0000" stop="20230102180000 +0000" catchup-id="TN6pp8XJR9ADrVcZAIZrNoGz5Mh6ZvZR0hEujhdT"><title>Flog It!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Members of the public try to make money out of their antiques by taking a risk at auction.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102180000 +0000" stop="20230102183000 +0000" catchup-id="7lgu9Pw3bYic1L2qqSnF3dmOdPspkCsS5-tJWyub"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 18: Monday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Adrian Chiles, Greg McHugh, Sukh Ojla and Jayne Sharp take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102183000 +0000" stop="20230102193000 +0000" catchup-id="a3bsPO3B6wg8_wiuKDGDeee-aJrSy_koggJjYuJf"><title>Inside the Factory : Trains</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/qzkvUj9rZwF1kJEEG1A35w.jpg"></icon><desc>Gregg Wallace accesses huge factories that use extraordinary engineering processes to make our most iconic vehicle.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102193000 +0000" stop="20230102200000 +0000" catchup-id="pMQWpN325kSTB3uT5pJDkGVHvZdn-AWiOPTmOar9"><title>Mastermind</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/2x2bAg5oZd-Vt9Cw9pfaCw.jpg"></icon><desc>Clive Myrie presents another heat of the classic quiz where contenders take on the famous black chair under the glare of the spotlight and the ticking clock in an attempt to become the next Mastermind champion. The specialist subjects are the British Industrial Revolution, the films of Christopher Guest, Charles Rennie Mackintosh and Succession.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102200000 +0000" stop="20230102203000 +0000" catchup-id="NWiRnmsyjCsPcn-aT80kPxXnJPQv-31gfsHY87Ky"><title>Only Connect : Statisticals v Morporkians</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102203000 +0000" stop="20230102210000 +0000" catchup-id="wlf22_Q5aSZUzaPPdF8nTA02K13YsX8RNsECedP7"><title>University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>The second round of the 2022/23 competition begins tonight. Two teams of students go head-to-head for a place in the quarter-finals. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102210000 +0000" stop="20230102220000 +0000" catchup-id="QXp2aB2P9LhGiNjpLRzxgJBTTZYYJStk2vT6dGqP"><title>The Mayfair Hotel Megabuild</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Although it looks like business as usual at Claridge's - one of London's most luxurious five-star hotels, set in the heart of Mayfair - beneath the surface of the exclusive hotel, filled with glamorous guests who enjoy the finer things in life, is a busy building site. An extraordinary engineering project is underway, which seeks to add a five-story basement at the bottom and 72 new rooms and suites spread over three new floors at the top. But the owners are insistent that the hotel must remain open throughout the build, with the guests oblivious to the noise surrounding them - leading the miners to tunnel by hand. Filmed over six years, this series follows the building team and the hotel staff as they try to complete the build with as little disruption as possible to the hotel's array of high-profile guests.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102220000 +0000" stop="20230102235500 +0000" catchup-id="SyZc5JVifXZ36zuA3lPyZQbCoIlMtzM_29eCVUC5"><title>Romeo + Juliet</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/ZuNJ2s6cH7aMR0v0LRNlNA.jpg"></icon><desc>Visionary director Baz Luhrman offers a unique take on Shakespeare's greatest love story, restaging the romantic tragedy against a backdrop of modern Americana. After meeting by chance at a costume party, young lovers Romeo and Juliet find their blossoming romance threatened by a violent rivalry between their two warring families - the Montagues and Capulets. Despite Juliet's betrothal and Romeo's banishment, the teenage couple are determined to overcome their families' differences - regardless of the consequences.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230102235500 +0000" stop="20230103005500 +0000" catchup-id="__cJ44e0LQF2MFd80wmnROpyzaNETRn6pMVjeDK-"><title>Digging for Britain : Roman Towns and Tudor Shipwrecks</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/LJ8awR8hj0JbnL4YR0XcGw.jpg"></icon><desc>Digs in southern England reveal a previously unknown Roman town, a Tudor ship buried beneath a quarry and evidence of Henry VIII’s financialforgery under the Tower of London.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103005500 +0000" stop="20230103015500 +0000" catchup-id="gLD_9klK7CHtdiHC40qCYVdT5iODhje4msJpqjYp"><title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/5_Dul6Lg_CFLFmGN6Ods1Q.jpg"></icon><desc>It’s pop star versus soap star as former Pussycat Doll Kimberly Wyatt takes on Coronation Street’s Ryan Thomas in a battle of buying and selling. These two best friends bomb around the B-roads in a muscle car from Kim’s American childhood while hitting the shops around Ryan’s old stomping ground, Manchester. There are also a couple of starstruck experts, Natasha Raskin-Sharp and Serhat Ahmet, to help them find the good stuff within a £400 budget. With an antique collecting heritage in the blood of both celebrities, the pressure is on to bring home that auction winning item. Kim and Serhat pin their hopes on a strange looking sculptural item with a hidden history, while Ryan and Natasha are on a mission to find an iconic piece of Corrie memorabilia.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103015500 +0000" stop="20230103025500 +0000" catchup-id="p7Mb1u13Pfe788UWmtVFB8TUIRCFJREw2DdmDJ_d"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Claudia Winkleman greets 22 strangers as they arrive at a beautiful castle in the Scottish Highlands to play the ultimate reality game of detection, backstabbing and trust, in the hope of winning up to £120,000. And it’s not long before the players are questioning everything, and everyone, as Claudia secretly assigns three traitors. It is up to the traitors, under the cover of darkness, to pick off their fellow players one by one, murdering them from the game. The rest of the players, the faithful, must try to work out who the traitors are and banish them from the game before they become their next victim. The lucky ones who survive to the end will have a chance to win that life-changing cash. But if a traitor remains undetected, they will take all the money.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103025500 +0000" stop="20230103035500 +0000" catchup-id="0m0iR8ezBloP9qhEhhyfxx027bOSp8rqcs5g_xp2"><title>Cinderella; A Comic Relief Pantomime for Christmas</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/6lbFffP6excffqZKL09_ig.jpg"></icon><desc>The worlds of theatre, film, comedy and music collide as Comic Relief presents a brand new ‘stay-at-home’ adaptation of the pantomime Cinderella. The timeless classic, rewritten by the award-winning Dawson Brothers and produced by Richard Curtis, sees a host of A-list stars take on some of the most iconic roles in panto. The stellar cast includes Olivia Colman as the Fairy Godmother, Guz Khan as Buttons, Helena Bonham Carter as Devilia, Tom Hollander as Baron Hardup and real-life sister and brother Daisy May and Charlie Cooper as the Evil Stepsisters. This virtual script-read guarantees big laughs whilst also raising money to fight loneliness, hunger and cold at home and abroad, both during Christmas and beyond.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103035500 +0000" stop="20230103063000 +0000" catchup-id="icYFr-d9UBaKbhzvUU3S9PvbkywKYLWzMh2ZYrpC"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103063000 +0000" stop="20230103071500 +0000" catchup-id="aXODDz7GodDSex39Gi1meFQmM2-sO99jFYg-wDFI"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Kilnsey Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Busy tenant farming couple David and Charlotte rear their sheep and cattle in the heart of the Yorkshire Dales with help from their young, enthusiastic children and are so determined to build a secure future for the farm that they both hold down second jobs. With their finest sheep in tow, the family are pinning their hopes on winning at Kilnsey Show, and to up their chances, they’re entering 18 different classes! Meanwhile, near the North York Moors, father and daughter James and Hannah are pulling out all the stops with a photoshoot of their first-class flock, in the hope that they can hold onto their championship trophies at Kilnsey Show this year. Being Dales country, though, competition is extremely tough among the hundreds of sheep farmers being judged today.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103071500 +0000" stop="20230103080000 +0000" catchup-id="6yOvUUsg4BbDhNMB86S91XJfhh_OczX2NyLyMQSK"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Cath from Cheshire and Morgan from Oxfordshire, both hoping to turn their talent into profitable businesses, step into the marquee. Cleaner Cath wants to swap the day job for a willow weaving business and is hoping Dom and his team can help. But mentor Eddie is worried that Cath’s giant life-sized fantastical beasts and fairies are not saleable and urges Cath to rethink her business model. For furniture maker Morgan, it’s all about having confidence in his skills, as mentor Alice tries to convince him to believe in himself and his work. Both makers are given eight weeks to put their mentors’ advice into practice. But can they make enough money to follow their dreams?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103080000 +0000" stop="20230103090000 +0000" catchup-id="lZ7AGMBTN2mLmRY0NU555RQfWquqHgxxyFjGQNSE"><title>Signed: The Repair Shop Christmas Special : Christmas Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/nNgi6NKnt4-BVyFPrYGWJQ.jpg"></icon><desc>The team revives five festive items, including a 100-year-old artificial tree that has been through the wars, and a repaired projector brings footage of loved ones back into focus.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103090000 +0000" stop="20230103100000 +0000" catchup-id="kcENGjCBYa5ClNlTxd21ZgPVWAZ2iLxAsegfaiEE"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103100000 +0000" stop="20230103130000 +0000" catchup-id="UMvIbSR3eYI5845sXNdvIOK8For6HoqphrPAaA0y"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103130000 +0000" stop="20230103133000 +0000" catchup-id="jX9Dg-5mfgYMp7WZlYuaWjmxal1tvJepqIaOsCmo"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Quick and Easy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge helps local dieters lose weight for good. Tom turns the spotlight on dieters who say they are too busy or inexperienced to cook healthy meals at home.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103133000 +0000" stop="20230103141500 +0000" catchup-id="zsmLlwUU9_L3F2wkN6i3nDjoy9XXxmkFuTg_IB8g"><title>Saved and Remade</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/oAfYIcPI0R4sG_ACTOv8ow.jpg"></icon><desc>A sailing club's training boat, damaged beyond repair in a storm, and a musician's first trombone are among the transformations for the skilled team of crafters.xxxxxxxx</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103141500 +0000" stop="20230103161500 +0000" catchup-id="VQ6x66YHVYV34Kqjv_LfNw_G_DwxxPR5MZc6G52P"><title>Carousel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/39U4UWojZllRzqjbCgcs1A.jpg"></icon><desc>Billy Bigelow, a vagabond and good-for-nothing carnival barker, finally settles down with a first-class woman but gets stabbed to death while committing a robbery. Many years later, an angel offers him the chance to return to earth for just one day to make things right for his miserable wife and the daughter he never had the chance to meet. Classic musical based on the stage play by Rodgers and Hammerstein.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103161500 +0000" stop="20230103171500 +0000" catchup-id="wyM6TylsvDGnuYD0w32dw4EvIz5OiZ7LwgFmFBs7"><title>The Real Marigold Hotel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Lq6Kza8WP3_iKQVZrV8GDg.jpg"></icon><desc>The group travel to India’s largest golden temple to explore Hinduism before taking a night train to Madurai to experience the sights and sounds of the Chithirai festival.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103171500 +0000" stop="20230103180000 +0000" catchup-id="Axyxwneit6BH74qmxXfxGGRn_FHBbKIB9B-mh4gQ"><title>Flog It!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>A special edition of Flog it! from all over the UK, travelling up and down the country, revisiting some of the historic venues from the series and bringing brand new valuations and unexpected auctions. Paul Martin finds out all about the fascinating people of Sledmere house through the ages.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103180000 +0000" stop="20230103183000 +0000" catchup-id="RYQSPH1W7kkFyd9LJ8flkcp3Y8hFGFHTu_wVWXhA"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 18: Tuesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Adrian Chiles, Greg McHugh, Sukh Ojla and Jayne Sharp take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103183000 +0000" stop="20230103190000 +0000" catchup-id="7te-pOdi-xGu-MSz_CKBiBb5VDnGpQAWveJCKaLL"><title>Take a Hike : Paul's Walk, Malham Cove</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103190000 +0000" stop="20230103193000 +0000" catchup-id="qjn9I4n1Wq40oPJGu0TpFIEp30Hbuh1obzm6AVOn"><title>Take a Hike : Ilaria's Walk, Ilkley Moor</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103193000 +0000" stop="20230103200000 +0000" catchup-id="CG1e45SZew-zcJ3YYezMbo8YmdEN4Avm7Xq0qsWO"><title>Saving Lives at Sea</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/vHIMpwylEHC32tE-4PvX9g.jpg"></icon><desc>The Dunmore East lifeboat crew come to the aid of a boat that's stuck and taking on water. Can they save this vessel from bad conditions before it sinks?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103200000 +0000" stop="20230103210000 +0000" catchup-id="5VJkvbbrW2Z2E6sYHND_cHHg_ikRBo9HnPQc24dD"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Si and Dave start their new adventure in south Wales, hunting for unique ingredients to include on the menu of a family restaurant that has its eyeson winning a Michelin star.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103210000 +0000" stop="20230103220000 +0000" catchup-id="fEH-O7u2qEnW2dicy5aApNgHy4qy1FMhBp874LYx"><title>Miriam Margolyes: Australia Unmasked</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>One of the things Miriam Margolyes has always loved about being Australian is being part of a nation that isn’t ruled by class. But she increasingly suspects that’s not the whole story. Ever alert to the contradictions, Miriam wants to understand what class looks like in Australia – and how much it shapes our expectations and opportunities. To answer this question, Miriam travels through the state of Victoria and across the class divide – attending polo matches and bogan burnouts.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103220000 +0000" stop="20230103223000 +0000" catchup-id="O4VD7rFk7S5xX7Pq2aJT2unwdBd_3kiqX99EfXiN"><title>Detectorists</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Gsw0l04x4-owX9aSN3P_tA.jpg"></icon><desc>A new comedy about two friends - Andy and Lance - who go searching for their hearts' desire with a couple of metal detectors. Following a chance encounter with a young history student, Lance and Andy embark on a journey towards the discovery of a lifetime. All they need to do is get permission from the local landowner, the mad one who is rumoured to have done away with his wife.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103223000 +0000" stop="20230103231500 +0000" catchup-id="3tcAVhTdOn0RJI9o0MRh-ZKQxOUUhzmxxzSlkK_1"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Sima Kotecha.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230103231500 +0000" stop="20230104001500 +0000" catchup-id="_2EwDnGn52YK_qOdqMsCFdITYo3rda0vqgPVfH55"><title>The Caribbean with Andi and Miquita</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/2re17rbWqyVFA4Aiac8qWQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Andi Oliver and daughter Miquita go on the journey of a lifetime to the Caribbean. In Antigua, they meet their eldest relative, who shares disturbing memories of colonial days.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104001500 +0000" stop="20230104020000 +0000" catchup-id="nYLbgnBXtrFE5HNpe10jKgzPaR84pW2HVmAt5SJZ"><title>My Old School</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/mBY0v_5n-ecNk-S_o-dnzg.jpg"></icon><desc>The story of Scotland's most notorious impostor. A 16-year-old boy is the new kid at school and becomes a model pupil - until he is unmasked.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104020000 +0000" stop="20230104024500 +0000" catchup-id="styp9kFQ5IBKefWXtPselcyzP3WpZEpd03HE3iys"><title>Signed: Expedition Rhino: The Search for the Last Northern White</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An expedition team including wildlife cameraman Vianet Djenguet venture into war-torn South Sudan in the hope of rediscovering the extinct northern white rhino.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104024500 +0000" stop="20230104034500 +0000" catchup-id="_ACMGcLU4aIvr4FyMCMrwprGZ6r7Zwk9amA6JB0G"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The ultimate game of detection, backstabbing and trust suddenly becomes very real for the players as it’s revealed who has been murdered during the night by the traitors. As accusations start to fly, the group are sent on another mission to continue building money for the prize pot. Evening starts to descend, and attention turns back to whom the traitors could be. The players head to the round table for the first dramatic banishment, but will the faithful be able to catch a traitor, or will they unknowingly banish one of their own?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104034500 +0000" stop="20230104063000 +0000" catchup-id="asVHbOnBi8FWdsCv-XawVXXGd67l4IMujZwZRUwa"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104063000 +0000" stop="20230104071500 +0000" catchup-id="2sFfKj80UqrLYwQZzuCOqnThYVhAv-quSG5g28m8"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Lavenham Farmers' Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>New farmer Greg has spent the past two years transforming a derelict council plot into a fruit and veg haven. After missing the countryside while working as a yacht crew member, and then overcoming heart surgery, Greg’s mission now is to provide fresh quality food to his community. As a new business making little profit, selling at award-winning Lavenham Farmers’ Market is a vital source of income, so creating an eye-catching stall to show off his colourful harvest is key. Nearby, hard-working tenant farmers Sophie and Tim have brought a full range of dairy and meat, from milkshakes to burgers, to bag as many sales as they can on a hot summer’s day. With young son Henry on the till, Sophie is freed up to go on the charm offensive with potential customers.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104071500 +0000" stop="20230104080000 +0000" catchup-id="yDYqEyFmkXGjwdFD4wvoKNZgbbyMHnyC5YuA7Ik2"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Glassblower Belinda from Northamptonshire and upcyclers Becky and Paul from Oxfordshire are hoping Dom and his team can help them turn their passions into profits. Belinda has only been glass-blowing for three years and has recently graduated from university. After originally worrying that her autism might prevent her from developing her skills, she’s become a talented glassblower with huge potential. Becky and husband Paul met and married after their partners both passed away. Now they want to establish a business that will support the two of them so that Paul can give up his painting and decorating job, and they can work together. Can Dom and his team help them both to build successful businesses and live the creative lives they dream of?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104080000 +0000" stop="20230104083000 +0000" catchup-id="7DbJQ_FOsm1UwOyxcKfGsISk0bFB62FoJOwbiu6S"><title>See Hear : On Tour: Edinburgh</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/ueAmDj_irz8MdgbkftyL0Q.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104083000 +0000" stop="20230104090000 +0000" catchup-id="k4JhiU5nB9baWY5KXilt4QWxJJQk5SXeBlz1_Fxu"><title>Signed: A Countryside Winter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Gethin Jones delivers the ultimate guide to a countryside winter featuring wildlife, food, gardening and outdoor adventure, all brought by a selection of favourite BBC faces. In this episode, Chris Packham demonstrates the wonderful wildlife spectacles to look out for in winter. Mary Berry cooks the perfect winter warmer, her potato and lentil jumble bake, and Paul Martin learns some simple and affordable tricks to keep garden wildlife happy during winter.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104090000 +0000" stop="20230104100000 +0000" catchup-id="tOgLomu-qQwgvUoleUEuCO4mij6niPXofHQ0Jmod"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104100000 +0000" stop="20230104130000 +0000" catchup-id="XrWd4-F_Jepcr3DrEsZezg-qng5p2GOSMcWoEO_x"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104130000 +0000" stop="20230104133000 +0000" catchup-id="bv2jqnTHoOWS1Mlf68jj-FHf-jbdOJ39jG3P1h8J"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Special Treats</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge helps local dieters lose weight for good. Tom provides special treat recipes targeted at foodies who love good food but still want to lose weight.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104133000 +0000" stop="20230104141500 +0000" catchup-id="vj-BDZs_FKJUTJC1njOwGcGNsROIQk2LOHxtTTqy"><title>Saved and Remade</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/oAfYIcPI0R4sG_ACTOv8ow.jpg"></icon><desc>A post box used in a wedding ceremony, a much-loved armchair and a church pew are among the items transformed into beautiful and functional items by a skilled team of crafters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104141500 +0000" stop="20230104161000 +0000" catchup-id="e9_sB92Ewi57WFmGS3vRyR7gOWXNN1UBe3gDw195"><title>Pride and Prejudice</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/iDSkPSIWDxoYjRc4Ss_LtA.jpg"></icon><desc>Period drama based on Jane Austen's classic novel about the five husband-hunting Bennet sisters and the impact of the handsome but apparently aloof Mr Darcy on the spirited Elizabeth. Though attracted to Darcy, Elizabeth - the second of the Bennet daughters - is repelled by his cold manner and by rumours of the man's cruelty towards one of his friends</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104161000 +0000" stop="20230104161500 +0000" catchup-id="VLTEl2a99gEic_s2J0E9A9LneN8CKzVW0utRRdor"><title>Beechgrove Repotted</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Jackie Fry has lovingly renovated two acres of previously overgrown land in Gifford on the edge of the Lammermuirs. Shortly after moving in, Jackie and her husband were hit by a snowstorm which quickly made them realise that their garden, 730ft above sea level, would have to be filled with hardy plants which would survive the harsh climate and cold temperatures. Jackie has created a garden full of charm and an array of flowers and fruit providing interest the whole year round.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104161500 +0000" stop="20230104171500 +0000" catchup-id="tY5TawEz6ZnMewDP5yiX85Muus8EIQTif_S9UZiy"><title>The Real Marigold Hotel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Lq6Kza8WP3_iKQVZrV8GDg.jpg"></icon><desc>Susie celebrates her birthday with the group, while Henry gets a chance to revisit the cricket ground where he made his last overseas broadcast.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104171500 +0000" stop="20230104180000 +0000" catchup-id="5CAMzL6zDGTOgtmbWtg-aO7C2zoaeiNMBKTnTJ-Z"><title>Flog It! : Wolverhampton 2</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104180000 +0000" stop="20230104183000 +0000" catchup-id="Svc8mF8fkpo9J3LDZa-4xkznbwEAIDOl-W_YVMs2"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 18: Wednesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Adrian Chiles, Greg McHugh, Sukh Ojla and Jayne Sharp take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104183000 +0000" stop="20230104190000 +0000" catchup-id="RZkv0MFaQo38js5TrEUbEfx3wHP5p9mjYslTqYml"><title>Take a Hike : Natalie's Walk, Robin Hood's Bay</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104190000 +0000" stop="20230104200000 +0000" catchup-id="A4zH87tbItqWOeirXu0knWo_9Spc20k5dSnNzSHj"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Following six farming families in some of Scotland's most remote locations. Emma and Ewan move to their forever farm on Bute, while cousins Donald and David prepare for a busy lambing season.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104200000 +0000" stop="20230104210000 +0000" catchup-id="K2exi6VgP7sBauD_CeTH4aZRvA8ZCwRYaHW85TGW"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dave and Si continue their adventure in Glasgow, on the hunt for new ingredients to include on the menu of a Scottish-Malaysian fusion restaurant.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104210000 +0000" stop="20230104220000 +0000" catchup-id="3E0rPDEMozRG4Ys9SccHfQcZleXoGqjUG4ZpyEpU"><title>Ukraine: The People's Fight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Filmmaker Olly Lambert spends two months on Ukraine’s southern frontline with volunteer special forces as they begin the push to capture Kherson. How are they winning the fight?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104220000 +0000" stop="20230104223000 +0000" catchup-id="f_qM9RrdqkoQStvT1RoKaYCgaD6Krf-G-TQik2a5"><title>Our Flag Means Death : Pilot</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>After uprooting his life in search of adventure, aristocrat-turned-pirate captain Stede Bonnet must go to new lengths to tame the mutinous motley crew of his ship, the Revenge. But when his efforts to impress the boisterous buccaneers lead to a raid on a vessel with ties to his former life, Stede is left to question whether he's tough enough for the high seas.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104223000 +0000" stop="20230104231500 +0000" catchup-id="reqWdDFYVddF79EhyVZd7B2XLCUXp5dkam9cwMQU"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230104231500 +0000" stop="20230105001500 +0000" catchup-id="WGJmoHFw9E89yftKOMcsVYDceLfNVeolVvDbYXLU"><title>The Caribbean with Andi and Miquita</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/2re17rbWqyVFA4Aiac8qWQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Andi and Miquita travel to Barbados as this most British of Caribbean islands prepares to become a republic, cutting ties with the UK. They also explore their roots as they receive DNA test results.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105001500 +0000" stop="20230105004500 +0000" catchup-id="2fm8mNNEzg-7QnlZtL8-FD5ol6OY3HM9eLHLqAXb"><title>See Hear : On Tour: Edinburgh</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/ueAmDj_irz8MdgbkftyL0Q.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105004500 +0000" stop="20230105014500 +0000" catchup-id="nSNPMSbFRnfl64TRVu2XTx5oir4VnzE-8KhASusJ"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>There are tears and anger over the breakfast table as the identity of the second person to be murdered by the traitors is revealed. The players are sent into a spin as they discover more about each other in the mission, and a dramatic showdown at the round table results in another player being banished from the game. As evening descends and the players reel from yet another day of treachery, Claudia has one more surprise twist up her sleeve.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105014500 +0000" stop="20230105024500 +0000" catchup-id="RJhs5INhx7klWuSNAK-vD2uO9BEFuMhrCiZhmOfh"><title>Signed: Oti Mabuse: My South Africa</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Strictly's Oti Mabuse returns to her childhood home to revisit the people and places that inspired her to be the dancer and woman she is today.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105024500 +0000" stop="20230105033000 +0000" catchup-id="-1jO3bYXvR7FdT-t53Cmw5NFMq0aGpxgi4U3pmSd"><title>Signed: Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/208x308/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, antiques auctioneer Charles Hanson, top trader Linda Lambert and trendy upcycler Zoe Pocock head to Glastonbury to find some bargains they can turn into some flipping profit. Rummaging through antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets, they only have one day to each find those hidden second-hand or used gems that will make them a nice big wedge of cash. Then we follow them as they try to turn these items into gold (or a profit at least). Will Charles ever be able to sell that expensive wooden chest? Can Linda find a buyer for that confessional door? And after her plans go awry, what is Zoe going to do with all those dolls? It's a race against time, as they only have three weeks before their profits are revealed. And at the end of it all, who will make the most flipping profit?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105033000 +0000" stop="20230105063000 +0000" catchup-id="m2fdavr1G5wrPFR8G1mU6RQvtREKE-dLzz0mYLZR"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105063000 +0000" stop="20230105071500 +0000" catchup-id="aT-3G9WVYaQ_z98SQYXwpFZvDEm2MD5HIlg2Vcjm"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Heckington Show - Shire Horses</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Committed horseman John is devoted to his shire horses Richard and George, who live at stables near Grimsby that John built for them. Shires are now a rare breed, and John fears for their future. By competing at Lincolnshire’s Heckington Show, he hopes to raise awareness of their champion qualities and rack up some rosettes with help at the reins from friend Terri, who is showing for the first time. Also competing are farming couple Lucy and Oliver, whose family farm is starting to reap the rewards of their hard work in breeding healthy shire foals, one of which will be making a star appearance with her mum in the judging ring. Show day has its stresses but also its successes for these determined competitors.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105071500 +0000" stop="20230105080000 +0000" catchup-id="OhKd9RIKVA3IgWLnF9yh1wLg05S9q2J-1fY3WTQm"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Mike and Sarah are looking to change their lives in the marquee. Labourer Mike has a passion for turning wooden bowls, but is held back by his struggle for perfection. Mentor Alice hopes helping him see the beauty in the imperfections in his work will be the key to unlocking a profitable business. Sarah’s life changed during the pandemic when she quit her job and took up pottery. One year on and she needs to start making money from her craft, but mentor Derek worries she’s pricing herself out of the market with her hand-crafted ceramic animals. Both makers are given two months to put their mentors’ advice into practice. But can they make enough money to give up the day jobs for good?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105080000 +0000" stop="20230105090000 +0000" catchup-id="QzIGcrWcFSVHK6DWQ6rI0uisVrR-9gjnJLVlDYzP"><title>Signed: Snow Dogs</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Wildlife film-maker Gordon Buchanan gets close to seven incredible huskies on a treacherous dogsled adventure through Canada’s spectacular Yukon wilderness, gaining a new appreciation for dogs and our place in nature. Gordon arrives in Canada’s vast Yukon wilderness to try and master the ancient skill of dog sledding. Inspired by Jack London’s novel The Call of the Wild, it has been Gordon’s childhood dream to command a team of dogs out in the Yukon wilderness and follow in the footsteps of the historic Klondike Gold Rush explorers who used this trail. Gordon meets Pierre-Luc Fortin, expert musher and owner of 29 loyal Alaskan huskies, and is introduced to his seven-sled dog team.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105090000 +0000" stop="20230105100000 +0000" catchup-id="dkmafesWtwylYkuklYiD2qbiJJRXNhLrxPjkwEYu"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105100000 +0000" stop="20230105130000 +0000" catchup-id="PJhCpbc6CXwcvguc5XE0VaTkbiXeb6WxNr4N5FJv"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105130000 +0000" stop="20230105133000 +0000" catchup-id="HP5RkUwIsR-lJlyVkGLc5f9cLhWE4bg2ABqwc5mC"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Takeaway Alternatives</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge helps local dieters lose weight for good. Tom sets about inventing lower calorie alternatives to takeaways and ready meals.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105133000 +0000" stop="20230105141500 +0000" catchup-id="iw_id-ZK6gKhTxJupMRueMoGb6xdcsY4aYZ9UiUh"><title>Saved and Remade</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/oAfYIcPI0R4sG_ACTOv8ow.jpg"></icon><desc>A Swiss clock that caused a honeymooning couple's first argument forty years ago, an upright piano and a collection of skateboards are among the radical transformations.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105141500 +0000" stop="20230105160000 +0000" catchup-id="J62igutF-EvPqOliQ71xCjOwlQp6xosW9vJKVVuq"><title>Scott of the Antarctic</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/U1C_vH0CwrNxDq6zCdwSxw.jpg"></icon><desc>A documentary-style dramatic depiction of the ill-fated 1911 expedition to the South Pole. Determined to lead the first expedition to reach the South Pole, naval officer Scott assembles a team to try to beat a Norwegian attempt. However, the conditions the men face in the Antarctic prove draining and disastrous</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105160000 +0000" stop="20230105161500 +0000" catchup-id="tOJOqMQz-0C8u0ju7waV2_VGhUdLlRxVaXVzcr1H"><title>Beechgrove Repotted</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Scotland boasts some of the very best public gardens in the UK. We visit a selection of Scottish gardens that are open to the public but we are given personal, and sometimes behind-the-scenes, tours of these lovely places. Kirsty shows the hidden living roof at the Royal Botanic Gardens Edinburgh, Brian gives insight into Scone Palace’s hedge maze, and at Branklyn Gardens in Perth we are treated to the gardener’s tour.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105161500 +0000" stop="20230105171500 +0000" catchup-id="0Y6QV0ERAN_sQX_JdAXU6s3Wdu30egD5nb26UtpG"><title>The Real Marigold Hotel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Lq6Kza8WP3_iKQVZrV8GDg.jpg"></icon><desc>The group travel to Rishikesh in the foothills of the Himalayas. Susie and Barbara visit a Buddhist monastery, while Britt, Henry and Paul visit an alternative retirement option.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105171500 +0000" stop="20230105180000 +0000" catchup-id="9yS87Yap56Wk_5-N2Co9x6egnwzaur4zNqrZ4HMx"><title>Flog It! : St Albans 11</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>This edition of the antiques series comes from St Albans Cathedral and Abbey in Hertfordshire. Experts Claire Rawle and James Lewis are on hand to value items and take them off to auction. James is excited when some historic coins land on his table, and Claire has fun with a 1970s robot. Presenter Paul Martin takes a trip to a local theatre company who use theatrical masks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105180000 +0000" stop="20230105183000 +0000" catchup-id="Q72-gNirhcYj9Tmm50G4gEVbExcWNZMqbWMhI1HV"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 18: Thursday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Adrian Chiles, Greg McHugh, Sukh Ojla and Jayne Sharp take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105183000 +0000" stop="20230105190000 +0000" catchup-id="i3tdEiRjP79A9AY6V5dfVeFNHMbB8RcxQLYNIKzi"><title>Take a Hike : Edwin's Walk, Brimham Rocks</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105190000 +0000" stop="20230105200000 +0000" catchup-id="0bRrW5a2TTeT_NgojqV0naaVC15JIx0_0sdDceQu"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>As spring arrives on the farms, it's all hands on deck to get through the busiest time of year. On Orkney fourth generation farmer Sean wants to one day own his own farm. For now he works alongside his dad and uncle. When their bumper lambing season is in full swing, his sister and her three you children also pitch in. In Stranraer Kayleigh's husband Rab has an important hospital appointment. Meanwhile it's full steam ahead with plans for their new, independent dairy business. The couple visit a dairy farm in Ayrshire, discovering how they've made a success of diversifying into milk shakes. On the Isle of Bute, Emma and Ewan are struggling to get to grips with their new farm, seven times the size of their old one. There's confusion in the fields as the ewes steal each other's lambs. They've still got weeks of lambing to get through and Emma is shattered.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105200000 +0000" stop="20230105210000 +0000" catchup-id="yy8muri5PpCGG1tVazIub3gSWhikLJ0EYS9WMIik"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The Bikers continue their adventure in the Cotswolds, on the hunt for new ingredients to include on a high-end, ten-course tasting menu.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105210000 +0000" stop="20230105220000 +0000" catchup-id="gea2uB9rZKIJr5KaehmXzKQRQiQGfViARQqFmhqh"><title>Marie Antoinette : Rival Queens</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/XarMFhUfVti5Dn8IZgZxaw.jpg"></icon><desc>With Louis still not consummating the marriage after four months, Marie realises that producing an heir will not be straightforward. She turns to Madame du Barry for support and advice. However, after discovering more about the woman’s past, Marie is shocked, and ‘friend’ becomes foe. There cannot be two queens at Versailles, and du Barry is not about to disappear.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105220000 +0000" stop="20230105223000 +0000" catchup-id="s6s3mFVIDMGTh-n1Y7i-wsTc6eLlW2ihoVOVwi_s"><title>The Apprentice: You're Fired : Antigua Tourism</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Taking an entertaining look at the process as Lord Sugar launches his search for a new business partner, host Tom Allen is joined by a panel of experts and fans to analyse this week’s task and meet the first candidate to be fired. Find out more on the website bbc.co.uk/apprentice or by using #TheApprentice.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105223000 +0000" stop="20230105231500 +0000" catchup-id="oaUlCGpWb6ypWqdK1tJlh1Q4Tu9YD5ahq9JmSYAT"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105231500 +0000" stop="20230105234000 +0000" catchup-id="XK_C1eWr3LN06XvTjMhW5UfIiGvMN8da_diUrSp5"><title>What We Do in the Shadows : On the Run</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/vUve-ZTQjVZIrhgVwNaRTw.jpg"></icon><desc>After a vengeful enemy from the past appears without warning, Lazlo flees the vampire home and goes into hiding to avoid certain death.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230105234000 +0000" stop="20230106000500 +0000" catchup-id="8PaSrokILpWYPGm5kiVzVPpEo5zcy3LChjJhMv81"><title>What We Do in the Shadows : The Return</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/5l1hQF318FS6Pv2e-cVD3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The vampires decide to open their home to an old nemesis who's down on his luck, and Guillermo grapples with the fact that he is descended from Abraham Van Helsing</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106000500 +0000" stop="20230106010500 +0000" catchup-id="WVdlA7iQKUxfmkb5Hn9j5O7TQWczRRkfNc5MTCoX"><title>Miriam Margolyes: Australia Unmasked</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>One of the things Miriam Margolyes has always loved about being Australian is being part of a nation that isn’t ruled by class. But she increasingly suspects that’s not the whole story. Ever alert to the contradictions, Miriam wants to understand what class looks like in Australia – and how much it shapes our expectations and opportunities. To answer this question, Miriam travels through the state of Victoria and across the class divide – attending polo matches and bogan burnouts.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106010500 +0000" stop="20230106020500 +0000" catchup-id="jN5dV5ARuikeUO2YfTjEUMvF8Xy_PLsoiToYFHf4"><title>Signed: How to Crack the Class Ceiling</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OnUHgXa6UZIpeijNX3DZKg.jpg"></icon><desc>Amol Rajan investigates how young people from working class backgrounds can secure jobs in Britain’s elite professions. With industries like banking and the law traditionally dominated by the middle classes, are there any tips or tricks that will help candidates from less privileged backgrounds secure their dream jobs? He meets people who’ve found their own ways to hack the class system, from a school etiquette class to a university soft skills workshop, and follows the progress of young people trying to get into the civil service, law and the City. Chris feels his Hull accent will hold him back, Paige is worried she doesn’t look and sound like a typical barrister, and Adnan wonders whether to talk about his working class background in finance interviews. Will any of the advice help these young people, or are they fighting against an impossibly rigged system?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106020500 +0000" stop="20230106030500 +0000" catchup-id="sShaaDvyiDP4zQxB2eRxIROTSdHvdwgtmv3hbUqR"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>With Claudia’s revelation throwing the castle into chaos, breakfast reaches a dramatic climax, and the levels of distrust reach boiling point. Before the dust has even had a chance to settle, the players must momentarily put their differences aside as they face another mission, where they are given the chance to add a potential £10,000 to the already growing prize pot. And with a tense round table on the horizon, one player has an extremely difficult decision to make.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106030500 +0000" stop="20230106035000 +0000" catchup-id="YYz-cc_2zKr1N13bqrFJhJQqyeVXUfHgEm9-wFRi"><title>Signed: Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, fine art dealer Gavin Claxton, market trader Gary Barton and aeronautical engineer/part-time upcycler Stu Abbott head to Durham to find some bargains they can turn into some flipping profit. The experts try to outdo each other by unearthing the best that Durham has to offer. Rummaging through antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets they have just one day to each find any items that will make them a huge profit. We then follow them over the next three weeks in their quest to make the most amount of profit in their own individual styles. As Stu gets mechanical, making money from bits and parts of a Mini, Gavin goes to auction to try to sell his pricey painting, and Gary uses all the Glasgow patter he can muster to sell his art deco bowls in Glasgow's famous Barras market. At the end of it all, who will make the most flipping profit?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106035000 +0000" stop="20230106063000 +0000" catchup-id="eESEaGYy6FFyiQTAPPptFk2-VIhNRBheNC2n6hwH"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106063000 +0000" stop="20230106071500 +0000" catchup-id="e4XNOlTA-cwck1McpE_CZX1p9_OCgbcuenfvDbaX"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Edenbridge &amp; Oxted - Sheep and Pigs</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Hard grafters Gussie and her mum Susan are a driving force on their family livestock farm in East Sussex, where three generations muck in every day to get the work done. Gussie’s passion is her Welsh pigs, and she his as keen for her pedigree team to scoop up awards at Edenbridge &amp; Oxted Agricultural Show. Meanwhile, Kent farmer Hayley and dedicated daughter-in-law Amy round up the finest members of their flock, hoping they can rack up some top rosettes for their badger face and Kerry Hill sheep. Although farming is in Hayley’s blood, she’s a newcomer to the judging ring. Armed with courage and a competitive spirit, these farmers face some of the best breeders in the region.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106071500 +0000" stop="20230106080000 +0000" catchup-id="STJaclptSl6SByzJhXdDrmPHy_hjsj9tmyF83Nro"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Ceramicist Izzy from London and stone carver Luke from the Scottish Borders step into the marquee hoping to turn their passions and skills into successful businesses. It’s high stakes for Izzy as she’s already given up her job in advertising to try and make it as a full time potter, but with lots still to learn when it comes to marketing, mentor Florian Gadsby, one of the UK’s most celebrated ceramicists, has the challenge of helping her make her pottery dreams come true. For Luke, dyslexia, and years of being bullied at school have knocked his confidence, preventing him from putting himself and his pieces out there, but Dom and mentor Louis can see just how talented he is. With just two months to put their mentors' advice into practice, can Izzy and Luke prove they’ve got what it takes to build successful businesses?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106080000 +0000" stop="20230106090000 +0000" catchup-id="1pteXfKdFYLn80_PPlZ6h-mCx6JZXjYFhbnsGugG"><title>Signed: Countryfile : Hogmanay and New Year Traditions</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106090000 +0000" stop="20230106100000 +0000" catchup-id="_RG_DAdKj5CBx0Svm1tCfx-v4bA93IY7a6b7SL0n"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106100000 +0000" stop="20230106130000 +0000" catchup-id="N3_x_dleLKsSNPPeQbc7WvInjJ97GUSZMgzCY0Y-"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106130000 +0000" stop="20230106133000 +0000" catchup-id="TKg4LFUuZ28wMlKRGnuUwKKpRlvz5HIdIfMlnNTp"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Movable Feasts</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge helps local dieters lose weight for good. The dieters need lower-calorie food they can take to work, so Tom creates delicious packed lunches and snacks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106133000 +0000" stop="20230106140000 +0000" catchup-id="7OU917-QI0rMjIBRKeZp_hy_A5fA4d0cu6BhH34c"><title>Tom Kerridge's Lose Weight for Good : Made for Sharing</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/6dGB0y_aYXlMwrcgp6z5vg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Kerridge invites his dieting gang on a river cruise to congratulate them on what they have achieved and to reveal how much weight they have lost as a group.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106140000 +0000" stop="20230106161000 +0000" catchup-id="wZSjHxYasMpY5GtqJYFp58XR_2af1PNHzK4I2KOl"><title>The Red Shoes</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/l0Uo-rAmn1whGGHmyt-V_A.jpg"></icon><desc>Eager young ballerina Victoria Page is delighted at being given the opportunity to dance with the renowned Ballet Lermontov, little realising the demands of its brilliant yet arrogant impresario will force a tragic choice between her career and her lover.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106161000 +0000" stop="20230106161500 +0000" catchup-id="DSFnpXCJw5kp09wNN6XnCgGHvLvDG9OsFnFJ5JiB"><title>Beechgrove Repotted</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Lynne Chapman loves her garden so much that she got married in it. When she and her family moved into the 150-year-old cottage, they renovated the garden, filling it with recycled items and free seeds they got from magazines. They built a pergola and put in a firepit to make the garden a family area surrounded by huge mature trees. Lynne used a lot of the junk metal that was left in the garden when she moved in to create planters for her many plants.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106161500 +0000" stop="20230106171500 +0000" catchup-id="Wqn8PYNx7KdpW5oQicWeQ9QAzOGl1Un56chHUqCe"><title>The Real Marigold on Tour : Mexico</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Bw3oW42n2O9IrDSGpzrvRQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Marigold On Tour favourites Paul Nicolas and Rosemary Shrager are joined by comedy duo Ian and Janette Tough to experience the secrets of a happy retirement in Mexico.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106171500 +0000" stop="20230106180000 +0000" catchup-id="efZ1xjSwyRgZZ0QvwfR6lclEdj8Rdxc3pEtJmplW"><title>Flog It! : St Albans 10</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Flog It! comes from the beautiful St Albans Cathedral and Abbey in Hertfordshire. Experts Claire Rawle and James Lewis are on hand to value antiques and collectibles. James comes across a pipe shaped like a polar explorer, and Claire discovers salt and pepper pots shaped like suffragettes. Paul Martin continues the suffragette theme when he visits nearby Knebworth House, where one of its past residents, Lady Constance Lytton, was a supporter of the cause.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106180000 +0000" stop="20230106183000 +0000" catchup-id="KSp6RR9hsiQd6QIWS_Jvk-t60YHgWzlKLdFLzl78"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 18: Friday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Adrian Chiles, Greg McHugh, Sukh Ojla and Jayne Sharp take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106183000 +0000" stop="20230106190000 +0000" catchup-id="tI_5TFPCnolLNDtXuyVhsG0Q-BMW0g6eN_TXdSzi"><title>Take a Hike : Annie's Walk, Flamborough Head</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106190000 +0000" stop="20230106200000 +0000" catchup-id="rfLjGmyC8aZ4TxNXtUPLaHIdmAgeYwmHdfsgzsvG"><title>Monty Don's Adriatic Gardens : Venice</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/9qNOPSMbQIWCs1dDY32zIQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Monty travels to Europe and explores the influence of the Venetians on gardening, starting in their home city at the top of the Adriatic coast and travelling on through Croatia and Greece. Visiting a range of public and private gardens, Monty learns about the impact that history, climate change and culture have had on the people who live there. To begin with, he explores Venice on one of the city's famous barges, stepping out to visit green spaces large and small that are often hidden from view behind high walls. He is invited in to see wonderful gardens along the Grand Canal, as well as meeting those who have managed to create a productive garden on a disused rubbish dump behind one of the city's famous churches. He then samples wine grown in vineyards inside the city limits before visiting a restored public garden with a secret passageway that leads to St Mark's Square.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106200000 +0000" stop="20230106210000 +0000" catchup-id="jdJIdVK6VUDIh2EiMnrlacNFKHOZUUm6E833ZlOo"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dave and Si continue their adventure on the east coast of Scotland, on the hunt for new, local ingredients to include on a menu at a beachfront café.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106210000 +0000" stop="20230106214500 +0000" catchup-id="mXyi9HF-vmT0mns-VJ84xiiP3y3mvcGc-3NxalsL"><title>QI : Ticks Tax Toes</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106214500 +0000" stop="20230106223000 +0000" catchup-id="2VpJgUR23D6KCusllA_xg5mWJMlAoUSpl2hcKMcW"><title>Live at the Apollo</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/R2ZYBlQacXTt2yaq81nYYw.jpg"></icon><desc>The brilliant Ed Gamble introduces comedians Tom Davis and Judi Love to the stage.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106223000 +0000" stop="20230106230500 +0000" catchup-id="_v0qMgKuwBl_nSfyZ1GTdU3a2fPXdX8XGdV3gTeI"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230106230500 +0000" stop="20230107010000 +0000" catchup-id="c8rXzhi-ajErmY8Et9YALri3m6Qpc8bKx54PfO8y"><title>Manhunter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/DDxSqWn9q85Qwy5PaUIH8g.jpg"></icon><desc>Dark thriller about an ex-FBI forensic investigator who is called in to track down a brutal serial killer known as the Tooth Fairy. To help him understand the mind of his quarry, he visits the prison that holds an old adversary of his - notorious serial killer Dr Hannibal 'the Cannibal' Lecktor. But the investigation comes to threaten his sanity and the lives of his family. Based on the novel Red Dragon by Thomas Harris.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107010000 +0000" stop="20230107020000 +0000" catchup-id="pgYipFyPTFLwDia-A4VQuA2o2thsN-jiQYzcTLE5"><title>Signed: How to Crack the Class Ceiling</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OnUHgXa6UZIpeijNX3DZKg.jpg"></icon><desc>Amol Rajan investigates how Britain's elite could create a fairer system for young people from working-class backgrounds trying to secure jobs in Britain's most prestigious professions. He follows Seth, who wants to get into the media but thinks they don't want white working-class candidates like him, and Adnan, who's struggling to land a graduate job in the City of London. What are employers and the government doing to create a level playing field for Britain's working-class young people? Amol meets leaders of top financial and media firms. Are they really trying to take action on class equality, or are they 'classwashing' - pretending to welcome working class candidates as a PR exercise? He meets the minister for equalities and someone from the top team of former prime minister Boris Johnson, and asks whether a government dominated by the privately educated understands the concerns of working-class people.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107020000 +0000" stop="20230107031000 +0000" catchup-id="Dp24zfTanW0yR6nyrb2PH2vH4TPMLWhfx7rB1wx4"><title>Signed: imagine : Malorie Blackman: What If?</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/oLYN1HV3OGywWqRXjEhbCg.jpg"></icon><desc>Alan Yentob follows one of Britain’s best-loved writers: Malorie Blackman, former Children’s Laureate and the first children’s writer to win the prestigious Pen Pinter Prize. Bold, provocative and challenging, her books have plunged children’s literature into previously uncharted waters: her tragic reverse-racism novel Noughts and Crosses challenged assumptions and declared her a writer like no other. As she prepares to publish her long-awaited autobiography, Malorie discusses the key moments in her life that made her a writer.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107031000 +0000" stop="20230107063000 +0000" catchup-id="gtqecOsU6gOoEgkniybXEPq8YGRsjVbbI4I00wNB"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107063000 +0000" stop="20230107063500 +0000" catchup-id="8v66kIIASXRmrkbLPX9S49GTBeROx1FFGoyah1rm"><title>Hey Duggee : Norrie's First Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/e0inMrqHDsuYReu_az2qiw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107063500 +0000" stop="20230107064500 +0000" catchup-id="yjL2H2TlHRfLi1Af3GS6F8CFvjGHF8BlcPE_cT0X"><title>Hey Duggee : The Moving Badge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/e0inMrqHDsuYReu_az2qiw.jpg"></icon><desc>Snail is thrilled to be moving house as she wishes to escape the wet and sploshy place she currently calls home for a more spacious house on the hill. But before she can move up in the world, she’s going to need some help from Duggee and the Squirrels to move her many belongings up the hill! Snail can’t do it alone, so Duggee teaches the Squirrels the best ways that they can get moving! They band together, cradling items and shifting furniture. Snail looks on with apprehension as they manage fragile vases with less care than she’d like. Luckily, Duggee intercepts the vases before they crash head first into one another and teaches the Squirrels all the ways they can move to ensure Snail has a stress-free and efficient move. They could lift, push or pull to get things moving! They work together as a team to get the job done before Snail can even reach the house, so they give her a helping hand too.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107064500 +0000" stop="20230107065000 +0000" catchup-id="0JamUzNQz7JQmcLHKj2YxVFDMH0p88y51j-lWGLQ"><title>Supertato : Tato Tower Takeover</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107065000 +0000" stop="20230107070000 +0000" catchup-id="8B_w6OU7Jt2Hy-8kNCqNrPxVDlf_Tua1pW9cKhwf"><title>Shaun the Sheep : Hot to Trotter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/PPo_AK-wdts_pvk6Ye3GeQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Can Bitzer and Shaun ensure that the regular dance competition is run fairly?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107070000 +0000" stop="20230107071000 +0000" catchup-id="jmhDotwfj1eEHcD4WrwMGBhg9dIg_imkMtgMfAf3"><title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher: Unleashed! : Thumb Wars</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/rv_UMd0MeToFCJbeUHRg-g.jpg"></icon><desc>Walter struggles to play fair during Miss Mistry's thumb wrestling solution to his competitive squabbles with Dennis, and the situation gets out of hand.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107071000 +0000" stop="20230107072500 +0000" catchup-id="r7O-sXN6HWcSq60Kw3sFrYhSi_HrfE0yK20rR9m0"><title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese : Begins!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/AV_bKsPSjxh2Z2bfvzQR7Q.jpg"></icon><desc>When Gramps comes to stay, the kids tell him the story of how Mum and Dad almost didn't get married. When the kids first met each other, neither family could get used to the other's funny ways and just didn't get along. They fought so much that the wedding planner quit! Will the six kids figure out a way to be a family, or will Mum and Dad be forced to call off their wedding?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107072500 +0000" stop="20230107075500 +0000" catchup-id="ZbYH7wBl0r2gYCtzrV-h7kNEx6Vo30DAP-IWC6k1"><title>The Football Academy : Twins for the Win</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In this episode, we meet nine-year-old twin sisters Kiki and Queenie. We also follow U11 boys Teddy and Miles in their biggest tournament of the year.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107075500 +0000" stop="20230107082500 +0000" catchup-id="n9kwDoshzJkenrzJanFzuj6Fc7qtKStcym5iRw19"><title>The Dengineers : Strictly Come Dancing Den</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107082500 +0000" stop="20230107085500 +0000" catchup-id="7imyAGz1Rll8RVM0Ou4peSApZLXh-573jeZWZAMy"><title>Operation Ouch! : It's Hairy!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/vcopIJ1YLcr4gaT4oNcCZw.jpg"></icon><desc>The doctors put the strength of human hair to the test and find out what makes different colours and types of hair.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107085500 +0000" stop="20230107090000 +0000" catchup-id="WZfHlF87B0CBOGOlc7BopmuRV-nPxRUeCW2GqZGI"><title>Newsround</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/HsG2NEk_PJ2ML7EYnugwRw.jpg"></icon><desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107090000 +0000" stop="20230107093000 +0000" catchup-id="SRSN7NH_Htz8GKb_UPbvTeNUT4b2OymscO_0UqyU"><title>Blue Peter : Iceland Adventure</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ylvd0hPRjbJfR-1aicRhFA.jpg"></icon><desc>Joel and Mwaksy hit the road for an epic Icelandic winter adventure! They visit an active volcano, learn about the effects of global warming whilst climbing a glacier and let loose on the famous black sand beaches off-roading on quad bikes!</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107093000 +0000" stop="20230107100000 +0000" catchup-id="HxHTd6WPSOlWMAhzFuhxMSDlBJllDD7SdSoKbv1P"><title>Deadly Pole to Pole : Guyana Giants</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/95wU6KmftkUlc7CVdUCSsw.jpg"></icon><desc>Steve's epic adventure from the top to the bottom of the planet has reached Guyana in South America. This is a land of jungle giants, and the team is on a search for supersized deadly critters. Steve's first encounter is with a two-metre long snake, but even this giant can't measure up to his next chilling discovery - the world's largest spider. Reaching the size of a dinner plate, it has huge venom-injecting fangs that it uses to hunt birds and snakes. Next Steve heads out onto the sun-baked savannah to track down a titanic termite terminator, the giant anteater. Finally Steve climbs 40 metres up into the trees to find a colossal canopy killer, the majestic but rarely seen harpy eagle.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107100000 +0000" stop="20230107110000 +0000" catchup-id="MW0t92yPmZJ5KF3L22lxE9EndgxSD2bM-ngBUqqD"><title>Dogs in the Wild: Meet the Family : Secrets of Success</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The secrets of canid success and their incredible strategies for survival, from leaping jackals to sneezing African wild dogs, and gray foxes that climb trees.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107110000 +0000" stop="20230107120000 +0000" catchup-id="SMQ8QR9nvsM0q93E6EZtd-5o8i5ht1wQvxKWaYsn"><title>World's Weirdest Events</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>In the final episode of this season, Chris Packham's world keeps getting weirder. Chris uncovers the cause of some mysterious holes in the Russian tundra, finds an underwater lake and meets the creator of a cannon built especially for salmon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107120000 +0000" stop="20230107130000 +0000" catchup-id="toHSYVoz4CNRgGoOo8jeQKiOKBIpcSkRyRx2UjEN"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Si and Dave start their new adventure in south Wales, hunting for unique ingredients to include on the menu of a family restaurant that has its eyeson winning a Michelin star.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107130000 +0000" stop="20230107151000 +0000" catchup-id="5X3xTR5YZyFcj2tgKo7_QI2jU52Goy8AtRISDgFh"><title>Dunkirk</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/pGUj9viK1JDkF0C9XhTamw.jpg"></icon><desc>In 1940, more than 338,000 men were taken off Dunkirk beach in an operation that became a legend. This epic film recreates the event.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107151000 +0000" stop="20230107161000 +0000" catchup-id="90P_vHlH8HaHs1W2wfAgtlNJ3cPPBhbABBDU09j3"><title>Natural World : Meet the Moose Family</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KHdf-6B1snGJORhx9i_Fkw.jpg"></icon><desc>In the wilds of the Canadian Rocky Mountains, a mother moose tends to her newborn calf. Spring is in full swing, but this far north, winter is never far away and, with hungry bears and wolves for neighbours, many challenges lie ahead. Local cameraman Hugo Kitching knows this only too well, but he is determined to follow the mother and calf through the four seasons. What unfolds is a very intimate story, and when Hugo finds a second moose calf born late in the year, things take an unexpected and dramatic turn.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107161000 +0000" stop="20230107164000 +0000" catchup-id="hxqMdJDt2kTKNbyOCFJkqS4AnzxA1ugx8ER9H3Wh"><title>Amanda &amp; Alan's Italian Job</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Amanda Holden and Alan Carr take on a project of a lifetime in the sun-kissed hills of rural Sicily. In a bid to breathe new life into forgotten towns, Italian municipalities are selling empty homes for one euro. Fulfilling a long-held ambition, Amanda purchases two dilapidated apartments in picture perfect Salemi and convinces best friend Alan to spend a summer renovating them, with the aim to create an Italian dream home. Arriving at the crumbling property for the first time, seeing the piles of rubbish and abandoned junk, it dawns on them that this is no holiday.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107164000 +0000" stop="20230107173500 +0000" catchup-id="QY19GfWxjBz1kp0ey2oEb93O0hJsKn1TbsjG6Jbq"><title>Flog It!</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Members of the public bring their antiques to be viewed and valued.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107173500 +0000" stop="20230107193000 +0000" catchup-id="FFku5xwAmq83m6UetbnctyS_VLsSzpDm-V9uZZLC"><title>The Guernsey Literary and Potato Peel Pie Society</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/VdWdVpaiS97WFc8MHQOokQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Historical drama set in the aftermath of World War II, about the Nazi invasion of Guernsey. While the Guernsey Literary and Potato Peel Pie Society was initially created in 1941 as a cover story for islanders defying the curfew imposed by their occupiers, it catches the eye of London-based author Juliet some five years later after the end of the war. Keen to learn more about the story behind the book club, she travels to meet the society's members - intent on penning her own novel about them</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107193000 +0000" stop="20230107200000 +0000" catchup-id="ADoAN75_3KOv4JCuPsxhJIwPOiP5SSC6_NgSZzH9"><title>Dad's Army : Don't Fence Me In</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/juDDWRwkKHZEdmITDYBNhQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107200000 +0000" stop="20230107210000 +0000" catchup-id="ovyLDQhpDGdCks6jR9KkwQqT53wBp23Ovuv0f9CM"><title>Rod Stewart at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Rod Stewart has already been honoured with one BBC celebration of his great career, but the man Elton John called Phyllis has had so many hits and is held in such affection by his army of fans that it's time for another deep dive into the TV archives. This second collection of songs from the gravel-voiced legend brings us up to date with some of Rod's more recent appearances and features some magic mic-stand-twirling moments from exclusive live shows. Plus rarely seen BBC performances of some of his biggest hits from over the years, including Tonight's the Night, It's a Heartache, Have I Told You Lately and Sailing.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107210000 +0000" stop="20230107213000 +0000" catchup-id="Jv_yYwh0AdqkqAX7kKlE_83iIorihPyN7aJGhUF9"><title>Rod Stewart: Reel Stories</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>How do you go from Rod the Mod to Sir Roderick Stewart? Dermot O'Leary sits down with the man himself to find out. From Abbey Road to the Albert Hall, Motown to Maggie May - Dermot takes Rod back to his childhood cinema to relive moments from a career spanning six decades. In previous episodes, Reel Stories has taken a front row seat with Kylie Minogue and Noel Gallagher, but this time we are going all the way back to the swinging sixties.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107213000 +0000" stop="20230107223500 +0000" catchup-id="wveq12fQKE46jhgV4cTaH01I33mdqrTMAKRlPAPN"><title>Rod Stewart: Live at Hyde Park</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/MkaxjpT3TRBnw9G1iW6-Xw.jpg"></icon><desc>On a sunny day in September 2015, Rod Stewart took to the stage in London's Hyde Park to bring to a close BBC Radio 2's annual Festival in a Day. In front of 50,000 people, Rod delivered not his usual stadium set but a bespoke selection of hits from his back catalogue spanning his career, including Gasoline Alley, Angel, In a Broken Dream and The Killing of Georgie (Part 1 &amp; 2), plus Faces classics such as Ooh La La and the blues standard Rollin' and Tumblin', a number that Rod used to perform with Long John Baldry back in the day. To close the set, Rod brought on his old pal guitarist Jim Cregan to help him perform his 1978 hit I Was Only Joking. All in all, a memorable and unique concert that is unlikely to be repeated anytime soon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230107223500 +0000" stop="20230108000000 +0000" catchup-id="FwHrispd-XVh4i2pHgt6WLbWHIG9KBtIAvY5iaiP"><title>Imagine : Rod Stewart: Can't Stop Me Now</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/oLYN1HV3OGywWqRXjEhbCg.jpg"></icon><desc>From beatnik to mod, from folkie to disco tart, from glam rocker to, most recently, crooner of American standards, the newly ennobled Sir Roderick Stewart has had a remarkable musical journey. Alan Yentob visits Rod at his homes in Beverly Hills and Essex and talks to his friends and family, including all eight children aged from two years old to 50. Featuring rare archival footage of Rod when he was barely out of his teens and living above his parents' north London sweetshop, in a revised repeat Imagine examines an entertaining career across five musical decades.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108000000 +0000" stop="20230108010000 +0000" catchup-id="xKQPS5ecopyIDZOQ-NoOF0li1swLfvbhoyjptmuf"><title>Rod Stewart at the BBC</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Compilation of Rod Stewart's finest performances at the BBC. We revisit the early 70s with The Faces performing Stay with Me and Three Button Hand Me Down on Sounds for Saturday. The BBC charted Rod's solo success over the years and there are classic performances and interviews that will make you dance, sing and pull on your heartstrings. Songs include Sailing, You're in My Heart, I Don't Want to Talk about It and Do Ya Think I'm Sexy? We also have Rod's performance from Glastonbury 2002 of the classic Handbags and Gladrags, and we dip into the Great American Songbook with his version of the Dorothy Fields classic I'm in the Mood for Love. Finally, rounding off over five decades in music is a performance from Rod's Radio 2 concert from May 2013.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108010000 +0000" stop="20230108020500 +0000" catchup-id="lySeqANuEuohUBBV1S0y79VOPgRWqC4WBnVqmzIL"><title>The Old Grey Whistle Test : Rod Stewart Christmas Concert</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The Old Grey Whistle Test presents Rod's Christmas Concert featuring The Rod Stewart Group performing on stage at Olympia, London. With a new introduction to the 1976 programme by Bob Harris, the performances include Maggie May, Sailing, Tonight's the Night and I Don't Want to Talk About It.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108020500 +0000" stop="20230108033000 +0000" catchup-id="T-lmtaI11IvLcnmxbBDQoMnU6hDHJJuV-rD1UtaA"><title>The Producers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/4bO0i3N07_xCAw7IAAQmWQ.jpg"></icon><desc>A struggling producer and timid accountant scheme to make money by putting on a Broadway show they know will flop, so none of the numerous investors will expect their cash back. A tasteless glorification of Hitler and the Nazis looks guaranteed to fail.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108033000 +0000" stop="20230108043000 +0000" catchup-id="ImV5Ii_1XRwS-aC0qFlRIXlLkcjkU-DMvR5VscUT"><title>The Mayfair Hotel Megabuild</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Although it looks like business as usual at Claridge's - one of London's most luxurious five-star hotels, set in the heart of Mayfair - beneath the surface of the exclusive hotel, filled with glamorous guests who enjoy the finer things in life, is a busy building site. An extraordinary engineering project is underway, which seeks to add a five-story basement at the bottom and 72 new rooms and suites spread over three new floors at the top. But the owners are insistent that the hotel must remain open throughout the build, with the guests oblivious to the noise surrounding them - leading the miners to tunnel by hand. Filmed over six years, this series follows the building team and the hotel staff as they try to complete the build with as little disruption as possible to the hotel's array of high-profile guests.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108043000 +0000" stop="20230108063500 +0000" catchup-id="VQw7YuV0hjaDM3tszsRMcEMNuKUzoOb7F4kW5jvo"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108063500 +0000" stop="20230108073000 +0000" catchup-id="1A8rqRnFLEt_KKpjKjvKWzpvlk5Lv6XpsLHGT-nE"><title>Countryfile : Rural Heritage</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc>John Craven is at the National Hedgelaying Championships as competitors go chainsaw to chainsaw, billhook to billhook in a bid to claim the coveted title as they set about specific regional styles and work against the clock. John gets a lesson in the Midland Bullock style and finds out why hedgerows are so important to our countryside. He also discovers the Cornish hedge tradition reckoned to be as old as the pyramids, and he delves into the Countryfile archives to celebrate rural heritage skills, revisiting the time Anita Rani met a traditional cricket bat maker and when Matt Baker helped with the ancient craft of wheelwrighting.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108073000 +0000" stop="20230108083000 +0000" catchup-id="5OAnMa9i519Z4i6Y9hpscgDLizyn9mj2lQa5-QQI"><title>Coast Great Guides : East Anglia</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Neil Oliver and Tessa Dunlop present the ultimate guide to East Anglia - from The Wash to Canvey Island. Building on the best of ten years of Coast stories from these shores, Neil takes to the sea on a variety of boats to seek out new stories for the Great Guide and bring well-known ones up to date, from seal-watching at England's biggest grey seal colony to extreme coastal erosion at Happisburgh. From its earliest prehistory, Neil explores the incredible stories that underpin this coastline, which was once our land bridge to the continent, and he also celebrates more recent times with a trip aboard a floating relic of the herring industry. Neil finishes his exploration at Orford Ness, where the battle between sea and land is still being fought out - and where one of East Anglia's most distinctive landmarks is at risk from the encroaching waters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108083000 +0000" stop="20230108090000 +0000" catchup-id="bgvxYUFu9HjFWTl669HPyyaWbK8TAGQ4kbzbPSJ5"><title>Weatherman Walking: The Welsh Coast : Cadair Idris &amp; Craig y Nos</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Week two's walks have something for everyone. Cadair Idris is a mountain steeped in legend and mythology; it's also one of Wales' most spectacular summits. Derek's climbing to three peaks in this range and even braving a quick dip in its glacial lake. In the Brecon Beacons, it's a much more relaxing route with singer and broadcaster Beverley Humphreys. Together, they're walking in the footsteps of one of history's most impressive sopranos, Madame Adelina Patti, exploring her former castle estate at Craig Y Nos Country Park.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108090000 +0000" stop="20230108100000 +0000" catchup-id="NnqSMnto66b1DsgqSjTugUyR7ew0emc1UQCI7bV1"><title>Around the World in 80 Gardens : Mexico and Cuba</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/P9LZb2v6iijT_rOJybsOgg.jpg"></icon><desc>Monty Don visits the world's 80 most inspiring gardens. This epic garden adventure starts when Monty travels to two very different but neighbouring countries. Mexico is one of the most plant-rich and artistic cultures on the planet, from the ancient water gardens of Mexico City, to the modernist extremes of Luis Barragan and a surrealist fantasy hidden in the rainforest. Travelling to the Caribbean island of Cuba, Monty discovers that the crumbling colonial grandeur of its urban landscape is now host to a very green revolution.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108100000 +0000" stop="20230108113000 +0000" catchup-id="sUxTi1jW4pTC1_nW3EWhmZb6dYeeoY2JAtj88yzi"><title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/RP_5PKqX4rIMk-YZUlBkXg.jpg"></icon><desc>Matt Tebbutt takes a look back at some of his favourite recipes and best moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108113000 +0000" stop="20230108123000 +0000" catchup-id="yvfJoDrHPJ-6jd2KO8yMN_eF9jteHkNBsjZ6szbo"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dave and Si continue their adventure in Glasgow, on the hunt for new ingredients to include on the menu of a Scottish-Malaysian fusion restaurant.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108123000 +0000" stop="20230108130000 +0000" catchup-id="QUyCFy6Gf3mjYoelmZ-9gqrz-s4TOVTXdo6V4Fx9"><title>Tom Kerridge's Fresh Start : Get Cooking</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ueqbGQ4aopu85wqGew4xzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom recruits eight families keen to change their lives for the better. The first step of his plan is to simply get the families cooking more. To spur them on, he presents all the families with a goody box containing a starter pack of easy recipes and the ingredients for sausage and mash - a Tom Kerridge favourite. Instead of traditional mash, Tom's recipe uses sweet potato and swede. Chris and Kerry, arguably the least experienced cooks in the group, struggle a bit with the instructions, but eventually sit down to the first meal they have cooked together in 15 years.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108130000 +0000" stop="20230108171500 +0000" catchup-id="CSqnTFMkwLq05ocbjlU9gC50eqsO8wV38oRlhfdD"><title>Masters Snooker : First Round: Neil Robertson v Shaun Murphy</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108171500 +0000" stop="20230108181500 +0000" catchup-id="ZUMYESWZqxX7ISvHyKMOvTVM9SAchY_R8cq3Rvkl"><title>Flog It! : Wallasey 30</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Paul Martin presents from Wallasey Town Hall on the banks of the River Mersey. Antiques experts Philip Serrell and Nick Davies get to meet people from all over Merseyside who have brought in their antiques and collectibles to receive a valuation. Paul gets special permission to go behind the scenes with National Museums Liverpool to find out how they preserve the millions of often priceless objects that are in their care at the Conservation Studios in the city centre. Paul also heads to the stately grandeur of Dunham Massey, which was a military hospital during the First World War. He explores an ambitious project which brings that significant time back to life.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108181500 +0000" stop="20230108190000 +0000" catchup-id="JWO9g0Do6Zc3fQnbhEStAZ6WC4Q1eeZj0Y8cQ6j_"><title>Ski Sunday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/kB9Mj5P5ngW4vJ6DkWewZA.jpg"></icon><desc>Ski Sunday returns with the best action and stories from the world of snow sports. The series kicks off with the classic slalom race in Adelboden, featuring history maker Dave Ryding. Known as The Rocket, Ryding became the first Brit to win a World Cup alpine skiing event in 2022. His triumph came in the Kitzbühel slalom – can he repeat the trick across the border in Switzerland? Later in the show, Jenny Jones travels to the USA to meet the incredible Vasu Sojitra, an amputee who hikes and then shreds the biggest mountains with an unmatched style and passion.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108190000 +0000" stop="20230108200000 +0000" catchup-id="oa_G0who07h_0uD8exgNKu4BnxfidGdDr7EU7CKL"><title>Countryfile : Shooting Estate</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc>Love it or hate it, shooting contributes around £2 billion to the rural economy. But it's a sporting industry under the cosh, as the UK is gripped by the worst ever outbreak of avian flu. Can game bird shoots survive the 21st century? Charlotte explores the 12,500 acre Rhug Estate in north Wales to see what it means to be a traditional shooting estate in the modern world and looks at how it contributes to local business. Sean is in Perthshire on the 1,300 acre Bamff Estate, which has eschewed shooting for eco-tourism, including a colony of beavers. Tom is in Wiltshire to investigate the threat posed by avian flu to the industry, and in the Cotswolds, Adam puts his new sheepdog Gwen through her paces. Will she pass muster?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108200000 +0000" stop="20230108210000 +0000" catchup-id="QIjqbdaYOzPvTeED9FKjqO_GUy8NZ2LrKJZCS9i5"><title>Digging for Britain : Arthur's Stone and a Georgian Mine</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/LJ8awR8hj0JbnL4YR0XcGw.jpg"></icon><desc>In the west of the UK, a spectacular monument older than Stonehenge, a 200-year-old mine trapped in time and a lost medieval friary.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108210000 +0000" stop="20230108220000 +0000" catchup-id="DT43motBkZui3othpMuqAJYcIGxQpVedSWcEakh3"><title>Antiques Roadshow : Bodnant Garden 2</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/3bzLUHsDZ7qzi7YPXgOBzg.jpg"></icon><desc>Fiona Bruce and the team are at Bodnant Garden in north Wales, where finds include a pair of rare Wedgewood tigers, a carved Russian chair and a silver box with a political connection. There is also some interesting art work: a picture from one of the great Parisian naturalist artists and an original Quentin Blake.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108220000 +0000" stop="20230108235500 +0000" catchup-id="rOMLjloKBlXl9K-iffG5ZppQBM3VCn69VbUHsFAv"><title>Mary Queen of Scots</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/iuda7TZQZnfF3qzx4sXfCg.jpg"></icon><desc>Historical drama chronicling Mary Stuart's attempts in the 16th century to overthrow her cousin, Elizabeth I, and claim the English throne. Married at 15 and returning to her native Scotland as a widow at the age of 18, a story of betrayal and conspiracy ensues as her efforts result in imprisonment and a death sentence.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230108235500 +0000" stop="20230109004500 +0000" catchup-id="-9-Rt8XdOx3Tv4A1AiAZZqUo8UaoTBDZ-1YUo-vp"><title>Masters Snooker Highlights : Day 1</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights from the first day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109004500 +0000" stop="20230109024500 +0000" catchup-id="RMm0k7UT3PA9-wnBRhGi8oWmIdfL4ixf3c_gO_eT"><title>Masters Snooker Extra : Day 1</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Extra coverage from the first day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109024500 +0000" stop="20230109034500 +0000" catchup-id="NGrgHIt-4PndQ1gD_y5ZqCzgpUfL-14-2AsH21cy"><title>Signed: I'm An Alcoholic: Inside Recovery</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Alcoholics Anonymous is the longest-running addiction programme in the world and has been operating in the UK for 75 years. At a time when problem drinking is on the rise, this film has access to an AA meeting in central England for the first time ever. Rooted in the evangelical Christianity of 1930s America, many of the cornerstones of the programme's structure have changed little. How does this organisation work in our modern society? How do members with no faith at all interpret the programme now, and why does it still work for so many?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109034500 +0000" stop="20230109043000 +0000" catchup-id="1ad7ho6txF8aBmowR1QmoPHUl1ACUSFferqRE1Rx"><title>Signed: The Travelling Auctioneers</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109043000 +0000" stop="20230109063000 +0000" catchup-id="IuCoj6fBPn3TS_4B-via2W640rdrUb_GWs2nvhBX"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109063000 +0000" stop="20230109071500 +0000" catchup-id="oGvf120vKIv18VjH0XZRqbUaqCvG4dHEki1jI1KJ"><title>Bargain Hunt : Llandeilo 18</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_n4I9rQNXfb1yt_rdabD_Q.jpg"></icon><desc>Christina Trevanion heads to an antiques fair in the town of Llandeilo in West Wales, where experts Philip Serrell and Charles Hanson help the red and blue teams as they compete to see who can buy the three most profitable items to take to auction. Christina also gets hands-on with the ancient art of silversmithing at a family business in the heart of nearby town Laugharne.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109071500 +0000" stop="20230109080000 +0000" catchup-id="kumJ7xehBpe8I8nwTZcG4ceUNGfu7kwUQIISwfqW"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dom welcomes willow weaver Dea and artist Gemma into the marquee. With chronic fatigue syndrome along with autism and ADHD, Dea dreams of being able to build a home business that suits her life. Mentor Eddie can see she has the skill to succeed, but can Dea make her pieces fast enough and market them with the confidence needed to turn her hobby into a full-time job? After being told art doesn’t pay by a careers advisor at school, Gemma gave up on her artistic dreams and became a teacher. She continued to create art as a hobby and after some recent success selling her art at a market she’s hoping mentor Sharon can help her finally become a full-time artist. With just eight weeks to show they can make their dreams a reality, Dea and Gemma must work around the clock to build new lives for themselves.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109080000 +0000" stop="20230109090000 +0000" catchup-id="eR8jF_dk3_vGifoisWfPnLwpSUCBTcvSiTKVrrXR"><title>Signed: Antiques Roadshow : Toys &amp; Childhood Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/3bzLUHsDZ7qzi7YPXgOBzg.jpg"></icon><desc>A special episode about the toys we love and how they’ve shaped our childhood, from Sindy and Action Man to Subbuteo and Lego. With a guest appearance by Jonathan Ross.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109090000 +0000" stop="20230109100000 +0000" catchup-id="HfJHpJ8S996mMq5--hnRUpXzG7geOJaY1BPV9XiD"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109100000 +0000" stop="20230109121500 +0000" catchup-id="mphfUDxaDkPvMmQtUKmcjfxKW-qopt92v5rwuxv2"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109121500 +0000" stop="20230109130000 +0000" catchup-id="75K7-VtKKwNdr_GUXcbqRNAU7LGIksNdtCr6Ifo2"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109130000 +0000" stop="20230109171500 +0000" catchup-id="tShTZfXXVz6RmMbMER-7xH75mPnU0He9TTzlZGV8"><title>Snooker: The Masters : First Round: Ronnie O'Sullivan v Luca Brecel</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109171500 +0000" stop="20230109180000 +0000" catchup-id="ELGVVgqtWAHNVotvkQH_rRknOjaVpIDKe11HCx_J"><title>Flog It! : Morecambe 13</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Flog It! comes from the Platform in Morecambe, Lancashire, which in its day was the main station bringing holidaymakers to the town. Antiques experts Charles Hanson and Catherine Southon find treasures to take to auction, including a vintage Rolex watch. Paul Martin discovers the rags-to-riches story of the town's most famous son, Eric Morecambe.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109180000 +0000" stop="20230109183000 +0000" catchup-id="Y01nqdbEWLYRkv7ECCFfZgfrBlhOUftBW1nNXXpJ"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 19: Monday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Jasmine Harman, Dave Johns, Professor Suzannah Lipscomb and Jason Mohammad take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109183000 +0000" stop="20230109190000 +0000" catchup-id="pGxuLNM8rzrBrW1-qVs6cCafLs29vW7NSbUSbSXu"><title>Take a Hike : Bruce's Walk, Dunvegan and Coral Beach</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109190000 +0000" stop="20230109193000 +0000" catchup-id="W4UfRgtSxR4mmusdaFblmxkjDC7wjuRTQKDAS3cM"><title>Nadiya's Fast Flavours : Comfort Food</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/osguFDRUEyBE3zwa8U5KNg.jpg"></icon><desc>Nadiya injects a joyful spark into our cooking with her flavour-packed comfort food, from a warming beef curry and parathas to custard French toast with pistachio syrup.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109193000 +0000" stop="20230109200000 +0000" catchup-id="C1nhdYIhMut-3qQu78w7QOfBPkj3UT5iW62ezlzC"><title>Mastermind</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/2x2bAg5oZd-Vt9Cw9pfaCw.jpg"></icon><desc>Another four contenders take to the black chair, answering questions on their chosen specialist subjects to earn a place in the semi-finals. Clive Myrie hosts an episode where the specialist subjects are Stephen Hawking, the music of Radiohead, Theda Bara and the Richard Sharpe novels of Bernard Cornwell.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109200000 +0000" stop="20230109203000 +0000" catchup-id="VE-dYTnwBHV7Gcf-_yXqAMeUhvYUBvaezpIac7WI"><title>Only Connect : Scrummagers v Croot Family</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/-dwHFg_l7ZoJCCwKGGBPXQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109203000 +0000" stop="20230109210000 +0000" catchup-id="XoVRvLuQz8JPl3o1KGs3B3tJr1fon7OZnz2ahNdM"><title>University Challenge</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/DthQg2qIu4T3wO2ltne1Hg.jpg"></icon><desc>The second round continues tonight, with two more teams competing for a place in the quarter-finals. Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109210000 +0000" stop="20230109220000 +0000" catchup-id="Y040fyYSAg6pmr5aMizKKSnJ1dqN0K1OV0al8e-9"><title>The Mayfair Hotel Megabuild</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>It's just over halfway through the seven-year renovation project, and the team have adopted unusual measures to make way for the next stage of the audacious build - a four-storey roof extension. Meanwhile, below ground, the basement reaches its fifth and deepest level after overcoming the challenges of groundwater and an underground river. But then disaster strikes as world events intervene. The Covid-19 pandemic forces the hotel to close for the first time in over a century, as well as derailing plans to complete the building work on time.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109220000 +0000" stop="20230109223000 +0000" catchup-id="zVBhl8mRv63tsmLrbR-8i-gC5XyQFRL8v37q5gab"><title>QI : Ticks Tax Toes</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mWzi8A0HiCWq5DjM2FsZkQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109223000 +0000" stop="20230109231500 +0000" catchup-id="MRxbrBjg8q2WAZ6nssTXoOOkyYWMPve6FzT1vkld"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230109231500 +0000" stop="20230110000500 +0000" catchup-id="2N2Vgxd-kXk-FJN2Mc71Qop6CZlBX1Hm08uZQmyB"><title>Masters Snooker Highlights : Day 2</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Extra coverage from the second day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110000500 +0000" stop="20230110020500 +0000" catchup-id="ryfcXWebyF-NT1NaTUgxgibNb6TFjNZ9OFBTsydE"><title>Masters Snooker Extra : Day 2</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Extra coverage from the second day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110020500 +0000" stop="20230110030000 +0000" catchup-id="U6BnEk3cNWQs5xVdqjoVm80jl5Z_V72BOC_UCjGW"><title>Signed: Countryfile : Rural Heritage</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/OmIgbtzITYU0rcuGfMFGUg.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110030000 +0000" stop="20230110040000 +0000" catchup-id="vm1NWavnEqTqCnjzQXGNNsQto_43MNBRUXsGi2rN"><title>Signed: Miriam Margolyes: Australia Unmasked</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>On the first leg of her adventure, Miriam Margolyes is confronted with the complexities of Tasmania’s rich history. She meets those still fighting for a 'fair go'.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110040000 +0000" stop="20230110050000 +0000" catchup-id="U4pSn_1K_NRUSE2-XOaN-iVE1DJKU7KKXg5xiUfs"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Tempers around the round table are more frayed than ever as another player is sent home. With the traitors set to murder again, the faithful are even more determined to catch a traitor in the act. But not even the traitors are prepared for the surprises in store during the mission, as Claudia proves that the castle really is full of secrets.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110050000 +0000" stop="20230110063000 +0000" catchup-id="G3-JuFegT60c561X2zzbBOQ3Lh8DnulgFSRf6-4D"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110063000 +0000" stop="20230110071500 +0000" catchup-id="JxDH_8AyT8pNgoLpDcTVmETlARxmsdGD5dqwKFQw"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Melplash Show</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Diana and Nigel are devoted to all the animals on their Devon farm, but Diana's shire horses hold a special place in her heart. After an impressive career in the competition ring with beloved horse Tilly, this year’s Melplash Show will be their swansong, and emotions are running high. Meanwhile, Barry and Jess are gearing up to leave their Dorset farm for the day. After Barry has calmed down his bees and treated his pig to some homemade jam, this committed duo can finally get their heads in the game and try their best to rack up some rosette wins with their finest Suffolk sheep.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110071500 +0000" stop="20230110080000 +0000" catchup-id="hFKriVDU5SoiOuR3WpXZ8LiJoTTGfWYT9ZHZ7zOQ"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Two makers from opposite ends of the country arrive at Dom Chinea’s Maker’s Marquee, hoping he and his team can help to change their lives. Emmy from Devon is a talented glassmaker returning to her craft after an eight-year break, and Zita is an ambitious textile designer from Fife hoping to swap her day job for her own business. Zita’s mentor Piyush loves her eye for colour and design but isn’t keen on the tools and techniques she’s using. Zita loves working with a sackcloth jute fabric, but Piyush is concerned it doesn’t feel high-end enough. Will sustainability champion Zita stick to her guns or take on Piyush’s advice to embrace alternatives to jute to widen her market and improve the quality of her textiles? Meanwhile, mentor Allister is so impressed with Emmy’s glassmaking skills that he has grand plans for her pieces, but can she live up to his high expectations? With only two months to turn their skills and love of making into moneymaking businesses, can they make it at market?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110080000 +0000" stop="20230110090000 +0000" catchup-id="fv4jqEhMCMfLEm_T-hBLD3yXqyTmvoIXOiBP-cM4"><title>Signed: Digging for Britain : Roman Towns and Tudor Shipwrecks</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/LJ8awR8hj0JbnL4YR0XcGw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110090000 +0000" stop="20230110100000 +0000" catchup-id="-7Ku_6L1VrTYC8l9PbhyWIC0VzB3nK42k7hfx5Im"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110100000 +0000" stop="20230110121500 +0000" catchup-id="VtsBwzOILHzH2ec8WwE-Ee3syB9WMJtt4sQRYsbs"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110121500 +0000" stop="20230110130000 +0000" catchup-id="HdjdC3pafz76k1kWPbDD1lOaBkWSVTQy7yijX1wO"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110130000 +0000" stop="20230110171500 +0000" catchup-id="gq07pBker3xtC1tsb2WzvIPKSWL5vCBtnzTpkIdo"><title>Snooker: The Masters : First Round: Mark Allen v Barry Hawkins</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110171500 +0000" stop="20230110180000 +0000" catchup-id="oTdEc_2T73M-uDLjgdF4066uNOaMzqBeUbKRLfRE"><title>Flog It! : Compilation - Coughton Court 17</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110180000 +0000" stop="20230110183000 +0000" catchup-id="hzUFQZPIvErZlzAEujaI__qPF5jA4TUUTBF7nDRO"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 19: Tuesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Jasmine Harman, Dave Johns, Professor Suzannah Lipscomb and Jason Mohammad take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110183000 +0000" stop="20230110190000 +0000" catchup-id="Bydw-O_lCG7pkT3KNLBzoE3fz4Opxa5HoYp1a3O2"><title>Take a Hike : Sorley's Walk, Loch Coruisk</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110190000 +0000" stop="20230110200000 +0000" catchup-id="DrQDRAyZIeOzDZVhAo88vWsQzm-m_4H3X1xOeVGW"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Ronnie and Pete prepare for a leggy new arrival, Joanna embarks on a steep learning curve, and young farmer Sean nears the end of a bumper lambing season.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110200000 +0000" stop="20230110210000 +0000" catchup-id="saVaTjNjS8wtoOWLrZ77S8HXQObfUukDm-n0s7mO"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The Bikers continue their adventure in Norfolk, one of their favourite parts of the world. Both Dave and Si are big fans of the seafood that can be found in the county’s 90 miles of shoreline, but this time they’re heading inland towards East Barsham, a tiny village close to the market town of Fakenham, to meet Jake and his partner Terri. The couple have only recently taken over the Barsham Arms, a country pub that’s doing a great job of attracting the locals to their 40-seat restaurant. But to keep the locals coming back for more, they need to keep the menu fresh, and that means finding a steady stream of new produce for Jake to play with. The Bikers meet Jake, and through his flamboyant scone and lamb dishes, learn they need to find produce to include on the menu that’s as creative as his cooking.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110210000 +0000" stop="20230110220000 +0000" catchup-id="xq8mHdZGCLZvCUtkpF9iiwab0UMLjKg02Q6UTqfF"><title>Miriam Margolyes: Australia Unmasked</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>As an 80-year-old woman, Miriam has never felt more vulnerable. And her own situation has left her concerned about the fair go for the most vulnerable in society today. On this last leg of her journey, Miriam travels through the state of South Australia. Along the way, she tackles ageism, experiences an eye-opening stay at a nudist club, and discovers vulnerable individuals and communities whose lives still hang in the balance.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110220000 +0000" stop="20230110223000 +0000" catchup-id="hOFcH7XUvtM0ygvFusIIC0Rm0HxJUR7xsjtsDjJl"><title>Detectorists</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Gsw0l04x4-owX9aSN3P_tA.jpg"></icon><desc>Lance and Andy haven't told anyone that they are hot on the trail of the holy grail of metal detecting - the final resting place of King Sexred of the East Saxons. But members of the rival detecting club already seem to know all about it. Who is the mole?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110223000 +0000" stop="20230110231500 +0000" catchup-id="X_VSyWiYrvGD2efIxE-doTGdAO6I9qfA3-VgVgFL"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230110231500 +0000" stop="20230111000500 +0000" catchup-id="ttGaFKCs8OKR_QRf7z6n7wzzCDsXWMIuhfKt8VMn"><title>Masters Snooker Highlights : Day 3</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights from the third day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111000500 +0000" stop="20230111020500 +0000" catchup-id="LjfoOvIu-5EHIoq6ln-tsca3CpRgoz9OoqVVZZ0i"><title>Masters Snooker Extra : Day 3</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Extra coverage from the third day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111020500 +0000" stop="20230111030500 +0000" catchup-id="yxD9f9WumvS-cy3QAyslaO-mt2nl4ruMpf4n35JH"><title>Digging for Britain : Arthur's Stone and a Georgian Mine</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/LJ8awR8hj0JbnL4YR0XcGw.jpg"></icon><desc>In the west of the UK, a spectacular monument older than Stonehenge, a 200-year-old mine trapped in time and a lost medieval friary.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111030500 +0000" stop="20230111035000 +0000" catchup-id="hRs0bsRPcHg2Ex2f5Y26Yns95-mffQAL7FIgmoWS"><title>Signed: Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, fine art expert Kate Bliss, top trader Linda Lambert and master upholsterer Anthony Devine head to Monmouth to scour its antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets for items that will make them a huge profit. Then we follow them over the next three weeks in their quest to sell their items on for as much cash as they can. Will Anthony upholster his crummy old couch in time or will he miss the deadline to turn his sofa into money? Will Kate's mysterious pendant prove to be the money-making jewel she hopes it to be? And will Linda find anyone desperate to buy a church pew? At the end of it all, who will make the most flipping profit?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111035000 +0000" stop="20230111045000 +0000" catchup-id="FyXuoDaXbd-wlr4fp_0BE0Eju_VbwFLo3UxUioOd"><title>Signed: Tokyo Vice : The Test</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/STmQdajjq7jPH9kv3UxtKg.jpg"></icon><desc>Young journalist Jake Adelstein, determined to make it in Tokyo, becomes the first foreigner to be hired by Tokyo newspaper Meicho Shimbun. Assigned to the crime desk and tasked with covering a stabbing, Jake becomes convinced the case is connected to something much bigger, but he discovers that, in Tokyo, journalists don't ask too many questions - if they know what's good for them. In English and Japanese with English subtitles.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111045000 +0000" stop="20230111063000 +0000" catchup-id="YmPSa0HPRHo-wAkZ6LXRS82eXMytgyV4vO5i_k7H"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111063000 +0000" stop="20230111071500 +0000" catchup-id="E_m3ZLaDrVSp7IiYMxzSZJzvJyTNMqBO4oI4cMhg"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Royal Welsh Show - Pigs</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Morgan and Tasha have only been pig farmers for a couple of years, but with over 100 pigs on their rented land near Prestatyn, they definitely mean business. However, funding their young farm is a constant concern. As first timers at the Royal Welsh Show, they want their Duroc pigs to turn the judge’s head, in particular their favourite boar, Sully. Meanwhile, Amanda’s farm near Abergavenny is home to her beloved Saddleback pigs. Looking after her latest litter of curious piglets is a full-on task, but she is passionate about rearing the best of breed and is a past master in the competition ring. She also wants rosette wins at the Royal Welsh to seal her reputation as a pedigree breeder. Show day brings the hottest temperature ever recorded in Wales, and the pigs need to be kept cool and comfortable while the farmers weather an unpredictable day of judging.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111071500 +0000" stop="20230111080000 +0000" catchup-id="wfzhrj2PeYPbEARmJ84k2yoMcTBzHQVC-RA3H8yc"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Blacksmith Alex needs to overcome his imposter syndrome to fulfil his potential. For furniture maker Cora, it’s about focusing on her strengths as a designer rather than a maker.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111080000 +0000" stop="20230111083000 +0000" catchup-id="ZjC_8ABT4qnf9-_Ua8LiqB1kUke-LIAYayPVMWmd"><title>See Hear : On Tour: Best Of</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ueAmDj_irz8MdgbkftyL0Q.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111083000 +0000" stop="20230111090000 +0000" catchup-id="COWEYkyqLnXyV5497C9daXTnTN3FdrSyUkTRM1S-"><title>Signed: A Countryside Winter</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Gethin Jones delivers the ultimate guide to a countryside winter featuring wildlife, food, gardening and outdoor adventure, all brought to you by a selection of favourite BBC faces. In this episode, wildlife artist and cameraman Robert Fuller shows us what wildlife species are thriving around his Yorkshire farm, and Sean Fletcher tries an extreme sport with a difference - winter cod fishing. Nigel Slater cooks up the perfect dish to welcome you in after a cold day, hearty stuffed squash.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111090000 +0000" stop="20230111100000 +0000" catchup-id="W4J0gnCT6rTu5WxFQfNa452VDBNTxdQVuw_TIVnU"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111100000 +0000" stop="20230111111500 +0000" catchup-id="8UOR9NqmAa19WoKRR1OIvLP4kgkBRoR1kRJUECY3"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111111500 +0000" stop="20230111130000 +0000" catchup-id="Et7VI65RAJgAYlNrLItKN6vuYkf8M-kgqsBdCb_l"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111130000 +0000" stop="20230111171500 +0000" catchup-id="Y_nClmMzj_5jUpK2SsrcoF_yLCI08xDCV_3EhZG0"><title>Snooker: The Masters : First Round: Judd Trump v Ryan Day</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111171500 +0000" stop="20230111180000 +0000" catchup-id="x-EKP7ctvIcDT56CE0jYue0CbTR-cTaPgzh92_xr"><title>Flog It! : Grimsby</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>Flog It! comes from Grimsby Minster in north east Lincolnshire. It's close to the famous port that once housed 600 fishing vessels. Antiques experts Christina Trevanion and Anita Manning find treasures among the hundreds of visitors to take to auction. Anita is entranced by some pigeon racing memorabilia and Christina uncovers a rare Chinese silver butter bowl. Paul Martin explores the battle faced by a Lincolnshire lord as he struggled between loyalty and duty during a royal scandal.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111180000 +0000" stop="20230111183000 +0000" catchup-id="Th5epbispmCu4S0TuwNxVMH8PlfsYgKaYm-IaxdP"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 19: Wednesday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Jasmine Harman, Dave Johns, Professor Suzannah Lipscomb and Jason Mohammad take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111183000 +0000" stop="20230111190000 +0000" catchup-id="1JFSMR6fM_JoFoEySyr_vMD4nrXtSTC1PdtDIl41"><title>Take a Hike : Fiona's Walk, Rubha Hunish</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111190000 +0000" stop="20230111200000 +0000" catchup-id="ZlUwG3nr7iK0vEsV4rADtmEfgoPGuIPWjmAo30q9"><title>This Farming Life</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/Ze4YmpYL_uzFB0C4cNvB_w.jpg"></icon><desc>Emma and Ewan hatch a plan to breed peacocks, Barbara gets her pumpkin plan off to a strong start, and Ronnie and Pete turn to cutting-edge science.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111200000 +0000" stop="20230111210000 +0000" catchup-id="3yXl3G4atKtZS7K9Tf7oYp9BL8sD0NTh32C13q6T"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dave and Si are heading towards Drighlington, to a vegetarian Indian restaurant called Prashad sitting on the outskirts of Leeds and Bradford. It’s run by husband-and-wife team Bobby and Minal, an ambitious couple who are on a journey of their own to create a unique dining experience based on a tasting menu inspired by both Gujarati cuisine and great Yorkshire produce. Bobby and Minal have built up a loyal customer base, winning a host of awards along the way, including a prestigious Michelin Bib Gourmand. But now they have their eyes on an even bigger prize, a coveted Michelin star. And that means creating an even more ambitious menu.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111210000 +0000" stop="20230111220000 +0000" catchup-id="VdxsXucfgV7pVxspNThFioBVBnFKDqlJ8-uvxQUx"><title>Billion Dollar Downfall: The Dealmaker</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>He was welcomed at the White House, met billionaires like Bill Gates and counted cricket legend Imran Khan as a friend. Silent since his 2019 dawn arrest at Heathrow Airport, tycoon Arif Naqvi is now seen and heard for the first time in this documentary. He calls himself the 'flag carrier of impact investing' - the idea that you can get rich while doing good. Naqvi's $14-billion firm Abraaj invested across the developing world, improving businesses and building hospitals. Then it collapsed in the world's biggest-ever private equity failure. Now, Naqvi is accused of fraud and racketeering. If found guilty, he faces 291 years in jail. So what went wrong? In a fresh examination of the meteoric rise and dizzying fall of Abraaj and Arif Naqvi, key figures speak out, while personal videos of Naqvi give a glimpse into his third year of house arrest.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111220000 +0000" stop="20230111223000 +0000" catchup-id="_Ah9t_f17jG9yMPxOZa_MnvxPZIyY89xW0JZ4M7I"><title>Our Flag Means Death</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Stede battles feelings of guilt while hunting for missing hostages. Lucius makes a surprising discovery.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111223000 +0000" stop="20230111231500 +0000" catchup-id="x7gH6lququQi_jZITsoO3XPmOK0IIumF2K5YnodO"><title>Newsnight</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bUQ-JbBOx1dTvpjQEinXPw.jpg"></icon><desc>The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230111231500 +0000" stop="20230112000500 +0000" catchup-id="4DjyK9N4P06yslIUwtZtrOjz3o3uQteTL1VhW69-"><title>Masters Snooker Highlights : Day 4</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights from the fourth day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112000500 +0000" stop="20230112020500 +0000" catchup-id="10H3FZYDXFPVnycSgDlxiuwM5_dHnSYCNFRxndd7"><title>Masters Snooker Extra : Day 4</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Extra coverage from the fourth day of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112020500 +0000" stop="20230112023500 +0000" catchup-id="U2Sqt-e8PCQdIxr1uVnMsAQpawTfmNGRE8zXoORc"><title>See Hear : On Tour: Best Of</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/ueAmDj_irz8MdgbkftyL0Q.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112023500 +0000" stop="20230112033500 +0000" catchup-id="bb3hd8_HASgKsRPjJ1uCBQ8s5KURgIlUzdKTSZ5D"><title>Signed: The Traitors</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>With the stakes getting higher and the faithful feeling like they are on the back foot, can they change the course of the reality game and put the traitors under fire? With life-changing money still at stake, the players must also remain focused on building the prize pot in a mission that sees them sink to new depths of despair. But that’s the least of their worries, with an explosive round table on the horizon.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112033500 +0000" stop="20230112042000 +0000" catchup-id="RkcHxyxVpU9OozCYkDb7P7peiJ2YxqmblmNfXfdv"><title>Signed: Flipping Profit</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>An antiques expert, a market trader and an upcycler battle it out to make the most money for BBC Children in Need. In this episode, antiques expert Caroline Hawley, trader Danny Sebastian and aeronautical engineer/upcycler Stu Abbott head to Buxton to rummage through its antique shops, scrap yards and flea markets in the hope of finding items that they can each turn into a healthy profit. When the day is done and they've got their items, they have just three weeks to turn them into cash. Will Caroline's pretty parasol fetch a pretty price? Can Danny flog his assortment of curios? And what has Stu got planned for those radiators? When the time is up, who will have made the biggest flipping profit?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112042000 +0000" stop="20230112063000 +0000" catchup-id="VbX6pV6O5AvZ4QJPnjnV1KeZ3JAW21N-OiqTzF63"><title>This Is BBC Two</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112063000 +0000" stop="20230112071500 +0000" catchup-id="PCAJ-pf522YfXBa4DtDDu7Id90rTHIgx71YzQzTY"><title>The Farmers' Country Showdown : Ludlow Food Festival - Cider and Meat</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Brothers Denis and Eric have lived and worked on their Herefordshire family farm for nearly 40 years. As well as rearing their native breed cattle, they’re proud of the orchards they’ve tended over the decades, which they now use to make award-winning cider and perry. As experienced sellers at Ludlow Food Festival in Shropshire, they know that serving up plenty of samples and flavours will be a magnet for buyers. Meanwhile, for Powys livestock farmers Joanne and Nigel, it’s all hands on deck getting their hot food stand ready for the hungry hordes of festivalgoers. Luckily, their children, now in their twenties, are on hand to help. For both these farming families, the hard work of being at the festival will be worth it if they win the loyalty of new customers and take home a healthy profit to plough back into their businesses.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112071500 +0000" stop="20230112080000 +0000" catchup-id="R106YPO3LNDiw4Uz4JDqhwBhkjursotzo_w9ePxy"><title>Make It at Market</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Today’s amateur artisans are jeweller Annelies from Glasgow and woodturner Lucinda from Wiltshire, both heading for Dom’s marquee with high hopes of turning their hobbies into their livelihoods. After investing £7k to set up her jewellery business, Annelies needs to see a return on her money. Mentor Rachel loves Annelies’s energy and skill but thinks she now needs to concentrate on higher end and more expensive pieces to boost her profits. Will Annalies listen? Mum of two Lucinda spends what little free time she has in her garage turning wood into stunning make-up brushes. Mentors Barnaby and Dru can see huge potential, but will her first ever market deliver the sales Lucinda needs? With just eight weeks to knuckle down and use the advice they’ve been given, can Annelies and Lucinda show that they have what it takes to become professional makers?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112080000 +0000" stop="20230112090000 +0000" catchup-id="KhuxznVntYblI6ulWR6FsXJirxu-ixr1rFxD_gpK"><title>Signed: Dynasties : Macaque: Monkeys in the Mountains - A Dynasties Special</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/_q0hn4HFVrECdTkTsuVVsA.jpg"></icon><desc>High in the Atlas Mountains of Morocco lives a group of Barbary macaque monkeys. The alpha male, known as Mac, has just battled to win the leadership of the troop. He must now lead and protect them while fending off rivals who still want his crown.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112090000 +0000" stop="20230112100000 +0000" catchup-id="QFpx6UpG_6-HYFi5bTG4BmAKFwrMn4dlsoYYw67x"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112100000 +0000" stop="20230112121500 +0000" catchup-id="2WdEvwivczuWGwqWvFljaRb46Nyf9Gts3IzfKfte"><title>BBC News</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7pjgDGeU9NWa4swtP7iQHA.jpg"></icon><desc>Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112121500 +0000" stop="20230112130000 +0000" catchup-id="HiaPphRetcwKCbzZMfk4hA92Mzf7Y6PB5gSyAPD1"><title>Politics Live</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>The big political issues of the day.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112130000 +0000" stop="20230112171500 +0000" catchup-id="3T951c68nuq_meTFiBVud7Odu7yXGnBvSVwmvAWU"><title>Masters Snooker : Quarter-Final 1</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Live coverage of the first quarter-final of the 2023 Masters.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112171500 +0000" stop="20230112180000 +0000" catchup-id="cEOd0rSjYVm37kTRiVBDmbMv2RwIzR41c6FYPymF"><title>Flog It! : Suffolk 38</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/KuwV1ojBPuDWd3bmUvU2kA.jpg"></icon><desc>In Suffolk, Adam Partridge values two light cavalry swords and a concertina. Plus, Philip Serrell examines an intriguing box of fruit knives and forks.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112180000 +0000" stop="20230112183000 +0000" catchup-id="pp_3qunuHHWjei-PzKk7Uo03b90aiCWo9eKqkZEt"><title>Richard Osman's House of Games : Week 19: Thursday</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7_x_UhYlBBbOn3_Pd-PYYQ.jpg"></icon><desc>Every day this week, celebrity contestants Jasmine Harman, Dave Johns, Professor Suzannah Lipscomb and Jason Mohammad take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games suitcase, or will they be tempted with the House of Games decanter?</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112183000 +0000" stop="20230112190000 +0000" catchup-id="kVMA2dsVjHLNHPawCHnQ9BkWyhcYwVlwjWx2zG7I"><title>Take a Hike : Rhona's Walk, Ashaig Beach</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/7mhsOvShIBS_s9xhU26dnw.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112190000 +0000" stop="20230112200000 +0000" catchup-id="kPJXS4pT_WpCtncSrivwviFfIYShYVihyg92H3LQ"><title>Snooker: The Masters : Quarter-Final 2</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/mR1HIh2hYcsk_BzQrBi2zQ.jpg"></icon><desc></desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112200000 +0000" stop="20230112210000 +0000" catchup-id="txTRA6kK42ePkBNt_QvKPzQDIIsCD8CaMkQl_q0g"><title>The Hairy Bikers Go Local</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Dave and Si are headed to The Stackpole Inn, a multi-award-winning gastro pub in Pembrokeshire. Owners Gary and Becky first took it on 15 years ago. The couple were joined in 2019 by head chef Matt Waldron, who prides himself on using local ingredients - 90 per cent of his menu features food from Pembrokeshire or from within Wales. It's the Bikers' mission to introduce Matt and team Stackpole to the fantastic local food producers that aren't yet on their radar. But first, they have to learn more about what makes their business tick. After enjoying a tasting session of lobster, crab and a dessert made from local strawberries, Dave and Si know they're going to get creative in their bid to introduce Matt to new local suppliers.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112210000 +0000" stop="20230112220000 +0000" catchup-id="UwQNTGm1TSMFhiZseVDI5E-VscD_pAHsr1CTNkZa"><title>Marie Antoinette : Pick a Princess</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/G5pUPFHfhYlWOWGmb3kRWA.jpg"></icon><desc>The royal family holidays at Fontainebleau, an escape from stifling Versailles. Marie’s hostilities with du Barry threaten to sour things with the King. Now the heir is wed, the ‘spare’, Provence, needs a wife. His aunts vie against du Barry over the choice. The danger is that the newcomer could conceive the future king if Marie fails.</desc><category></category></programme><programme channel="xWWrXQIZOlzzQ3l7Rh4AFVKblg5hv-xe8eGnoki4" start="20230112220000 +0000" stop="20230112223000 +0000" catchup-id="D5KJl8ACzmxWshBaX1rzhyQcY0QMNkFW6wnmFAtD"><title>The Apprentice: You're Fired : Bao Buns</title><date></date><icon src="https://m7be2.solocoo.tv/m7be2iphone/mmchan/mpimages/260x145/bGIRSdog-LSk-VfOJ1st3A.jpg"></icon><desc>Tom Allen is joined by a panel of experts and celebrity fans who analyse the week's task and meet the latest candidate to be fired. Find out more at bbc.co.uk/apprentice [bbc.co.uk] or by using #TheApprentice.</desc><category></category></programme>